Chapter 32 - Salt of the earth

That was it with strip clubs for me; I was done. There was nothing I could learn from it anymore. I spoke to two girls and took it as far as possible, with the predictable result. The first girl, Megan, kept her word and sent me a message on Instagram. She liked a whole bunch of my photos and commented on a few of them. Where would I take it from there? Another date? Another bed? Another disappointment?

This would be a perfect recipe if I was interested in having sex with as many women as possible, but that’s a fool’s errand rooted in insecurities. I’d take quality over quantity any time. The quality of the person over the volume; the quality of sex over new experiences. Sometimes, the variety of sexual experiences is a vertical proposition, like bringing in toys or another girl into play, rather than constantly changing lovers.

I was tired and needed some rest from psychological pressure. I had one of the best nights of my life, just to be followed by the same old problem as always. It was time for me to take care of it, and Dan promised to help. After finishing my food, I went back upstairs, took a long shower, groomed myself, stripped down the bed, and asked the reception desk to send the crew in hazmat suits up and fix the room after the night of debauchery. When I looked at it, I laughed, thinking Caligula would be proud of me.

There is something weirdly relaxing about New York City. One could switch off, disappear, merge with the crowds, and blend into the background. Unlike California, the New Yorkers walked. I didn’t look like a strange foreign weirdo who went against the grain in New York. The city was like London: imposing and hurried, with pockets of calm where you can sit down and breathe for a while, have coffee, and have cake.

You hear about New York pizza, and I wanted to try it, so I asked around, and people sent me this way or another. Everyone had a different preference, a different view on the matter. What makes a great pizza is as subjective as choosing which woman is prettier, a blonde or a brunette.

After some time, I found what promised to be an original Italian place. I was sure it wouldn’t be as good as in Europe, but it was an adventure. By then, I had worked up an appetite, and the slice tasted sublime. Whether original or not, it was made moot by my hunger, so I ate it with gusto and ordered some coffee.

Sometimes, It feels nice to just sit down and breathe, look at the people passing by, living their lives, and work hard to build their future. Green people, blue people, some wearing colourful mohawks, others with shaved heads, in all shapes and sizes, milled about like ants, adding to the chaos, creating the tapestry of life. Imagine all the world without colour, just shades of grey where everyone thinks and does the same, no different and everyone is the same. I wouldn’t want that, a Pleasantville nightmare.

I lost track of time, watching the world and thinking, examining my experiences, trying to assign them to their places. Each into one box; now march, move. There were so many things to weigh and consider, too many potential mistakes. My plan started to unfold, and I was committed. The only thing left for me was to wait it out and survive the fallout. The storm was coming, and I was prepared. It would change everything.

The waiter came over, and I paid, leaving a generous tip. I didn’t know where I was and was reluctant to look up the phone map. Eventually, as it started to get dark, I surrendered to my curiosity and learned I was on the Lower East Side. The scenery changed; the people were poorer. I saw a few groups of rough sleepers. Everyone tried to do what they could to survive, equally a bum and a gentleman. We just walked on different sides of the street to avoid each other, but with one stroke of bad luck, that line blurred, and we fell. We all lived only one life.

I saw druggies and people in terrible shape, living, surviving from day to day. It made me think there is always a bottom below the one you stand on, and it sometimes comes with a great fall. As I walked around, I saw misery and despair, as well as hope and friendship. I saw people trying to help each other, having nothing to give but share each other’s warmth. This was a humanity in the making, the far end of a grinder that chewed up and spat out everyone. It put so many things into perspective.

I heard a little cry as I passed an alley, but I decided not to get involved and just walked away. A hundred yards later, I turned around and walked back. I couldn’t get it out of my mind. It was a young girl, no more than twenty, emaciated and covered by garbage and ripped newspapers. She looked like a junky, and I knew it was a problem I couldn’t solve. Yet, something pulled me there. Perhaps it was my guilt from just walking around with pockets full of cash while others starved.

The girl looked terrible, like an abandoned dog, sick and suffering, wearing a ruined T-shirt that used to be burgundy and black cut-off jeans that smelled of urine. Her hair was long and used to be blond. Everything about this girl was in the past tense, was, used to be, before, some time ago. What she was at that moment is “ruined.”

I had never seen someone so thin before. The girl couldn’t be more than eighty pounds with her clothes. Her arms were bony, and her face was skeletal. The only thing human on her was her big blue eyes and her teeth, which, thanks to some miracle, remained whole and reasonably white. She was the poster child for a junky on her last stretch, a few more months before she expired. It was a terrible thought. There goes another soul into the void.

If I gave her money, she would use it for drugs or get robbed. If I got her food, it would get stolen. If I called someone, nobody would come. It was a shit deal for everyone. That’s why most people just walked away. It was too big of a problem for them, and I wasn’t even local. I didn’t live there.

I reached for my wallet to give her a hundred bucks, more to assuage my conscience than to truly help. It ripped my heart apart. The girl was going to die, and I wanted to run away from there. I was too much of a coward to do anything that mattered, so I rolled the cash and put it into her hand. She watched me do it with her endless blue eyes. Tears came into mine. I wanted to kill someone; I wanted to cry. That was another human dying in front of me, and I was disgusted by it. It made me face my own hypocrisy. I was the proverbial rich man using a hundred bucks to clean the dog shit from the soles of his shoes. It was a shame; I was ashamed of myself.

As I stood up to go, the girl grabbed my sleeve, and my first instinct was to take off my jacket and run away.

“Please,” she said, and I froze. Everything seemed so much worse when she talked. “Please help me,” she begged. Nobody ever begged me for anything in my life, and her eyes were so deep, endless, and vulnerable. I didn’t know what to do; I panicked. I squatted next to her, feeling helpless.

“I am scared,” she said, tears rolling down her eyes. She took my hand into hers and trembled. “I was raped.” Imagine a ball of bile rising from the depth of your stomach, climbing up into your throat, and the metallic taste of saliva just as you are about to puke. All I could think of was the pizza I ate and how embarrassing it would feel if the girl saw that. She was starving, and I was picky.

“What can I do?”

“Please help me. Please save me.” Fuck my life. What could I do? Put her into a program? Get her clean? Give her a new chance? Then what? Throw her back where I found her? I almost screamed. Never before did I want to run away from something more. I’d rather be naked in a pit full of vipers. My entire body was covered in goosebumps, the wrong kind. It made me feel like millions of scabies were burrowing under my skin. I wanted to jump out of it and run.

This is what happens when you dress up nicely in a tailor-made suit and custom shoes, then go slumming it at the human zoo, watching the indigent, feeling bad about them, and then walking away. I was stuck between two massive rocks, and they were grinding my soul.

“Forget it!” My mind screamed at me. Was I a man or a piece of shit? There was no way in hell I would be able to let the girl die. I just wasn’t built that way. All the things I learned, all the glimpses I had of myself, led me to this moment, and I see it clearly now. It wasn’t a contour of who I was anymore, a murky, shadowy image of myself. Whoever I used to be in my past life crushed and crumbled into dust at that very moment. The last remnant of the cocoon was gone, and I was out in all my glory, for better and worse, but I wasn’t a butterfly. I was something else, with sharp teeth and scales reflecting the sunshine in a rainbow of colours, basking in the warmth.

“How old are you?” I asked. She looked up as if searching for the answers.

“I turned eighteen three days ago.”

“Where are your parents?” She just burst into tears and curled into a ball. That told me everything I needed to know, and I couldn’t stop myself, so I spat onto the floor to clear the bile in my mouth.

“If I am going to risk helping you, then you must obey my every word, or we are done.” The girl’s eyes got big, and her pupils dilated. “It means from this moment, you would be mine.” She nodded her head quickly, and her tears ran. Memories of Tara went through my head as I said that.

“Repeat it. I want you to say exactly what will happen.” She cried, and her hands trembled.

“I will be your property. I will obey everything.” This wasn’t what I said, but it was a good enough equivalent. It would work for now, at least until I could figure things out.

“Are you sure that you want this?” She nodded her head again.

“Yes, sir, I promise,” she said and bawled.

It was surreal. What kind of monster would make such a deal with someone so vulnerable? Of course, the girl would accept anything I said. She was at the very bottom, at the very end of the rope. She had no chance, no escape; she would die in days. Someone raped her recently, and who knows how often it happened. The girl looked like a skeleton, barely alive. Then I came and dangled the salvation, but the only thing I wanted in return was her body and soul, her very essence. She was trading one evil for another. So desperate.

“Can you walk?” She nodded. “Follow me.” It took some effort for her to stand up. She swayed on her feet and ambled forward. Her leg shook weirdly, so I offered her a hand. The girl grabbed my arm instead and used it to keep me stable.

“What is your name?”

“Dixie,” she almost whispered. I knew the story. She was a runaway from somewhere worse than where I found her, probably somewhere in the Midwest, judging by her accent. She must have been fifteen or sixteen when she left home. It takes years to do this level of damage to someone. She was so young, and her life was almost over. The only reason she wasn’t picked up by traffickers by now was that she looked terrible, like a skeleton with skin stretched over it and a dirty old wig someone found in the garbage. I wondered who would even want to rape a broken-down creature like that. It was a biological miracle.

I saw a cab pass, and I flagged it down. The driver looked at me strangely as I pushed the homeless girl inside, but money is money, and he didn’t comment. I asked him to stop by a sporting goods store and a drugstore on the way, hopped out and returned with four big plastic bags, then we were away.

The best thing about five-star places is they don’t ask their guests too many questions. A guest is the law at five-star, and they kill you with kindness. You snap your fingers, and they bow down. Even the best-trained staff couldn’t help but stare at the man leading a homeless girl through the lobby and into the elevator.

Dixie looked around wide-eyed as if she had never seen this kind of luxury before, and she probably hadn’t. I secretly smiled at the girl. That’s what she really was, a baby, barely eighteen. We didn’t speak at all, but the more time I spent watching her, the better I felt about taking her off the streets. I might be a monster for what I would unleash in my professional life, but I did at least one good deed on the other side. The real question is whether I did it for her or myself. Was I altruistic or selfish? I guessed time would tell.

“Stop here, wait.” Dixie froze as soon as I closed the door behind us. “Take off your clothes and throw them inside.” She shuddered when I ordered her to undress, but she did it without complaint, unbuttoning her jeans with trembling fingers. “Underwear too, everything.” Her eyes glistened as she undressed, and she bit her lip but did what she was told.

“Now, hold this.” I gave her a brand-new black bean bag and removed all my clothes, including the shoes. She looked at me with wide eyes, took a step back, but kept herself stable. “Hand it over.” I took the bag with my clothes and the one with hers, tied them off, and put them to the side before tiptoeing into the shower, carrying a white plastic bag I got at the drug store and waving her over.

Everything changed when Dixie felt the hot water. She closed her eyes and sighed. I took this opportunity to look at her body, which was terrible. Dixie was thinner than I initially estimated. I could see every rib, even from the back, every bone, including the vertebrae. She was dangerously underweight and starved.

Once upon a time, Dixie might have been cute, even attractive. She was about five-nine with a pleasant bone structure. Who knows, maybe in some other life, she could have been a model or an actress, but here, in this existence, she was nobody and nothing, irrelevant to anyone.

She jumped a little, feeling my hand on her shoulder, but calmed herself. I rubbed the sulphur soap all over her body and waited. She took a bar and soaped me up as well, starting with my back. I don’t think she had ever washed a man. In my mind, I thanked Tara for teaching me proper hygiene.

When Dixie was done soaping me up, I turned around and washed her hair, passing on the shampoo to her, and she did mine. Her face was still red from embarrassment when she rubbed my genitals with a soap bar. I caught her staring at my cock a few times. I used the shower handle to rinse us off, then I took a fine-tooth comb and went through her hair once, squatted, and knocked the comb against the floor. Hundreds of little bugs fell off and started to run.

Dixie watched with big eyes, finally realising what I was doing. I took a bottle of special shampoo and rubbed it into her hair. She took it from me and did the same, and then we just waited. After five minutes, we washed it away, then applied treatment again, just in case. In the end, when I combed Dixie’s hair again and knocked it against the floor, all the bugs that fell were dead, not moving at all.

This is when I opened another bottle of chemicals, poured some onto a brush, and scrubbed Dixie all over. She mewed in response, not liking the roughness, but it was necessary. I needed to massage the chemical into every pore. I didn’t test for it, but I was sure Dixie had scabies.

She brushed me back, and we waited, washed off, and then brushed ourselves again. In the end, I stopped the water and took another bottle of chemicals. It was a white cream, and I rubbed it everywhere, covering every inch of Dixie’s body, including her hair, and rubbing it into her scalp. It would be funny to see how she looked, but scabies are terrible, and you have to get rid of them as soon as possible; otherwise, you might never get rid of them.

It took some twenty minutes for the lotion to be absorbed by the skin, and we got out of the bathroom. I gave Dixie a bathrobe while I put on another. We finally could sit down and look at each other. Dixie was the first one to smile.

“Are you hungry?” She nodded quickly, so I went to the mini bar and pulled out some chocolates and two cans of Coke. Then we sat down and shared. Dixie ate fast, stuffing her face. That’s what I was afraid of. She was starved, but I couldn’t have ordered her a meal yet. I had to build up her stomach first. After two Mars bars and a soda, Dixie started to lose consciousness. It was late, and I was exhausted, so I lay on the bed and tapped beside me.

She climbed on top and lay there, keeping her distance. To calm her, I gently stroked her hair. It took some time for her to get comfortable and move closer until she rested her back against my chest. I hugged her from the back, and she wrapped her little hands around mine, and like that, she passed out.

The exhaustion must have finally caught up with me. It was well into the morning when I woke up. Dixie was sitting in a lotus position at the end of the bed. She must not have noticed or cared that her bathrobe was open. I had a clear view of her genitals and nipples. She had no breasts, not even a little, flat as a board. I wouldn’t expect anything else from someone so emaciated.

Dixie followed my gaze and blushed but didn’t attempt to cover herself. I smiled at her and offered my hand. She smiled back and rolled on the bed, getting close and letting me hug her tight. After the initial shock, Dixie appeared stable and needed a cuddle. I would imagine there are few cuddling opportunities for people living on the street or homeless.

“Are you hungry?” She nodded. I figured out she woke up at some point at night and had the rest of the chocolate, two more cans of soda, salted nuts, and a small can of Pringles. It made me happy. At least her appetite wasn’t destroyed.

“Come, let’s have a shower, then go down for breakfast.” She almost jumped. This time, our shower went without issues. Dixie took the sulphur soap and rubbed it all over my body. It was morning, and my erection raged. She looked at it without a word and worked around it. I did the same to her, soaped her body, then took some Pantene, washed her hair, conditioned it, and washed everything off after doing mine.

While she was brushing her hair, I unpacked a brand new pair of teal lace-up sports leggings with a matching hoodie. It still looked big on her even though it was the extra-small size. Dixie looked much better, though, wearing a fresh set of clothes without underwear. The sporting goods store didn’t have any to sell.

Dixie put on her new socks and sneakers while I put on latex gloves and carried two garbage bags outside, flagging down the room service and cleaning the rooms on the other end.

“Can you please dispose of this? It likely contains scabies.” The woman didn’t even blink. She put on her heavy-duty gloves and carried them away, probably to be incinerated. I handed her colleague the bag with my clothes, asking her to use all the precautions, fumigate them, and dry clean them. They were too expensive to just throw away.

Dixie’s eyes popped out as soon as she saw breakfast. So much food was served on the tables, which looked like a banquet. I chastised myself for being amused. Of course, the poor homeless girl never entered a five-star hotel. She wanted everything all at once, but I held her hand.

“The breakfast won’t finish for the next two hours, so pace yourself.” I didn’t want her to get sick, but I understood she wanted to try everything, so I taught her how to do it: take a tiny bit and then take more if she liked it. Even with all that, Dixie returned to the table, carrying three plates loaded with food. I had to slow her down a few times, make her chew, and savour the taste.

Even with all that, she was only able to eat half a plate. She almost cried when the waiters came to take what was left and throw it into the garbage at the end of the breakfast. Food was scarce where she lived, delicious food like that, and there was no reason to throw it away.

“Here, come with me,” I offered my hand, and she grabbed it without hesitation. My Vertu concierge had made an appointment, and the car was already waiting. We only went a dozen blocks before coming out in front of a private clinic. Dixie was scared, but I stared her down, and the nurse took her away while I did all the paperwork.

In the end, the doctor called me inside, explaining that things were much better than they appeared. There were signs of significant recent vaginal bruising but a lot of signs of previous trauma. He didn’t want to speculate, but I connected the dots. This wasn’t the first time Dixie was raped.

The doctor went on, listing a range of issues—improperly healed broken bones and muscle tears. Those were old but countless. I remembered how Dixie curled up in fear when I asked about her parents. As for the rest of it, things weren’t as bad as I thought. To my great surprise, she wasn’t a junkie but had a tapeworm infestation. Combined with the lack of food availability and quality nutrients, Dixie looked like a skeleton when left untreated.

“We only found chlamydia, but no other sexually transmitted diseases,” the doctor went on, listing all the tests which proved negative. We will get another confirmation in about a week. It takes some time for the lab to grow all the hepatitis cultures. It turned out Dixie only had hair and body lice, but not scabies. The treatment we did last night killed them all, and she got rid of them.

The doctor pulled out two pills, explaining that the red one was Praziquantel and the other Azithromycin. One treated the tapeworm, and the other with chlamydia. Dixie also had a urinary tract infection. He gave her a course of Amoxicillin to start in two days so as not to overload her system and advised no irritants like alcohol or coffee.

This is where he went into a spiel on proper nutrition and regular checkups, pointing out that she should return in a month to verify everything was clear. The process took four hours, but when we got out, Dixie held tight to my arm, looking up at me with her big blue eyes like she saw a god. She knew something was terribly wrong, and she thought it was AIDS or cancer, but it was just a stupid tapeworm that died after one pill. She didn’t even have to receive a shot. All her other blood work was fine, a little strained due to her terrible general state, but the doctor was adamant she would be fine.

“She is eighteen and still growing, at the peak of her health. With a lot of love and care, I see no reason for her not doing well.” It was a medical way full of double negatives to say she would be fine, and I’ve never seen Dixie happier. We walked down the road like fathers and daughters, and she kept thanking me for everything I did.

I made an appointment for her at a beauty place. As soon as we walked in, they rolled her inside, the haircut and treatment, the skin treatment, the laser removal of her pussy and armpit hair, manicure, pedicure, makeup, the works. It took another three hours, and when she walked out, I made a double-take. Dixie completely transformed. I surmised she would be stunning after gaining some weight.

Dixie couldn’t believe what was happening. She looked into every reflective surface, trying to find herself, but the only one she could see was a super slim cutie with beautiful, clean, voluminous, dirty blonde hair. The next stop was a lingerie store, and I bought her two bags full of nighties, panties, teddies, and such, all silk and lace, but no bras. She didn’t need any.

Finally, in the end, we hit a department store where I bought her a little mountain of high heels and dresses, all the high street brands like H&M and such, nothing really fancy, as I expected her to fill out at least a size. I got her a makeup kit, and the consultant taught her how to apply it. At the fitness store, I bought her a whole bag of supplements, primarily vitamins, immune boosters, and weight gain proteins—chocolate, vanilla, and strawberry. We could barely carry it to the car, and the bellboy helped us.

As soon as the doors closed behind us, Dixie fell to the floor and cried. She bent over and kissed my feet over and over again, sobbing like someone died. It was heartbreaking to watch. I tried to lift her up, but she didn’t let me. I tried to walk, but she held onto my feet, kissing them repeatedly. All the emotions Dixie had kept bottled up for a day, she let out in a heart-wrenching burst of tears. For almost half an hour, I stood there helpless and watched her cry.

“Are you hungry?” I asked when Dixie calmed down a little, and she jumped. It was a silly rhetorical question. She was always hungry and starved. I was wrong about so many things. The girl could eat and not get sick. It’s just the damn tapeworm ate all of it, and she had little to start with.

It took Dixie forever to choose what to wear. Such a resplendent choice had never happened before, and she was torn between all of it. After some twenty minutes, I told her what to put on, and she stripped in front of me without even blinking. That’s when I saw her perfectly smooth pussy. It looked pretty and petite, just a little line with two puffy sides.

Dixie grinned, meeting my eyes, catching me in my lascivious lurking. She was a woman, all right, and it excited her to be ogled by a man sexually, not because there was no other choice, but because she actually wanted, imagined in a sexual way, and desired. It did wonders for her sense of value. She wasn’t a throwaway street urchin anymore, but a woman with a pretty pussy a man with many options found attractive.

I took Dixie to the restaurant downstairs and ordered spaghetti and meatballs for her, with beef soup for starters and chocolate mousse as a dessert. I never saw anyone eat with such gusto, and I had to slow her hand. Her instinct was to just stuff her face with everything.

Despite all my guidance, she ate all her food in record time and looked at me, then at my glass with chocolate mousse, and then back at me. I pushed the glass towards her, and she smiled like a kid, so I waved the waiter over and ordered one more with marshmallow bits on top, plus another dozen to be delivered to the room’s fridge.

Dixie watched with big eyes as one more glass was delivered, licking her lips. The waiter got her a cup of hot chocolate while I got coffee. I could tell she struggled to swallow, but she couldn’t stop. Luckily, the food ended, and she sat back, breathing hard, like after running a marathon.

As soon as we got into a room, Dixie went to the toilet while I checked the fridge. The chocolate mousse was delivered. I wanted to keep it as a bit of surprise if Dixie woke up early again and decided to have a snack.

“Eww,” I heard a little scream, then swearing, followed by a shower. I didn’t want to ask; I knew what was happening. The pill worked, and the tapeworms were coming out. I checked it out on the internet earlier, and it was the stuff of horror. The doctor gave me another pill for her to take in a week, just in case. Dixie’s infection was quite dire and took a long time, so I expected many more Ewws in the coming time.

I hopped in and took a shower. It was a long day, and my skin still itched from the psychosomatic effect of imagining scabies. I put on my bathrobe and sat on the bed. Dixie had all her new clothes out of the bag and sorted into piles. It seemed her state of undress didn’t bother her at all. On the contrary, she seemed to enjoy being watched by me.

“Why don’t you try them on for me,” I suggested, and Dixie clapped her hands. She would put on an outfit, and I would score it from one to ten. Dixie especially liked thin, almost transparent lace panties and the effect they had on me. Even though she looked like a skeleton, her tiny pussy looked attractive, and she noticed that.

Dixie put on various combinations and entertained me for over an hour. I was getting a little tired, so I dimmed the light and watched, slowly dozing off, wondering where she got all this energy; then a formula popped into my mind, the calories consumed divided by her weight and virtually zero body fat. All this had to go somewhere somehow. At this age, Dixie was unlikely to ever build enough fat cells to look anything but slim, and she would probably never grow any tits.

My eyes popped open. I felt a warm hand on my balls. Before I could even focus my eyes, Dixie had my cock in her mouth and was sucking it slowly. I wanted to tell her to stop, but it felt so good, so I bit my tongue and let her do what she liked. In no minutes flat, my cock was a rigid pole, and she sucked it slowly, probably not even trying to make me cum. She feasted on my member like it contained a treat inside. After some twenty minutes of slow, steady sucking and rubbing the underside of my cockhead with her tongue, my cock started to twitch and spurt semen.

Without missing a beat, Dixie gulped all my sperm down to the last drop, then, keeping her head on my leg, she continued sucking like nothing happened, like I just rewarded her with my essence, and she continued. I was too tired and still floating on my cloud nine from the post-orgasmic haze when I closed my eyes and drifted to the la la land.

Chapter 33 - Mr Nice Guy

I barely noticed my flight back home. The last day in New York was an emotional rollercoaster. Dixie cried all day, petrified that I would never return and she would be on the street again. Even the meeting with my lawyer couldn’t assuage her fears. I bought her a cellphone, installed Instagram, and connected it to mine so we could be in touch. Then, I rented a reasonable apartment for a month and gave her a prepaid credit card with a thousand bucks. Her job was to eat well and exercise while the lawyer sorted out her passport. It was an incredibly complicated and costly procedure for someone homeless without any papers and applying for documents while living in another state. It made me think of England, the home of the red tape.

“Please don’t abandon me, please. I will do anything,” Dixie went on and on. How many tears can a person cry before drying up? Dixie cried all day. She even seasoned her steak with her tears. It made it a little easier when I connected her with Tara, as both girls were from the US. The two talked, and Dixie kept asking her to promise I wouldn’t change my mind. I had never seen such desperation before. In the end, I pulled her into my lap, kissed her lips, and everything changed. She hugged me so tight I thought she would pull a muscle and her body would unravel into a heap of bones.

“You promised to obey me. Yes?” Dixie frantically nodded. “Who are you to me?”

“I am your property. You own me.” It was a bad idea to get her to talk to Tara. She only reinforced this idea, telling her about her own life and how she was also my property. I didn’t have time to unpick that mess, and it would have been helpful for the moment if Dixie had believed it.

“So, do you think I would throw away something I own?” She shook her head.

“But…” I slapped her butt.

“But, nothing. You are mine, and you’re coming to London. End of discussion.” The poor girl almost snapped to attention like a soldier. Someone, somewhere in her past, trained her this way through fear, but oddly enough, Dixie found comfort in such a direct approach. She liked it when I took her choice away and ordered her what to do rather than let her decide by herself. Whatever happened to her, someone taught Dixie to be obedient.

Lamin met me at the airport and took my rolling hardshell suitcase with a curious smile. When it persisted during our drive, I got suspicious.

“The girls planned something, didn’t they?”

“It is not my place to say, sir,” he said and chuckled. I shrugged. This was my life; I made it, and now I had to live it. I was a victim of my own success. We hit a traffic jam, and I asked Lamin to stop.

“I need a breath of fresh air. Let’s park up somewhere and grab a cup of coffee.” Lamin nodded, and ten minutes later, we were sitting outside a lovely local pub, and I was having a pint. I hadn’t had cider in ages, and this place had a good one. Lamin and I sat and talked for a while. I would ask questions, and he would answer. At one moment, he looked at me in a strange way.

“Excuse me, sir, may I ask you something personal?” I thought he would ask me about my life, but Lamin took me by surprise.

“Would you maybe have some more work for me?” He explained that he was struggling with money. Most of what he made he sent to Gambia to support his family, but it wasn’t enough. He had three sisters and two brothers, all of them younger, but they were growing up and needed more food, clothes, things for school, everything, and this job was what separated them from poverty.

“Unfortunately, not at the moment, but maybe I will in a few months.” He expected that answer, and I thought that was it, but I was wrong.

“Don’t you like black women?” That came out of left field. I wasn’t expecting a question like that. It made me smile, bringing back memories of the voluptuous black goddess I slept with when I met Dan for the first time and how great she made me feel. I laughed.

“I like black women just fine.” This made Lamin smile.

“I could give you my eldest sister for twenty-five thousand dollars.” This would sound surreal if I knew nothing about Gambia. It is a majority Islamic country, and Lamin wasn’t selling his sister but talking about a dowry. It was a traditional proof and a sign of commitment to give the girl’s father a dowry. A dowry was customary in Europe a hundred years back, so I wasn’t shocked.

“You know I am not looking for a wife, and I have other women. I don’t think it would work.” Lamin looked down, and I couldn’t tell, but I thought he was blushing. He pulled a picture of his sister on his phone, and I almost gasped. She was breathtaking, tall and slim with the body of a goddess. I nearly choked, and Lamin laughed, telling me this was a common reaction by everyone who saw her, but only a few people did because she always wore conservative clothing.

“She was supposed to marry this year when she turned eighteen, but the groom bailed out.” He and the father agreed on a ten-thousand-dollar dowry, which was peanuts for such a beauty, but there was a problem. Someone caught Lamin’s sister kissing another girl at the age of fifteen, which escalated into a whole debate about the wisdom of female circumcision. The older people maintained that this would never have happened if the girl had been circumcised as a child. Some suggested it should be done now, but it was against the law. The government deemed This custom barbaric, and laws were made to prevent that.

None of this helped the young girl. Everyone learned she was perceived as a “lesbian pervert,“ and nobody wanted her in their house. The man who wanted to marry her could negotiate such a low dowry just by using this fact. Still, when it came down to it, his family exerted control, and the arrangement failed. The poor girl was seen as a wrong choice, and her family was tainted. That’s why they were poor. Nobody wanted to give good work to a family perceived as perverts. It got me thinking, and the lightbulbs started to fire.

“Are you sure she would fit into my family without a problem?” We were talking now, and Lamin knew he had me hooked. Twenty-five grand would solve his financial problem in Africa, and he could complete his studies and get a well-paid job with a starting yearly salary of sixty thousand pounds.

“I am sure, sir. If you want, I could talk to my dad.”

“I would prefer if you talked to your sister and explained everything. I don’t want a woman who is with me out of duty.” I could see Lamin was excited. It was time to negotiate the price.

“If I marry your sister and pay twenty-five thousand dollars, I want something in return. I want you to come and work for me as a Chief Operating Officer for the same salary the investment firm offered you.” That surprised him.

“Would it be okay if I think about it, sir?” I couldn’t ask for anything more. We finished our drinks, and Lamin drove me home. It was a win-win for everyone, a checkmate. Everything in life could be described through a strategy game. If I took his sister, I would fix the problem in Africa. Lamin’s father would get enough cash to raise all the kids, and I would get someone I trust to be the COO of my company for the price of an entry-level student at a hedge fund firm. What’s best is his loyalty would be absolute because we would be family. All of it was tied into a nice little bow. I just loved when things came together like this.

***

“Come next door,” the yellow post-it read. Lamin just shrugged with a wicked smile. I went to Amy’s apartment and opened the door. Instantly, there was a scream, “Surprise!” and party poppers released, launching colourful confetti into the air.

It was a surprise, all right. I was expecting Tara and Amy, but Rylee and Callie were also there. They secretly used the tickets I bought and perfectly timed their travel to the UK while I was in New York. This was their secret revenge for travelling to the US and not inviting them.

“You’re not going to get rid of us this easy,” Rylee joked while Callie climbed my back like a chipmunk. Tara clung to me; Amy kissed my cheek. Lamin stood by the door with a big smile, recording all of it for posterity and Instagram followers. I burst into laughter and started kissing everyone. Something in me changed, and I was truly happy after a long time. This wasn’t just a simple get-together but an example of how life could be. All of those people were my new family.

“I am starving.” My simple statement sent everyone into overdrive. I wanted to book us a fancy place, but the American girls insisted on the authentic British experience.

“So, a curry house, then? Chicken tikka masala anyone?” That didn’t go down well, and the girls pushed me onto the recliner, climbing on top of me, pretending to strangle me, throwing a kiss here and there for good measure.

“Okay, okay, I give up.” I reserved a table at The Royal Oak in Bethnal Green. The girls did a little dance, celebrating the fact I wouldn’t make them dress like princesses, so they could put on casual clothes and just enjoy themselves. It was a slippery slope.

It was all a ruse. By the time we got ready, I was the worst one dressed there. The girls united against me and shared their clothes, making all sorts of combinations and looking like supermodels. They chirped about this and that, jumping from one subject to another. I closed my eyes, and my thoughts drifted on with a smile. This felt like a big family gathering to celebrate a birthday or something. I was glad the girls shared the same language, behaving like sisters. There was no trace of jealousy between them, quite the opposite. Sharing the same man seemed to unite them. It gave them a strong common theme, and they felt comfortable with each other.

Sometimes, I wondered how did I manage to pull that off? The only way I could explain it was that, inadvertently, as I tried to avoid settling into another relationship, I failed to define this, whatever one may call it. I never called any of them a girlfriend or gave the girls any label. We were together and happy. It’s all that mattered. Perhaps they all figured out independently that it didn’t matter how we named it. Somehow, it worked, and I wouldn’t poke at it. Some magic tricks are meant to remain a secret.

I always imagined entering an English pub with a group of women. It wasn’t a fantasy anymore as four girls and I walked into The Royal Oak, and a waitress took us to our table. Everyone in the place stared at us, including the staff. The girls were dressed to impress, and I was wearing my casual attire, still made by Savile Row tailors, only with a relaxed feel to it. Rylee and Callie immediately took the seats by my side. They hadn’t seen me in a long time and wanted some love.

Instead of each ordering a meal, I ordered a lot for everyone to share, with five empty plates, so we could have a bit of a banquet. Getting used to that kind of communal living would be easy, with family getting together for dinner. The only thing missing was the kids, but I was working on that. My ex, Tina, must have called me a thousand times, leaving all sorts of nasty, threatening messages, texting me about taking me to court or sending her man to find me and break a few bones.

Tina was getting desperate because her boyfriend was desperate, and she needed the money to pay someone back. The man got himself involved in some shady business, lost some cash he didn’t have, and desperately looked for a way out, so he’d been pressuring Tina in different ways, asking her for money to fend off the beatings. The guy was a sleaze from the very beginning, and I had been paying for years so he could sneak around behind my back and sleep with my wife.

When we divorced, it was a tough time for the guy. The judge decided how much she got, and she was giving at least half to her man. Lately, it wasn’t enough for his appetite, so he kept pressing Tina for more and more cash, helping her come up with schemes to extort more, using my sons as bargaining collateral. Effectively, he kept my children ransom.

After I stopped paying child support, the money dried up, and whoever the guy owed began putting pressure on him to pay up. The man took a beating, then came to my ex-wife to blame her for everything because she didn’t give him cash. This, in turn, caused an avalanche, and Tina was going insane, threatening to harm my children.

Over the last week or so, her calls turned demented. Her brand-new car stalled and wouldn’t even move out of the drive. This forced her to use public transportation like a commoner, reminding her where she came from, and Tina didn’t like that. I would enjoy her rage if it wasn’t for my children. They took the brunt of it with nobody to help.

“Hold on, boys, help is coming,” I whispered into their ears the last time I saw them. Daddy had a plan. Just a little longer, just a little while. I smiled at the girls, tasting lamb shank, the mixed grill, the salads, the stew, and the vegetables. They laughed, talked, and jumped from subject to subject. Who would have guessed a year ago how my life would turn? If someone told me this, I would laugh in their faces, accusing them of being under the influence of something they smoked or snorted.

Amy’s loud burp brought me back from my trance. Everyone laughed, and then Tara tried to do the same. Suddenly, the girls had a burping competition, seeing who could burp louder. It started to attract the attention of other guests. It was time to call it a night before it escalated. I waved the waitress over, paid, and tipped well.

Rylee and Callie were full of energy, while Tara and Amy were ready to sleep. They ate so much that they reminded me of Dixie, yet both remained slim. It wasn’t a mystery how the two managed to stay so fit. While I was away, both used my gym, especially the pool, sauna, and spa and then they would go home and spend most of the night exhausting each other. Tara was insatiable with a perverted mind, and she was turning Amy into a nymphomaniac.

The girls went to change, and I took that opportunity to take a quick shower, put on my fancy suit, and met Rylee and Callie outside. I didn’t feel much for a walk around town or high-energy scenes, so I instructed Lamin to drive us to The Chamber. It was fun watching the girls‘ faces as we passed the entrance of a large, nondescript property with no signs outside.

As soon as they entered the main room, their eyes popped, trying to soak in everything at once. It was fun to watch. I wondered if my face looked like that when I first saw it. The place was quite busy, with plenty of members in town. I recognised a lot of faces I’d seen before, and I greeted them.

The word spread like wildfire after the waiter took our order and learned that the two girls were American. Many guys came over to introduce themselves, starting with Jean-Philippe, another French guy in his mid-fifties, born and raised in Martinique, a sole heir to a lot of real estate from colonial times. He was the “old money” kid whose only job was to not fuck it all up, and he lived a lavish lifestyle from the dividends without working a minute all his life. The legend goes he sired at least a hundred kids in his lifetime, spending a portion of his money to keep them comfortable, realising early on that he wasn’t dad material.

The girls laughed and giggled, responding to the jokes of the old player who refused to act his age. I thought it was part of his charm in the first place, brushing the whole age thing aside and acting like a playboy all his life.

In the corner seat on the other side of the bar, I saw Cassie with some younger guys, the investment banker kind. They were trying to get her drunk and interested, and she was smiling and playing games. I knew who would win, and so did all the older members. She smiled at me, and I smiled back and waved.

As the music changed, the two girls got positively aroused. Callie pulled my hand to dance, and I let myself be persuaded. Not to be outdone, Jean-Philippe offered his hand to Rylee like a courtier does to a princess.

“Puis-je vous inviter à danser, mademoiselle,“ he asked and bowed. Rylee stood up and curtsied, and the two joined us. After the song changed, JP and I switched partners, and a few more couples joined us on the floor. Why not? I read the club rules twice, and there was nothing to prevent people from dancing if they liked.

The girls wanted another drink, so JP thanked them and left. I ordered another round of cocktails and sat down on a plush brown leather sofa with a girl on each side. They wrapped their arms around mine and gurgled sweet nothings into my ear, mostly about how happy they were to see me again and how much fun they already had.

London could be daunting for first-time visitors, but the girls had the best guides. Amy was a Londoner, and Tara went exploring almost every day. Together, they were an unending source of information and entertainment. I’ve never visited Tampa, their hometown, but of all the cities I’ve seen in the US, none come close to the likes of London. Even New York and the Big Apple couldn’t compare. Sure, it had its charm, quirkiness, crowds, and imposing presence, but it lacked that “je ne sais quoi“ that joie de vivre London possesses – intangible, yet evident. Its class, history, and culture; at night, when you close your eyes, you can hear the city’s whispers.

“I am horny,“ Rylee gurgled into my ear, licking my earlobe. Callie said nothing; it was unnecessary. She was too far gone.

“Let’s go to the movie room,“ I suggested, and the girls looked at me like I said something strange. It would take too long to explain, so I stood up and pulled their hands. It was the place Cassie took me to when I became a member and allowed me to eat her pussy to an orgasm. I looked at her group and saw her watching me with big eyes. I learned quickly that “the movie room“ was a club euphemism for everything that should remain unseen.

I almost burst into laughter when I saw that the movie playing was “The Sound of Music.“ We sat on cushy chairs and watched for a moment. It was a scene with Liesl von Trapp singing “Sixteen Going on Seventeen“ and dancing in the rain with Rolf Gruber, the telegram delivery boy who later becomes a Nazi soldier. I almost laughed. The two girls loved the movie and had seen it a million times. Within seconds, all thoughts of sex vanished, and the girls sang along. That was enough for them to cuddle up to me tightly.

They don’t make films like this anymore. The sign of a good one was when the story pulls you right in, and musicals? Forget it. Hollywood is not interested, let alone Netflix. Maybe if someone pitched a beloved classic to Disney as the next project to ruin, but apart from that, if it doesn’t fly, drop bombs, or isn’t gay, nobody was interested.

It is enough to notice that the director’s award at the Sundance Festival went to a movie called “Cuties,“ which shows prepubescent girls dancing sexually, resulting in criminal felony charges against Netflix and outrage. What happened? Nothing, just like the Balenciaga bondage bear controversy. They surely were coming for our children. No wonder many people enjoyed classics like “The Sound of Music.“ Perhaps they could identify the commonalities with the world today, a story of the rise of the Third Reich for the Fourth Industrial Revolution times.

The girls giggled and sang the songs all the way home. They left their stuff at Amy’s place but pushed me into my apartment. There was no more stalling; it was business time. We took a long shower together, and the girls still talked about the movie, complaining that no more musicals were available.

“Anyone want to go and watch Phantom of the Opera with me this weekend?“ I was sure their squeals could be heard outside the apartment. The girls went nuts when I told them about The Lion King, Matilda, Les Misérables, Mamma Mia, Moulin Rouge, The Book of Mormon, and Wicked.

“We want, we want!“ the girls demanded, especially when I told them about all the cultural marvels—the British Museum, the Tate Modern, the Natural History Museum, the Royal Opera House, Madame Tussauds, and Shakespeare’s Globe Theatre. The girls wanted it all, to taste life. Who knew that just mentioning those things could get women all hot and bothered?

Rylee and Callie pushed me out of the shower until I lost my balance and fell on the bed. They jumped on top of me like a thirst of vampires.

“I want to suck your cock,” Callie said, sliding down, still trying to master the art of making me cum in seconds. Rylee was more direct, climbing on top and nestling her pussy on my face, grinding it up and down while my tongue probed her depths.

Rylee tasted fantastic, clean and musky. I could eat her pussy for hours. In fact, I did that plenty of times. One doesn’t eat a girl’s pussy purely to make her cum. I liked the smell and the taste. If it was up to me, I’d have fresh pussy for dinner every day.

I almost chuckled thinking about that. With all these girls around me, this was precisely what happened. I tried to remember the last time I went a week without a taste, and I failed. The key to a healthy life is a clean, balanced diet with all four groups represented, your carbs, proteins and fats, as well as a generous serving of willing pink pussy every day.

This was going nowhere. Rylee was trying to make herself cum on my face, but she couldn’t get her movements right, so I lifted her bit and pushed her on her back, diving straight between her legs. Instantly, she started to moan and roll her eyes, feeling all too familiar motions of the tongue against her moist privates.

Callie adapted from the other side, making me jump from the unexpected surprise. She stuck her tongue into my asshole, making my cock jump up and down, trying to swallow my balls whole, then spitting them out. I was in heaven, trying to focus on the job in front of my nose and ignore the pulsing of my cock inside Callie’s hands.

“Mmm, I’m going to,” I tried to warn her, but Callie was ahead of the game. She quickly lay on her back, pushing her head between my legs and frantically jerking my cock with its tip right inside her wide-open mouth.

I could feel the tip of Callie’s tongue lash against the tip of my cock head. It made me twitch, feeling incredible. The very moment she tried to stick her tongue inside my piss hole to get another taste of my precum, I couldn’t take any more. My balls contracted, and my cock jerked. One, two, three blasts went straight into Callie’s mouth. That’s when she lifted her head and sucked like a penis pump, forcing the very last drop of sperm from my balls right into her mouth.

On the other side, Rylee screamed, reaching her own orgasm. I was too out of it to do anything about it, riding my own pleasure wave. Callie wiggled out and pushed to the side, grabbing her best friend’s legs and pushing her up so Rylee’s pussy was up in the air. This is when Callie pushed an index finger from each side and opened Rylee’s pussy wide to a big black gape. I could see her cervix inside.

I wondered what this was all about, but Callie didn’t make me wait. From her kneeling position, she spat my sperm out, letting it drool all the way inside, covering Rylee’s cervix with a white, slimy layer like it was glazed.

My cock was instantly hard again, seeing this bizarre sperm play. The two best friends had some hardcore fantasies that only grew bigger and more elaborate with time. It shouldn’t have surprised me, as all the girls constantly talked with each other, sharing the minuscule details of who tried what and who did what to another. I imagined that I was in the top ten of their debates, wondering what I did to whom and how it felt.

This is what happens when you have two insatiable minxes at home, making you cum all the time. It happened with such predictable regularity that my body started adapting to it like it does to exercise. I found it normal to cum multiple times a day, and my balls didn’t hurt anymore. It was hard to tell what was due to constant sex, exercise, or all the supplements. I just knew for a fact that my testosterone was going up, and I couldn’t be happier.

“My turn now,” Rylee said, pushing me on all fours and licking my asshole while rubbing my cock up and down. Callie settled herself in front of me and used her hands to open her pussy wide.

It took us only about half an hour to give Callie four orgasms and me one, filling Rylee’s mouth with another serving of steaming hot baby butter. She did the same as Callie, lifted her up and spat the sperm out right into her pussy. The girls embraced and kissed.

“You’re not going to sleep until you fill all our holes,” the girls chimed, pulling on their butt cheeks to drive the statement home. This got me going again.

In the midst of this, I remembered the time we met, and they showered naked while I wondered if I should have joined them. We had come a long way since then and fucked hundreds of times, but more than that, we had developed a sort of bond all of us enjoyed.

For some reason or another, the girls had latched onto me. The conventional wisdom would dictate that the girls should have been jealous or using me for something. None of that was true. Of course, the girls enjoyed nice things and a lavish lifestyle, but this was something different. The girls genuinely loved doing all sorts of things with me, and not just having sex.

We were all happy, naked, and sweaty, lying on our backs, hugging each other. I would kiss one then another, and the girls would coo and hug me tighter while absent-mindedly playing with my cock.

“Okay, next round,” I demanded, pushing Callie onto her back, getting on top of her, mounting her, and slowly pumping my cock inside. This was life.

Chapter 34 - Evil Dick

The day started with gloom and rain. People on the street wore long tweed coats and tiny black foldable umbrellas. I watched their black shoes splash water out of puddles. It would be my first day in the office, and I wasn’t looking forward to playing that game. I fired a first salvo with the whole woke nonsense, but nobody was fooled, I was sure. The only thing I managed was to create a record of disagreement, playing chess with a vastly superior opponent.

I was right. As soon as I came into my office, my secretary sent me a message to meet Diarmaid at ten. I had a sense that just like The Boomtown Rats, Diarmaid would remind me why I don’t like Mondays. It was to be expected. Like most people, I disliked confrontation and blame, but it was necessary. I couldn’t quit my job, and they wouldn’t let me get my way.

One look at my secretary was enough for me to understand that everyone knew something was happening, and my career was hanging by a thread. I was a marionette controlled by greater interests, and one of my cords got cut off and others entangled. I went to the canteen and got a full mug of coffee. This place, this office, carried so many memories. My time here was ending, and I missed it already. I spent years here, in this prison of the mind, doing what I was told and spinning the plates.

All my dreams and plans of moving vertically with time were crushed. Nobody would hire a techie for the CTO role without the same person being a political monster. Ironically, I have become one now, but a little too late and way too aggressive. I pulled out the “gay card,” and human resources got involved, playing this by the book lest it affect our ESG scores.

Diarmaid always despised gay people or anyone different. He did his utmost to manipulate the other managers to shift them around, restructure and get them the hell out of his department. The man was a bigot and racist, with a closet homosexual son and a daughter he wanted to fuck. His own perversion sickened him, and he took it out on everyone. Still, he was a shrewd political player, never letting anyone learn about that.

How did I find out? Simple. The secrets never stay secrets with the computer systems. He used our in-house psychologist, who recorded all his notes in a database on his computer. It turns out it wasn’t encrypted. When I proposed the system, my architectural design insisted on encrypting the sensitive data at rest to satisfy non-functional legislative requirements but guess what? It was too costly, so the managers decided we didn’t need to do that. In fact, it was Diarmaid himself who signed the waiver. I found it equally ironic as funny because of my role; I had access to everything.

This was, in fact, how I found the other Jim for Lexi. He was the best candidate, one of the directors of legal compliance. Diarmaid and Jim never saw each other face to face. Jim was a stickler for rules and often a pain in Diarmaid’s neck. To add insult to injury, Jim was favoured by the current CEO as a replacement, but the rest of the board favoured Diarmaid.

I had no clue what Lexi planned, but given the two’s history, Jim was the best option for Lexi’s revenge against Diarmaid. She never told me the ins and outs of it, and I didn’t have to know it, but whatever it was, given the animosity of two men, it wouldn’t reflect great on Diarmaid. Everyone knew, up and down the food chain, that whichever one wins the CEO job would squeeze the other one out. It was inevitable.

Lexi smiled as she passed by me, carrying two cups of coffee. Somehow she got herself employed by my company. I thought to stop and greet her briefly, but Lexi turned her head, pretending not to know me. She was planning something, and it made me wonder. Curiosity killed the cat, they said. Whatever it was, I better take care and stay the hell away from Diarmaid or the company before whatever Lexi planned started to happen.

At ten sharp, I knocked on Diarmaid’s door, and he pointed at the seat on the other side of his desk, not even lifting his head to greet me. I shrugged and sat down. Those kinds of mind-control tactics didn’t work on me anymore. The good thing about knowing you’re out and accepting it is that the other side loses the power to use it. I didn’t just accept my fate; I counted on it, and the game changed. It wasn’t whether I get fired, but how it happens and when.

“Do you know why I called you here?” White pawn to C4, an English opening. The man liked to start strong, and I was game.

“Your message didn’t specify why you wanted to see me. I couldn’t speculate.”

“That was some shit you pulled with the human resources.”

“You chose Dick for CTO despite the fact he is incompetent because he is a political brown-nosing animal and would do what you say without complaint. I was just showing you that I could do the same and more.” Diarmaid smiled. He hated me for defying him, but he enjoyed me using Dick this way. Dick was the wrong choice, everyone knew that, but his obedience couldn’t be questioned.

“Tell me, why shouldn’t I fire you right now?”

“For what cause? Because I am lesbian? That won’t fly with Jim in statutory compliance.” Diarmaid smacked his knees and laughed so hard that, for a moment, I thought he’d come off his chair.

“You and I know that you’re not gay.” I shrugged.

“What people believe and what the records reflect are often different.” We stopped talking and had a staring contest. I could see anger in Diarmaid’s eyes, but all he could see in mine was resignation. I was resigned to losing this way or another.

“Watch yourself, Jim. You’re treading on thin ice.”

“Would that be all, sir?” he waved me away. Stalemate. Someone said, choose your enemies wisely, and I just made my choice. Diarmaid would look to change a score soon, but he won’t dirty his hands. He was more of a cloak-and-dagger type, using puppets so as not to dirty his hands.

“One more thing,” he said as I took the door handle. “Richard is still going to be your boss. I expect you to meet with him as soon as possible. I can fire you for disobeying a legitimate order.” Diarmaid knew I wouldn’t do it, and I knew he wouldn’t dismiss me because he needed me, but it was loud and clear, the warning received. So we began with the first shot fired across the bow. It was my turn now. Do I double, or do I fold?

I sat at my desk, drinking coffee. There were no tasks to complete, and I had already taken care of everything—cleaned my desk, shredded all my printed documents, and removed any traces of tasks that were not assigned to me. All my ideas, plans for improvement, suggestions, and architectural documents that I had prepared for my new role were gone.

If someone were to walk in today and seize all the computers, they wouldn’t find anything that would explain how to manage the system without me. Diarmaid had stated on numerous occasions that my job was to keep the system alive and apply live patches. None of the knowledge remained anywhere. I had planned to form a team and push for a migration, but all that was gone.

Was all of this unprofessional or unethical? I would argue for both. The company would be within their rights to sue me, and they would win the case if anyone bothered to listen to me or look at all the collateral I had created. In not so many words, they told me to stop doing anything beyond my job. Still, I would have gone mad a long time ago if I had to come to work every day and stare at the wall, just waiting for the off chance that I was needed.

Instead, I involved myself in hundreds of projects, helping the developers and the team and doing whatever was necessary to keep my mind busy. I spent all my free time programming and creating software for the future, when one day, I would be asked to fix everything, save my company millions, and prove to everyone that I was a keeper.

All of this was gone, lost, purged from source control systems as if it had never existed. I kept everything to the contractual minimum, and everything else vanished.

Once upon a time, I had this grand idea of getting rid of our on-premise servers and migrating to the cloud. Unfortunately, that was incredibly complicated, mainly because the crucial part of our software was designed to run on mainframes, and nobody, including me, knew what it did because we had lost the source code.

With all the time I had and the help of ChatGPT, I created thousands of tests and data segments to model the inputs and outputs of a complex weighted state machine. I pushed it through the original software, which was a highly complex calculator that operated on a large set of numerical information representing airlines, flights, routes, planes, and prices. It would take all that information, chew through it in milliseconds, and return the data back, processed, sorted, and scored.

This technology was the foundation of the GDS global distribution system, which underpins transportation, the hotel industry, and many other large businesses. It was the key technology that enabled all the bookings for planes, hotels, trucks, trains, and more. In essence, if the software failed, the world would come to a halt, nothing would move, and we would go back to the classical age until it was fixed.

That’s why we needed mainframes for speed and the volume of information processed. With all the time in the world, I started from scratch, modelled inputs and outputs, and wrote thousands of tests, tweaking the algorithm. I was unable to reverse-engineer the code, concluding that it was impossible. However, I succeeded in writing a new set of algorithms that would take the same input and return the same result, taking a purely mathematical approach.

At first, I would get a massive deviation, but I got the perfect numbers after tweaking the code for over a year. I could get a sample from a live system and compare the results. The discrepancy was vanishingly slight, showing only every few million transactions and not by much.

A layman would call it artificial intelligence, but it was nothing even close to that. I made an expert system based on CLIPS, extended with a weighted statistical model. We kept the exabytes of audit log data with historic ins and outs. All I had to do was replay it inside my system, which would generate a blindingly fast code I could run straight on a CPU or Cuda core. It would scale like mad and be blindingly fast.

After failing to get it to a hundred per cent, I concluded there was a bug in the original software that was not present in my new algorithm. I used the opportunity to learn the Rust language to build a distributed system, but unlike the original mainframe developers, I had an opportunity to make the algorithm horizontally scalable, running on a swarm of commodity processor cores and graphics cards. It meant the system no longer needed mainframes, and everything could move into the cloud horizontally scaled with on-demand burstable capacity for peaks like Chrismas.

With all my enthusiasm peaked, I wrote hundreds of Terraform and Ansible scripts which would, at the press of a button, create from scratch a hybrid cloud solution using AWS and Azure for high-availability and data delivery purposes, bringing the core servers closer to zones where they were needed, thus fixing the latency issue we were unable to solve for years.

There were about fifty milliseconds of latency between the UK and the US. However, we cut it, and it was a terrible waste for the APIs at scale. It was the number one contention point between our software and our customers. Everything else was solvable, and over time, the dev teams came up with an intermediate layer serving initially proprietary data format, going to CORBA, going to SOAP, and ending with REST and JSON as the times changed.

We could do anything except change the software or move the mainframes. There was no appetite for doing that, and I found out why. The management teams knew for a fact that our client would never leave us.

The group’s CEO was getting a tax-free kickback straight into his offshore account. On top of it, there were no viable competitors. We had them by the balls. With a position like that, it was easy to feel complacent, which was why nobody listened to me. Our rolling contract was about to end in a year, and we would negotiate more money for a tech refresh, moving to the cloud, anything they wanted, and they would pay billions for that. The CEO would get his sweetener, and the world would be better.

I was the fool who thought he could save everyone, who wrote software and scripts that would do all this work in three days; how long it took for all the servers to instantiate, configure themselves, deploy all the software, and pass all the integration tests.

I could press a button and do everything I wanted, drinking coffee and browsing the internet. This also meant I would take away at least a year of work from the company and a billion dollars in charges we could suck out from the client. I wasn’t thinking straight; I was stuck in technology, not business.

It was gone, forgotten, deleted, and never spoken about again. My time in this company was ending, and yes, I was a disgruntled employee, but truth be told, it was my fault. I did it to myself. Despite the management being perfectly clear with me, I ignored them and went beyond the terms of my employment. They had all the rights and reasons to fire me, and the only reason they didn’t do it already was because they needed me.

This is why Dick wanted me to do a knowledge transfer. I wasn’t only the single point of failure but also a risk now since they wouldn’t give me the CTO job. I could just walk away, and it might be terrible. There would be nobody left to mitigate any potential problems that might happen. It would take them about a year to develop a new system, but the contract expiration was in a year, meaning they had to keep me and pay me like a king for at least two years. I was indispensable until I raised my head and asked for more.

The company would happily keep paying me for those two years, and when the system went live, they would absorb me into some team as a manager or something, but I was shooting for the stars, and they were displeased. This is where they devised a risk mitigation strategy of pairing me up with two bright programmers. I should have kept my head down, but I dared to stand up and demand something I wanted.

It was just past lunchtime when I went to the canteen, looking to have my usual baked potato with tuna mayonnaise and mushy peas. People shook their heads when they saw me eat that, and I agreed. Those words shouldn’t be used in one sentence, let alone eaten together, but I liked it. A long time ago, I calculated the caloric and nutritional values of this combination, and it fitted my metabolism perfectly. It is not too light and not too filling. It kept me going for the rest of the day.

I joined the long table with all the Indian senior engineers. Over the past two months, we have become good friends. They respected me, and I respected them. I used to work closely with their boss, who was a very competent techie. This helped establish my credentials with the guys, who grew to respect me, if not admire me.

Over time, they told me about their lives, families, kids, and wives. All of them missed them. The company would pay for one trip a year to India for a few weeks, then back. It was just too far and expensive to travel back and forth. All of them lived on the outskirts of London, four to a room or more, saving all the money they made to send home and keep their families well-maintained. They all sacrificed for a better future, and their kids missed them terribly. Not even a single one of them had a plan to stay in Europe.

I found it interesting how everyone loves the consumer society when they need to make money, but nobody plans to stay and make their home here. On the other hand, I was born in London, St Mary’s, like the future kings, and lived my entire life here, apart from a few years in Cambridgeshire, to get my master’s degree.

With nothing to do, I spent the rest of my day on my computer, tethered to my phone, and through VPN, fiddling with a personal project. Nothing was left to do anymore; I just had to wait for the right time to act. Patience was always my strong suit, and I practised it all the time.

When I called Lamin to pick me up, he told me about his talk with his sister and father. They agreed on the terms and a pro-forma marriage performed by some priest in a village, with nothing on paper. For all intents and purposes, we would be married, but without any legal document recognised by any government.

“What about the other thing we talked about?” I asked Lamin, and he confirmed it. If I helped clear his family’s name by marrying the black sheep and I paid him an equal salary, he would sign a five-year contract with me.

Amy waited for me in the lobby as usual, wearing the skimpiest white mini dress imaginable, ending mere inches below her crotch, and I knew she wore no panties. A single gust of wind or a careless move would expose her pussy to anyone who looked her way, especially as she stood tall in her fashionable sparkling white platform shoes.

She squealed and hugged me tight, to the sheer amazement and dismay of my Indian colleagues. At one moment, Amy accidentally dropped her phone and bent down to pick it up. All the guys gasped, having a direct view of her pussy and asshole. She smiled and waved at them, but the guys were too shocked for any kind of sensible response.

Only when we left and sat in the car did my work colleagues start to move, discussing something lively, gesticulating with their hands and shaking their heads.

Amy had a plan. She booked us a table in a fancy French restaurant with a great view of the city, great food, and fine wine. The maître d’ showed us to our table. I ordered some fine scotch as an aperitif and a bottle of wine. It was a romantic candlelit dinner, and Amy went all the way to make it feel special.

“I have a little gift for you,” she said with a naughty smile. When she was sure nobody was looking, she pulled the top of her dress down, exposing her two perfect pink nipples. I almost gasped. Rylee and Callie told Amy how much I liked playing with theirs, and she felt left out a little. So, one day, they went out together and got Amy’s nipples pierced.

“Do you like my pierced nipples, Daddy?” Amy asked with big eyes, making an innocent face. Who would have guessed that an eighteen-year-old shy little teenager would blossom into such a sex kitten? Amy was horny all the time. All she wanted to do was fuck and play sex games. With it, her fantasies grew and refined, turning a former shy girl into a full-blown exhibitionist nymphomaniac looking to get laid all the time.

“I think they are very sexy.” She took my hand into hers and placed something inside it. I took it back to look at it. It was a small white piece of plastic with a few buttons and a transmitter. Amy gave me a remote control for a vibrator she put inside her pussy when I wasn’t looking.

“I am yours, daddy. You can do anything you want with me.” What could a man say to that? The waiter brought us two plates and a fancy brass pot with a cream of mushroom soup inside and served it. I pressed the button on the remote control and set the buzz to max. I had to admit that eating the soup and watching a young woman squirm across the table was a lot of fun.

We made it through the dinner and two courses of desserts. Amy lost her appetite halfway through the food. Her eyes glazed, and she dabbed her forehead with a napkin.

“Are you alright, miss?” the waiter asked at one point, and she forced a smile at him. She was more than alright. Amy was electrified.

“We can’t go home until you finish everything,” I said, making it clear that we would stay there until she ate everything. There was something primally erotic about watching a woman on the edge of orgasm trying to eat fast to get out of the place and finally allow herself to cum.

“I don’t know about you, but I could use a nice walk after dinner,” I said, making a wicked grin.

“Please, Daddy,” she begged, looking at me with those big, blue, innocent eyes.

“Please, what, honey?”

“Daddy, please fuck me.”

“Come on, darling, just a little longer, and I promise, Daddy will fuck your pussy and fill it with sperm.” She hugged my arm, barely able to walk as we strolled through the streets of London at night. After some time, we came across St. Giles, a church with a small park outside. It used to be a meeting spot for junkies until they installed street lamps.

I sat on a wooden bench; that was all Amy could take. She grabbed my crotch, unzipped my pants, fished out my cock, and stuffed it into her mouth, sucking for dear life. As soon as I was hard enough, Amy pulled the vibrator out of her pussy and sat on my cock. She came almost immediately, sinking her teeth into my neck like a vampire and screaming into it.

That wasn’t nearly enough, merely an appetiser. Amy bounced up and down on my cock, moaning like a cheap whore, not caring who could hear it. In fact, it added to the excitement. To be seen copulating in public, the danger and the embarrassment only heightened her arousal, and she came again, but this time screaming loudly into the air.

I’ve been reading many books lately and watched some courses on orgasm control and how to extend my erection for longer. With regular sex, exercise, and the help of chemicals, I kept my testosterone high and my balls producing sperm like a teenager. I could come six times in a day. In fact, Tara trained my libido this way. She wouldn’t go to sleep until I blew at least six loads. She felt six times a day should be standard, with ten or twelve times at the peak. Tara made it her personal project to achieve that.

Many times, I heard various men say it was impossible, that they could ejaculate only once a day. I thought that was bullshit, and I proved it. A healthy reproductive system should function all day, and it is like building muscles or fat. If you train every day or eat too much, you will gain weight. The human body is a beautiful machine. It self-heals and adapts. I jumpstarted mine with methylates and the pro-testosterone pills and followed up with heavy weights, two hours, five times a week.

Did it work? Of course, it did. I was able to ejaculate six times a day at a minimum after a few months of training. Of course, it helped to have a willing sexual partner who took it as a personal failure if I didn’t do my best to try impregnating her every day. It made me realise that on some biological level, when you put all the social programming aside, women love when you desire them, fuck them, and cum inside them.

I was always meticulous, detail-oriented, and borderline compulsive. So when I started all this, I got myself tested. My sperm count was low, and I had a poor volume; my testosterone was at a deficient level, and my sperm motility was shockingly bad. I was only a few steps away from being sterile. My ex-wife and ex-life sterilised me from enjoying my life.

All of it changed after Tara arrived. My cock was constantly erect. My testosterone was through the roof, and I could ejaculate large amounts. For the last six months, if I ejaculated deep inside a woman’s pussy, it would leak out when I pulled out, even without her standing. Tara told me she always received a mouthful and had to swallow a few times. I was probably blasting out half a centilitre of sperm or more. Recently, I got my sperm checked, and the count was extremely high, with the motility at almost one hundred per cent. If I came into a river merging into a lake, all women bathing there would get pregnant, so much for the widespread belief that sperm dies in your forties. It was all nonsense. Use it or lose it, I said.

Amy started to move faster, hearing my rapidly increasing breath. I pinched her nipples, and she almost screamed. Then I pulled on her hips and thrust my cock deep inside. She came again purely from feeling my hot sperm erupt against her cervix, as well as the powerful throbbing sensation of a cock ejaculating with high pressure.

She finally stood up, and the sperm just ran out, landing on the ground. Her pussy, thighs, and legs were covered in cum. She giggled and kissed me on my cheek, saying, “Thank you, Daddy.”

I took Amy’s arm, and we found my car. She unzipped my trousers again and lazily sucked my cock all the way home, receiving another mouthful just as we arrived. She thanked me for a snack and returned to her apartment, leaving me at mine with Tara, who couldn’t wait. I came two times that day. Four more, and I would be allowed to sleep. Life is often a struggle, pain, and suffering, but as men, we keep a stiff upper lip and soldier through it without complaining and crying about it.

For almost a week, life went on the same way. I would go to work, sit and wait, then go home and spend time with my girls. The Americans wanted to go out, see everything, do everything, especially take me to musicals and watch plays. Tara and Amy joined us sometimes, and I finally discovered something Tara loved. Since she came to London, I tried to get Tara involved in something other than sex.

I had limited success getting Tara interested in a gym, but everything else was a bust. All of it changed when Tara saw her first ballet. She was enchanted, mesmerised. Tara stared at it with wide-open eyes, popping in amazement with her mouth gaping. I couldn’t understand why, but I didn’t care. I was happy she found something she resonated with deeply. It gave me hope that someday, she’d get another interest.

We were sitting in Amy’s living room one evening when a knock on the door came. It was Cassie. I couldn’t believe it. She greeted the girls and made a friendly chitchat for a few minutes before taking my hand and pulling me to my apartment.

There she was in front of me, looking at me like a hungry cat, licking her lips and pulling my necktie. She unbuttoned my shirt and pushed me onto the bed. No questions were necessary; I was too dumbstruck to ask any. I watched as the gorgeous evening dress slipped off her shoulders, leaving Cassie completely naked.

She knelt on the bed and walked on her knees, resembling a lioness. I was the mouse; I was the prey. Before I could even whimper, her lips were on mine, and our tongues wrestled. My hands had a mind of their own and found their way towards Cassie’s magnificent mammaries with extended long nipples.

Suddenly, I felt dry in my throat as my mouth watered. All I wanted to do was nurse on Cassie’s two perfect pink cones, but she gave me no chance. She slid down my body and stuffed my cock all the way into her throat, bobbing up and down, making my toes curl, and my thighs tremble.

All I could think of at that moment was bursting a big load down Cassie’s gullet, then flipping her around and riding her ass until my cock bent and broke. I was too shocked and excited to assert any sort of self-control over my natural responses. It took Cassie less than five minutes before my cock erupted like a burst water pipe, feeding her with a copious amount of fresh, hot nut butter. Cassie ate it all and swallowed, sucking my cock for a while after to savour the very last drop of the sperm I made for her.

My cock remained hard like a steel rod, ready for action. Angels don’t fall from the sky like this every day, and I was counting my blessings and saying my prayers. Cassie came up with a smile, and I rolled her on her back, knowing exactly what I had to do. I slid down, and the first time, it was a fluke that caught me by surprise, but not this time. I had enough opportunity to learn and practice, should the gods of the universe give me another chance.

Cassie moaned, arching her back and bending her hips to give me better access as my tongue started lapping her up. It took only a minute for her to cum. Cassie must have been horny as hell to come so easily and quickly. It would explain why she came to me. We already had sex a few times, and maybe she saw me as safe. There could be no doubt in anyone’s mind I was crazy for her, head to toe.

This was my chance to prove myself again, and I did that, eating Cassie’s pussy like mad. One, two, three orgasms and counting. She let me do my thing, holding her hands locked while I feasted on her clit, and she moaned. The poor girl was on fire, horny as hell. Her pussy was running with juices, and I lapped them all up. Screw the French restaurants or fine wines. I could eat that pussy for the rest of my life. I barely even noticed the numbness in my tongue.

Some thirty minutes in, but who’s checking time, I saw the telltale sign of an approaching monster. I pinned her down and doubled my efforts, and just a few minutes later, Cassie exploded with a scream. Her pussy convulsed so much that she almost prolapsed; her muscles squeezed like a vice and relaxed as she screamed.

This was the best show on the planet, and I had the front-row seats for the performance, watching Cassie cum, squeal, and tremble, fighting for her breath. I couldn’t guess why she visited me. I was hoping for this. Inside my head, I liked to imagine that my pussy eating technique was better than others, and she came for me. If only that were the case, I could guarantee she always returned and never left.

My cock was throbbing like mad as Cassie calmed down, so I mounted her and pumped, kneading her perfect fat tits with my hands. She looked into my eyes as I did that and smiled. She was messing with my head, as I could see love in her eyes. There was no way it was real, but I wanted it to be more than anything. Then we kissed.

I made love to Cassie slowly and urgently. She moaned and grunted as I stabbed her with my dick. In and out, I pumped, jackhammering my cock inside, squeezing her tits so hard that it must have hurt, but Cassie only rolled her eyes and gyrated her hips for more.

She came sometime later, then again, joining my scream or release with a hissing noise. My balls pulled back, and my cock pulsed as my sperm gushed out, painting her insides. I was breeding her in my mind. Oh god, how I wished that were true. It just turned me on more to imagine I was claiming this woman to be mine.

Cassie clearly had no objections about me having other women. In fact, she and the girls grew to be friends over time. Deep inside, I hoped the girls could convince her to join us, but nothing ever worked on Cassie. She was a woman with her own mind, plans, and priorities. No matter how hard I tried or whatever gambit I threw her way. Cassie would choose what to do, when, and how, and then reset the next day.

We lay like this, kissing and fondling, knowing we were nowhere close to the end. I fully intended to fuck Cassie through the night until she passed out, and I collapsed. If I died having sex with her, it would be the best death I could imagine.

Cassie felt my cock stir and grow big in her hands, and she bit my lip, smiled, then licked my face. I pushed her on her stomach, grabbed her hips in my hands and pulled her back. Her perfect pussy smiled at me, recently fucked, but not nearly enough.

I had a simple plan: destroy Cassie with sex tonight. I grabbed a fistful of her luscious hair, showed my cock into her and pulled, making her back arch and her lungs release air; then I rode her like a Comanche, rough, fast, and bareback.

The world became a blur as the night echoed with screams, moans and slaps. I fucked Cassie so hard that I was convinced she’ll get bruises on her ass. All of it turned into a jumbled mess inside my head, fucking, kissing, feeding her with my sperm, gnashing her tits, pulling her hair. Somewhere along the line, I even licked and fucked her asshole. All of it turned into haze. If someone arrested me and insisted to explain what happened, I wouldn’t know what to say.

When I opened my eyes, the sun was up, staring at me through the window, making me feel like a vampire. I looked around, and Cassie was gone. I would have thought I ingested some DMT and hallucinated everything, meeting the giants who made me imagine Cassie if it wasn’t for the bed. It was ruined, covered in sweat, piss, drool, cum and pussy juices. There was even some blood when Cassie bit my hand in orgasm, as I was hatefucking her hard.

I rolled on my back and smiled, thinking how blessed my life was. Cassie came to me on a whim, which must have meant something, no matter how little she wanted to show me. Despite her reset, some small feeling or thought about me remained. It was hope inside a box Pandora left for me. The day was shaping up like a dream.

I thought it was strange that Cassie came over like that. She usually avoided me or kept our interactions distant and friendly. Everything suddenly changed without any explanation.

Since that day, Cassie would visit me about twice a week. She would hang out with the girls, have friendly chitchat, and even join them in a round of table games like monopoly. I would sit on the sofa, watching a group of gorgeous women lying with their tummies on the plush carpet, talking and giggling, and rolling a dice.

After some time, or after a game, Cassie would come over to me and drag me into my apartment, and we would have harder and rougher sex each time. Like all the other girls I’ve been with, she preferred hard, rough sex over lovemaking. For some reason, Cassie loved to be spanked. It turned her on immensely. Often, I would put her across my knees and make her ass red before throwing her on all fours and fucking her doggie style. I would thrust my cock forcefully, grab her hips, watch her breasts sway in the mirror, and listen to her scream.

It was strange, but I didn’t complain. Somehow, Cassie had convinced herself that we were lovers. She was polite, friendly, and fun, but she would come over to have sex, take a shower, and then leave. She had convinced herself that I was a friend she could trust and use as a live body to have sex with whenever she felt horny, and I wouldn’t complain.

There was something fundamentally wrong with Cassie and many other women as well. I really needed to figure it out. If for nothing else, then for my own sanity and peace of mind. I needed to learn the hooker game.

Chapter 35 - African drums

The sound of the drums added to the festive atmosphere. It was an essential part of the traditional Gambian wedding experience. An entire village was invited to witness the Mawlānā perform the ceremony. Neneh accepted; I accepted. And we were married.

Suddenly, in the eyes of everyone gathered, Neneh Jallow wasn’t that lesbian girl anymore, but my wife. Her duty was to represent me, and her honour was my honour. To disrespect her or her family would mean they were disrespecting me, a man who travelled across the continents to take a woman as my wife. It was the last thing the traditional people would dare to do.

The Muslim priest performing the ceremony was also the chief of the village. I had met him before and gifted a flock of goats to sacrifice and bless the marriage with enough leftovers to feed the entire village. The man had an honest look in his eyes and thanked me with all his heart. Without anyone knowing, I spent a few thousand more and hired people to build an extension to a local school as a gift to the village.

The butcher prepared the meat early in the morning according to Muslim traditions, and the priest said the prayer. The goats were grilled on an open fire, and most of the village witnessed the pride of Neneh’s parents. All was forgiven, and all was forgotten. They were elevated. Her parents felt like kings for the day.

All I had to do was look into Neneh’s eyes to see how much it meant to her. I couldn’t even see her brother’s face. Lamin covered it with his hands and cried. What I did saved his family from more than poverty. It gave them their face back. I could tell Neneh’s heart was churning from the pain she caused everyone.

“Thank you, husband,” she said, holding my hand tight, never letting it go. I’ve never seen such fervour in someone’s eyes. All the girls that chose to be with me decided to be mine, but not like Neneh. There was no second thought there, plan, or agenda. For all intents and purposes, that woman was mine. Somehow, I had a feeling if I ordered her to jump into a fire, she would do it and thank me for the opportunity. That was some hardcore upbringing and training from the beginning.

I finally understood everything. Like many Westerners, I grew up with prejudice against Muslim people. The blue-haired feminists were talking bullshit. I was willing to bet none of them ever lived amongst Muslims, either. What I saw in Neneh was a dedication so strong that it would be impossible for a man to not respect her or ever abandon her. When someone looks at you like that, you are bound to that person, love or not. The strength, the commitment, the purity, and on top of it all, Neneh was gorgeous and also a virgin. What did any Western people, including myself, know about that? It was admirable and worthy of respect.

The party went on till dawn. Somewhere along the line, I was too tired and took my new wife to the house. We stripped naked and washed before lying on the bed, too exhausted to even think, but sleep wouldn’t come instantly.

As I lay on my back, Neneh wrapped herself around my side and explored my body with her fingers. Seeing that I wasn’t protesting, she took my cock into her hand and weighed it, looked at it, examined it. She had never seen a penis before and was intrigued. Somewhere along the line, my eyes closed, and I drifted asleep.

The following day started with your typical village life and the sound of birds making a ruckus. Neneh was already up and packing when I opened my eyes. Immediately, she came to the bed and hugged me.

“Good morning, husband,“ she chirped, and we kissed. It was a good thing we liked each other. I remembered the moment we first met. All her pictures and videos didn’t do her justice. Neneh was one of those people who looked great in photographs and absolutely stunning in real life. She was tall with long legs and arms, long thin fingers, and an almost surreal narrow waist.

Neneh had a long neck, a pretty face with perfect symmetry, an ideal nose, big eyes, and kissable lips. She had a nice bubble butt, and her breasts were a bit on the larger side, with big nipples, all of them perky. What else could anyone expect from a girl in her prime at eighteen? As much as we could appreciate a young Naomi Campbell at her best, she couldn’t even compare to Neneh’s looks. No wonder all the single men wanted to marry her, and only the stigma of her past kept her chaste. She was a rare find.

I came out of the washroom to see Neneh putting on a plaster. She had cut herself and smeared her blood all over the white bedsheets. She looked at me and smiled. I waved her over and embraced her waist, and she melted into my arms, offering her lips for a kiss.

Soon after, a car arrived. We hugged and said our goodbyes. It drove us to the docks, and we boarded a boat. It was easier this way than driving, taking us only about thirty minutes on the Gambia River from Darussalam to Banjul, the capital, where another car met us and took us to the airport.

Lamin went with us all the way, ensuring we left the country okay. I watched a profoundly emotional moment when the brother and sister hugged and said goodbye to each other. He then shook my hand and embraced me. We were a family now, joined by his sister’s marriage.

It was an expensive and arduous flight with multiple stops. The first one was in Freetown, Sierra Leone, where we caught the connecting one to Accra in Ghana. From there, we flew to Addis Ababa in Ethiopia, where we caught our final connection to Dubai, our destination, just over sixteen hours end to end. It made me understand why Lamin visited his family so rarely. The Gambia seemed like it was at the edge of the planet.

I had never visited Dubai before, so when the taxi picked us up, I was almost as excited as Neneh. Her eyes were everywhere. She had never flown on a plane before and loved the experience. Everything was new to her, the people, the big cities. Her eyes were as big as saucers.

In Dubai, it didn’t matter where you came from, your religion, skin colour, or culture. All was there, right on Neneh’s face. She was just a young girl looking forward to her life. Everything else was a facade, a mask atop a mask of all the garbage, but deep inside, we were all the same. We feel, we love, we cry, we die. We live this life to the best of our abilities.

This was proof that I made the right call to book a room at Burj Al Arab, the iconic hotel that looked like a sail, which was seen on almost every Instagram of whoever visited Dubai. The only difference is that you never see the pictures from the inside. The starting price of a thousand dollars per day was pretty steep for most people, but I wanted the room for my own purposes.

“Oh, god! This is so wonderful, husband,” Neneh said with her melodious African accent. She wore an exquisite black and white boubou in a sort of smeared checkerboard pattern, looking like it was photographed at high speed. On her head, she wore some kind of marching white scarf with a black sewn-in design, making her look like an African princess who came to inspect the world at her knees. Neneh seemed beautiful and proud, going through the rooms and examining everything.

“I thought our first time should be special,” I said, and Neneh ran into my arms, hugging me tight and kissing me all over. Sometimes, people see those of different cultures as being different. People are the same everywhere. Neneh acted from her heart like anyone would. She didn’t want to marry that other guy, and destiny intervened in the form of her brother talking with me. We spoke through video calls before we met, and we liked each other, and now we were husband and wife, just without papers.

I would never make the same mistake as with Tina, my ex-wife. Neneh knew that; she knew I had other girls, and none mattered. When she kissed that girl, people thought she was a lesbian, but none of that was true. Neneh grew up with a powerful sex drive and just wanted to experiment and fulfil some of her fantasies.

Neneh and I got pretty close since her brother introduced us, and she confided in me, sharing her sexual proclivities as well as her fantasies. Sometimes, I laughed, telling her she would fit right in with the rest of my women. She almost burst into tears from laughter when I told her some stories of Amy’s escapades. It just turned her on further. All Neneh wanted was to get rid of her virginity and get laid.

“Are you hungry?” I asked, and she smiled.

“I am starving.”

“Let’s take a shower and have a nice meal.” We got into the bathroom together and disrobed. Neneh’s eyes were focused on my cock.

“It is beautiful,” she said, and I almost laughed.

“Would you like to suck it?”

“Yes! Oh, yes, but I don’t know how.” Neneh was raised in a small religious place without a mobile phone or any access to the internet. Most women in the village had their clitoris removed when they were little, so they couldn’t get sexually aroused like her or even masturbate. They couldn’t feel any sexual pleasure.

Neneh’s father was a good man who loved his daughter, and he would never allow something like that to happen to her. It cost him years of misery and pain, and people pointed out it was all his fault. If he let his daughter go through vaginal circumcision, she would have never kissed the other girl, and she wouldn’t have destroyed their reputation. It was a misery for everyone involved, most of all for his oversexed daughter.

We soaped and washed each other and massaged our bodies. I could see Neneh’s eyes glaze. She was horny as hell. It was good, and I liked it this way. The hornier she got, the more memorable her first time would be, so we dressed up, and I led her downstairs.

Adjoining the hotel was the Souk Madinat Jumeirah, a traditional Arabic-style open-air shopping mall with tens of dozens of little stores selling anything imaginable, from candy to carpets. We walked around the place, admiring everything. Neneh’s eyes were restless. Her mind tried to absorb it all, suck it all in.

We came across a women’s fashion store selling all kinds of traditional wear. The saleswoman smiled, seeing a boubou Neneh wore. It looked incredible.

“Do you have something that would fit her?“ I asked, and the woman rushed to the back. She returned with an exquisitely made abaya, the simple black robe Muslim women use to cover themselves, except this one was done with the utmost care and love and stitched with golden thread in an intricate pattern. With it, she brought a black hijab and a scarf to cover one’s hair and neck. It was made with gold print or something similar, featuring a traditional Arabic design.

I sent Neneh to change, and when she got out, she looked like an angel—so gorgeous and pure. I couldn’t stop staring at her. The saleswoman seemed to share the same view. She didn’t say anything, but the look in her eyes was sufficient.

The woman went into the back and brought more black and gold designs. Never before did I appreciate the beauty of simple robes like that. They were exquisite, like plain wrapping for a Christmas present with a gold bow tie, and they fit Neneh perfectly. She was made to wear robes like that.

At first, I thought Neneh’s African boubou looked fashionable, so colourful, so in-your-face, and I thought she looked gorgeous. Not anymore. Who could have guessed you could make something more beautiful by taking things away? It was subtle and magical.

“I’ll take them all. Can you please deliver this to Burj Al Arab,“ and I gave a room number. It wasn’t cheap. I was surprised at how expensive the simple clothes could get. Neneh wore one and left her boubou to be delivered with the rest.

Immediately as we walked out, I noticed everyone looking at us, or rather at Neneh, who walked like a princess. Suddenly, everyone showed more interest. The subtlety changed everything, and she walked a step behind me like a traditional wife. I smiled at her, and she smiled at me.

As soon as we found a restaurant to eat at, the waiter almost bowed. He gave us their best table, while another brought a foldable wooden partition so my wife could take off her hijab and nobody would be able to watch her eat.

The entire city looked exquisite. I had heard so much about Dubai, but I never expected this level of indulgence. Perhaps it just struck a chord—the weather, the smell, the opulence. The entire Madinat Jumeirah was built like Venice on an artificial set of canals. No expenses were spared in creating this oasis of opulence.

I climbed on top of Neneh, and our bodies touched. She gasped before our lips met, and my hands roamed her smooth, warm skin, squeezing her breasts and rubbing her nipples. I could see that Neneh was clearly on cloud nine, pushing her head backwards and closing her eyes.

She gave me access to her long, beautiful neck, and I sunk my teeth into it like a beast, ready to devour it. Life is like a box of chocolates, as the famous line from the movie says. I was taking my time with the perfect chocolate morsel of mine, kissing her lower, tracing some symbols with my tongue. It was the ancient language of love from the beginning of time.

When my lips went down, Neneh’s entire body trembled and shivered. One gentle touch of my tongue was all it took to bring her over the threshold, and she screamed. Neneh’s trembling legs squeezed, trapping my head with her thighs. She hissed and squealed as a powerful orgasm took her, and she gyrated her hips, asking for more.

What’s a man to do? I feasted on her pussy, tasting her musky delight, rubbing her throbbing clit up and down with my tongue, savouring the way she tasted. Neneh’s screams came in relentless waves, high pizzicato crowning the longer melodies. The urgency and sheer potency of the moment surprised me and forced me onwards.

“Please, oh please, fuck me,“ Neneh’s words broke through the moans. No matter how often she came, she wasn’t sated, wishing for something she had dreamt of for ages. What’s a man to do but the husband’s duties? A measure of a man is his stoic endurance as he suffers silently through adversities. It was time for me to be that man.

I moved up until my body towered above her, suspended by my arm. Our eyes met, and she sighed, feeling the bulbous head of my cock part her innermost folds. I rocked my body in and out, knocking ever so lightly against her front door.

Neneh’s eyes softened as her gaze locked on to mine. She bit her lip and nodded slightly in a slight sight of encouragement. That’s all it took to give me a start. In one decisive move, I extended my body, sticking my cock all the way inside, ripping her maidenhead like it was made of wet paper, lodging the head of my cock against her cervix and waiting.

She squealed and quivered, stuck her nails in my back and pulled as her thighs trembled and her toes curled. Neneh’s eyes rolled back, leaving her neck open to the attack, and I bit into it again, adding a gurgle to the scream escaping her lips as she buckled.

One stroke, one orgasm. Neneh was so prepped and so aroused, dreaming about it since puberty, expecting it all her life, the moment she stopped being a girl to become a woman who had sex with her husband. In one fell stroke, I ended her childhood, ripping her virginity asunder. I consumed this marriage like the traditions planned, claiming Neneh for the rest of our lives.

It would be a great time to stop and reflect on life if I wasn’t interrupted by Neneh’s increased moves. She froze a little at first, ridding her orgasm, but as soon as it ebbed away, she started begging for more. Her body took control of her mind, pushing it aside, asking and begging for more, feeling a new kind of fullness for the first time.

I slowly pulled back and pushed in, just to be rewarded by a moan and a sigh. In and out, I moved, picking up speed, before I was punching my cock into her with high speed like a jackhammer, a roaring engine pistoning at high revs. Gone were the moments of one-sided pleasure. After Neneh’s first orgasm, I chased mine.

With brutal abandon, without mercy or regret, I stabbed my cock into Neneh’s pussy like a rabbit on coke. There was just something nasty, primal, primordial, turning my brain into a mindless troglodyte. All I could think off is taking my pleasure, ripping her pussy apart with merciless smacking of my cock. High-speed deep strokes it was precisely what the doctor ordered. I took it out on Neneh and her insatiable pink folds.

I felt her cum, then cum once more, but I didn’t stop or even watch. The thunder came all the way from my toes, climbing up my legs into my balls and further until I screamed aloud, squeezing her breasts in my hands. My cock twitched, shooting out the sperm bullets. It was a nine-shooter, nine thick wads of sperm spraying her insides, right against her cervix, pushing my cum directly into her womb.

Neneh joined in with my screams, adding her own wails and pants. My cock was still hard and erect, and we weren’t done yet. I let my orgasm ride, and her pussy slid until my vision cleared and I could breathe again; then I pumped. I fucked her hard without any plans to stop. It would be a long night where I would set the bar high, turning my wife into an insatiable nymphomaniac. That’s what I liked.

Chapter 36 - Strange encounter

I opened my eyes, feeling fantastic. The sunshine broke through the windows into the room. I could live this way, I thought. Then my eyes fell and focused on my wife’s smiling face. She was kneeling between my legs, naked, smiling, watching my morning erection grow.

Instantly, without a word, she slipped down and put my cock into her mouth and sucked. It felt so light and gentle that she obviously didn’t know how to do that. Neneh was worried about hurting me with her teeth, so she applied only the lightest pressure. Her mouth felt like hot feathers.

I would have stopped her and taught her how to do it better, but combined with my arousal and her innocence, she was already doing quite well. So I smiled at her, and our eyes met. Neneh could sense I was enjoying myself, so she increased her efforts and had me at the edge. One, two, three, and here we go again. My cock twitched inside her mouth, erupting hot sperm like a geyser.

She knew what to do with it now, so she sucked and swallowed it all until my cock started to go soft. Then, she resumed her initial efforts until the last drop.

“Mmm, this is how to wake up,” I commented. Neneh smiled at me, acting like I gave her a trophy or something.

“I will do it for you every day, husband.” I could tell she meant that; I wanted to tell her how it was unnecessary. Then I changed my mind and told her that I would love it. Both were factual statements, but the one I chose was better. It was going to be a good day.

Neneh washed me, and I washed her in return. On the way out of the shower, I noticed blood on the white linen. It took me a second to realise where it came from, almost forgetting that last night, Neneh was still a virgin.

It was going to be a busy day. Neneh put on another abaya and a different hijab. She saw how much I liked it and how people looked at her wearing it, so she decided it would be how she dressed to honour our marriage. I led her downstairs, and we had an excellent breakfast. Neneh had lived all her life in a small place on the outskirts of Darussalam, and she could never even imagine splendour like that. Even for someone like me who grew accustomed to five-star hotels, the breakfast at Burj Al Arab was much better.

The car arrived and was waiting for us. The driver, Iqbal, was a Syrian immigrant from Aleppo. He moved to Dubai when NATO and friends decided to liberate them from the oppressive government by bringing democracy like they did in Iraq, Afghanistan, Libya, Vietnam, and so many other places.

Iqbal was a middle-aged man who was well-spoken and well-presented, looking healthy and vital. He spoke excellent English as well as his native Arabic, which I thought might come in handy. Iqbal knew Dubai like the back of his hand. Iqbal liked to talk and act as a tourist guide with a little smile. He was a likeable character.

The first order of business was to meet with a friend of a friend. An Arab guy I knew from The Chamber had one of his acquaintances, a Dubai local, willing to rent out his villa quite affordably with a view to selling it. Because of its price, the place remained unsold for a very long time. It was one of the landmark developments, right at the end, at the tip of one of the palm leaves, touching the sand, going for an asking price of messily twenty-seven million dollars and change.

The diver took us to the Palm Jumeirah, less than ten minutes’ drive from where we stayed. I knew nothing about Dubai, but I already loved this place, and living close to Burj Al Arab, Madinat Jumeirah, and Jumeirah Beach seemed to me to be a distinct benefit.

“This is an artificial island built for rich people,” Iqbal started, telling us about the genesis of the place. Apparently, the Palm Jumeirah was one of the most exclusive developments in Dubai, not because of glitz and glamour but because of quiet, exclusive living. The place was centrally located, a stone’s throw away from the Mall of Emirates, good restaurants, the beach, and entertainment, as if the new Dubai grew around it. The city planners designed it to be perfect.

Ahmad waited for us at the building, wearing a white kandurah, the UAE national robe. He stood next to his screaming red Lykan HyerSport by W Motors, a company he was invested in. Ahmad smiled and shook my hand, barely acknowledging the driver or Neneh. He fiddled with the keys and the security code at the gate before taking us inside.

To call it a villa would be inaccurate. It was a modern three-story rectangular building made with glass, concrete, and marble, white outside and white inside, clearly basking in brightness and sunshine as its most prominent feature. The place had clean, straight, modern lines, polished white stone floor tiles, white marble, and white leather furniture with gold and silver accents. Someone with impeccable taste knew exactly how far to push it before the place looked sterile.

They used flowers, bushes, and palm trees outside to bring the environment in rather than clutter the house with all sorts of nonsense. The place was airy, fresh, and breathable. It made me feel like I was on a beach instead of inside.

Outside, a long pool some fifteen feet wide encircled the building like some modern-age mote, seamlessly blending with the white sand outside that ended in azure blue waters. I was pretty sure if I had a rock, I could throw it that far as the sea was no more than thirty yards away.

“You can have the house for a month. Enjoy yourself. Do let me know if you decide to buy it.” Ahmad said after finishing his tour. We shook hands, and he left. I watched him open the engine and listened to the Lykan roar away.

“What a car.”

“Did you say something?”

“I was just jealous of the car.” Neneh giggled and went inside to rummage through the house. I went on the patio right by the sand, sat on a comfortable, soft outdoor sofa and put my legs up, watching Dubai in the distance across what seemed like a mile of water. “I could get used to this,” I said to no one, then chuckled and stretched my arms. Yep, I loved this place. It had all that I liked about California and none of the things I disliked.

I did a lot of research about Dubai, including the economy, taxation, and legal system. It was a safe haven for people with a crazy amount of money or those starting offshore businesses. Neneh found me about ten minutes later and brought me a glass of cold water.

“There is nothing else in the house.” I drank it and pulled her hand. She lost her balance and landed in my arms, giggling like a child.

“How do you like this place?”

“Oh, I love it. It’s fit for a king.” It was, indeed, when I thought about it. I didn’t even bother counting the bedrooms. I thought about a dozen, somewhere in that ballpark, three stories of luxury living right at the tip of an elongated artificial island with incredible and breathtaking views.

“Come on, let’s get some stuff.” I pulled Neneh’s hand, and we went back into the car. I instructed Iqbal to take us to the Mall of Emirates. It was a gorgeous luxury place with everything a mind could imagine. First things first, I found an electronics store and bought Neneh a brand-new iPhone. She knew how to use a mobile phone but never had one. Her father was so strict he didn’t allow her access to the internet. I set her up over a cup of coffee with a Dubai number, and Instagram wired it all up and explained what’s what.

I pulled back later as we got into Carrefour downstairs. I pushed the trolley, but Neneh chose everything—food, primarily fruits, cleaning liquids, and so on. I noticed no toilet paper. They used water instead. Each toilet had a little douche used for that purpose. They were much more hygienic to use than paper. Little things like that made me feel uncivilised. It was as if the West jumped straight to a digital age before figuring out how to clean our own asses.

We cared for technology, style, and wealth but little about the culture. A museum here and there to feed the curious, but even here in this modern place, I could see endless cultural references. Arabs were proud of their heritage, while we in the West did our best to erase it and replace even the simplest concepts like mother and father with some other nonsense. The rest of the world was building monuments, and we were tearing them down. Sometimes, I wondered if it was because we were ashamed of ourselves. Certainly, we had plenty to be ashamed of, least of all the endless conflicts.

Just in my lifetime, we managed to murder and displace millions of people in the name of freedom and democracy and even celebrated instead of jailing the murderous, warmonger pigs in high seats that flat-out lied to their people. No wonder some world politicians referred to the West as the empire of lies.

While we were busy debating how many penises a woman should have, the world was busy developing its arts, culture, and science, leaving the barbarians behind them. No wonder the rich were fleeing the sinking ship called “the West.”

About three million people live in Dubai, with only ten per cent being Emiratis. However, all the Western press had to say about them was how poorly they treated their labourers. They failed to point out that those labourers signed up for this hard work, fleeing the much worse situation at home, sometimes caused by our bombs. Like Iqbal, the taxi driver who used to have his own business in Aleppo. Unfortunately, we brought him freedom and democracy, so he and his family were left with nothing.

Perhaps I was a little starstruck with the place, the climate, the opulence, all the exotic things bombarding my senses, or I was a bit jaded with the West. I had plenty of opportunity to see pain and misery back home. The grass always seems greener elsewhere, or the sand softer in Dubai’s case. Still, one thing was undeniable—the Emiratis did well for their people. They supported and enriched them, making their lives better. Isn’t that the whole point of government?

Back home, we never referred to the government as “us.” They were always “them,” the members of the permanent class of the ruling elite, an impenetrable group of people so detached from everyone else that they might as well have been from another planet. No wonder the commoners referred to some as pigfuckers.

I couldn’t help but notice the glaring differences between the places. They were so obvious and in-your-face, like little needles stabbing my eyes. No amount of positive thinking or creative justification, explanation, or outright bullshit was able to cover that and convince me that the West was the first world and the rest was not.

While we busied ourselves with utter nonsense, the world has moved on and left us behind. Looking at Dubai, one can’t help but realise that the wealth has long since left Western shores, apart from a few tiny pockets like Monaco. But the West was done. Just try walking at night through the streets of the Bronx or moving into the capital of knife crime. Seen from the Mall of Emirates with snow and an artificial ski slope in the middle of the desert, you get the message loud and clear. They were laughing at us.

Rats were fleeing the ship, New York, the City of London, and setting up their shops elsewhere. Nobody ever moved to Brussels to start their empire. The seat of the European Union was often lauded by the press as a shining beacon of integration, a blueprint for all nations of Europe to join hands and work together. No wonder the UK left. Has anyone ever been to Brussels? Political turmoil, strife, rampant prostitution and crime, uncontrollable immigration and homelessness, apathy and helplessness. But hey, look, here’s some chocolate. It will all be okay as long as you don’t look that way.

The only thing propping the West’s hegemony was its military posturing, but even that was just smoke and mirrors with politicians huffing and puffing, drumming their chests like gorillas and screaming NATO. We saw it in action in Afghanistan when they ran like a bunch of pussies, and people fell from the planes. Those we betrayed and left to die. After twenty years of posturing, what message did we send? The mighty alliance lost the war to a bunch of illiterate villagers. They threw billions into Ukraine. Half a million dead Ukrainian soldiers later and two million wounded, what did we have to show for it? Nobody took us seriously anymore, even Africa, who showed us the finger.

This is what happens when, for decades, you act like a bully and build an image of an oppressor. New generations of people are born and grow up with hate for us, and of course, they just wait for the right moment. Looking at all of this in the Emirates, it was like someone switched on the light. We weren’t just sliding; we were done.

The West was finished. Even the Saudis joined BRICS, putting their oil on the table and pricing it in Yuan instead of the dollar. India, the recently most populous nation in the world, was coming out of poverty into a modest middle-class living, and what have we done in the West? Decided that it is hate when lesbians refuse to have sex with women that have penises and call them TERFs to shame them, take a beloved child stories writer and send her death threats because she dared to say there is such a thing as a biological woman? Western contribution to the world at large was self-evident. No wonder nobody wanted to have anything to do with that.

All of it hit me at once. I read and followed, but actually, being in the Emirates and seeing the world with my own two eyes, all of it sank in and connected. I was raised to believe that we were the best. Our colonial past, the rule of law, democracy, and all that I learned was great about my country proved to be, at best, outdated and, at worst, a steaming pile of manure. Just try getting into an NHS surgery. It looks like a MASH unit with field medics, so could you even get an appointment?

After my divorce, when I moved, I had to register with a different surgery closer to my new place. It took me four weeks to get an appointment with an administrative nurse to register, and then four weeks later, I got the NHS letter. When I had the flu and was feeling unwell, they told me the earliest I could see a doctor was in four weeks.

“What if it is something serious?”

“Call the emergency and go to the hospital.” Does this sound like a functioning medical service or one that’s turned to shit and just waited for someone to notice?

We knew the game. Our beloved politicians were purposely ruining it so they could make a case for privatising it and selling it to the highest bidder, pocketing cash in legal bribes through their offshore Cayman Island businesses. Someone should update the Oxford dictionary to say that the word government expanded to a synonym for a crime syndicate. Whether it was getting your dick sucked in the Oval Office or having COVID parties at Number Ten while arresting people for trying to see their dying parents. It was a fucking embarrassment.

Of course, I was angry and bitter. I resented what the parasites did to my country. Decades of political misadventures, incompetence, or deliberate mismanagement have turned the place I once loved, even revered, into something I was ashamed of. Still, I loved London, my home, my country, and I was upset and torn when I saw how it slid into practical poverty. While some nations join hands and pull together for everyone’s benefit, the only thing we learned to do was become more divisive and signal virtue to each other, making us even more isolated.

I heard people say, “It will get better,” over and again, but I never saw that better future materialise. Perhaps it was my fault to passively sit and wait for someone to make it for me, for all of us, while others took the matter into their own hands. If you’re not moving forward, you are sliding backwards.

Truer words were never spoken, and they came from the mouth of my friend, Jack. I never thought they would apply to a broader context, and we as a nation lifted our hands into the air. We surrendered to the apathy and stopped even voting. One just had to look at the general election turnout to understand how little people cared. Each year, fewer people voted. It was a vote of no confidence by the populace, confirming that whoever we voted for didn’t matter because they were all the same.

What was the point anyway? They’ll count the votes, congratulate themselves, and continue with their mandate like nothing ever happened. The only difference is that they would have another excuse for their own incompetence. “We inherited a mess. It takes time to fix it.” It was a popular song they sang, an evergreen. We all know the words by heart, but I was tired of listening to them.

One might wonder why did it matter? How did it personally relate to me? It was the system created through apathy focused on affirmative action and equity that marginalised men for the sake of some misguided ideology. Tina was allowed to take my children, turn my boys into women, and be applauded for being a responsible parent. I was deemed to be an abusive husband without a single proof. They didn’t even bother investigating it; they just took her word for it. We made this system through our inaction, and I carried a part of that guilt.

Intersectionality became the word of the day, creating a hierarchy of perceived oppression. The more oppressed, the better. There is just so much a person can take before blowing a gasket and walking away. I reached that point when my kids were taken, and despite all my pleas for help, nobody cared, nobody listened to my prayers, and nobody wondered if I was okay. No wonder so many men felt betrayed and marginalised. I didn’t want to raise my boys in the world like that and explain to them why they had to become girls without someone even trying to talk to them or ask them how they really felt.

Neneh was done shopping, and I pushed the trolley out, paid for everything, and asked them to deliver it. As I was about to pay, the cashier asked me if I wanted to have my shopping delivered. It was a brilliant concept, and I readily agreed. Neneh and I walked around for a bit, and I kept noticing the people staring at her. She was tall, and it was how she walked with so much grace, wearing the most beautiful hijab I saw anywhere. We stopped at a restaurant and had a nice lunch before it was time for me to continue with my day.

Iqbal dropped Neneh home just in time to receive the deliveries. I waited until the truck left, and then Iqbal drove me to a new free trade zone named Dubai Silicon Oasis. I did all my research and found the right contacts who introduced me to some people to help turn my business plan into reality.

The man in a white kandurah introduced himself as Omar. We spoke over the phone before to discuss some preliminaries.

“It is good to put a face to a name,” Omar said, and we shook hands. His English was perfect, and it was easy to tell he was Western-educated. He handed me some brochures about the free zone and went into a spiel, telling me all the benefits and positive sides of starting a business at the Silicon Oasis. “It is a perfect fit, Jim.”

Free zones were inspired concepts. You could open a company that would work exclusively within free zone limits and have a hundred per cent foreign ownership. Most other companies operating inside the Emirates had to have at least fifty-one per cent ownership by a national. A foreign business couldn’t just enter the UAE and start selling its goods, but it was possible within the confines of the free zone.

“The only limitation you have is that you can’t sell anything on the territory of UAE,” Omar explained. This restricted my trade to only the clients from other countries, but on the flip side, there was no tax to pay. Whatever money my business made was pure profit. I could just pay it out to myself as dividends and pay no tax. I loved how that sounded.

This offer was clearly tailored to medium and large businesses. There were costs associated with a minimum number of square meters of office rent for each firm employee. It was a different form of taxation, paying rent instead of percentage costs. The key was finding the right balance between how many people you needed onshore or within the UAE and how many offshore. It made perfect sense.

We had a quick break before Omar took me around to show me the offices, facilities, cafes, restaurants, and such. They built a lovely place to work with hundreds of people already milling about, taking care of their own business. It was perfect.

“Let’s sit down for a minute,” Omar suggested as we passed a restaurant. Immediately, a waiter showed up carrying cups and plates with sweets. “This is Arabic coffee and the best baklava you’ve tried.” I smiled and took a bite. It was true that Arabs kill you with kindness and hospitality, and Omar was a gracious host. I could see he was enjoying it. It wasn’t just a sales tactic, but the man was proud of his place, the work he did, and helping me achieve my dream.

“Where do I sign?” I chuckled after having a sip of coffee. The man smiled and lifted his hand. Immediately, a secretary appeared out of nowhere with a golden fountain pen and a bunch of printed documents.

“I must give it to you, Omar. You know how to close.” The man watched me sign and laughed.

“My mother was Egyptian.” It must have been a cultural joke, as I missed the punch line. Still, I could appreciate the attempt. A man approached us, and Omar introduced me to another assistant. “Abdul will help you with everything. Whatever you need, he can sort it out for you.”

Omar excused himself, shook my hand, and then he was gone. Abdul sat on the other chair, helped me understand what I signed, and explained the process. He would help me with everything I needed, including corporate and personal bank accounts, visas, and work permits, for me and all my future employees.

After I finished my coffee, he took me up and showed me around, helping me choose my offices. I took five small ones designed for two people and a larger one for ten, working on an open plan with enough space for all the whiteboards and flip charts. With this, I got a separate glass room with a large desk, a dozen chairs, and a massive Microsoft video conferencing system.

“I would need some computers,” I said, and Abdul jumped to attention.

“Just send me what you need, sir, and I’ll handle it. That was some first-class service. I promised to send him the complete inventory list within a few days. All the major suppliers were there. I wanted to spec out twenty ThinkPads, a bunch of monitors, some server equipment, and a virtual WAN with locked-in VPN routing through a central access server that I could then bridge into various DMZ zones across cloud providers. I’ve been planning this for a long time and knew exactly how to organise it.

It was getting around that time, so I got up and walked outside. The ever-efficient employees gave me access cards and a printed folder with a welcome pack. My offices were ready to use, and I had access. Abdul promised to sort out my visa and bank accounts within a few days. Everything was going according to plan.

”To the airport, Iqbal.“ The driver nodded and put the car into drive. I spaced out, looking at the passing buildings, construction, and sand. These people managed to take one of the most inhospitable environments and tame it using knowledge and science. Someone told me Dubai was oil independent and successfully transitioned from a crude oil exporter to a city of luxury and commerce with one of the lowest crime rates on the planet. There was a lot to respect and admire.

It took us less than an hour to get there. I checked the display, and the plane had just landed. Some thirty-odd minutes later, I saw the girl pulling a yellow hardshell suitcase.

”Jim!“ Dixie screamed, running towards me with tears in her eyes. This trip tested her nerves and faith, but she made it from New York. That was all that mattered. She let it all out and cried. I barely recognised her for a moment. Dixie still looked incredibly slim but not sick and skeletal anymore. Regular diet and exercise did wonders for building her mass and muscle.

”Come, I’ll take you home.“ She gave me a faraway look. I imagined a home would be a novel concept for someone who spent almost four years homeless. The lawyer was able to get her birth certificate, after which everything was simple, and she was able to get her passport. Dixie wasn’t one of the nameless anymore.

I watched her eyes as Iqbal drove. They were full of wonder and amazement. I wasn’t the only one. Dixie grew up on the streets of a city several times the size of Dubai, and if anyone would be used to high-rise buildings, it would be her. New York looked mighty big for a small girl living on the streets.

Nothing prepared Dixie for what awaited her. She was expecting a city akin to New York, yet, just like me, she watched in awe as it sank in—a city inside a desert. A few generations ago, there was nothing there but sand, with a few lone Bedouin people with their camels and tents. They tamed the elements and the harshest of climates, turning their land into a miracle.

If suddenly all of humanity disappeared and mankind started again from caves, when they reached maturity and looked at the Earth from space, they would see the world and the palms and talk about the lost civilisation that created them, just like we do with the pyramids today. The people in this land, no matter how harsh and inhospitable, nurtured it, gave it water and made it blossom and thrive. There was a fundamental disconnect between the East and the West, and we were exporting our culture, infecting others with godlessness.

I wasn’t a believer, but I found faith. Somewhere along the line, following breadcrumbs thrown by Jack, reading between the lines of Montana, I found my faith. These simple yet complicated people in high rises and sports cars bowed down and knelt at dawn, before sunset, and at lunchtime—five times a day. They fasted for a month without food and water during daylight so they could remember and honour what they believed in. What did the West believe? What did I believe in? As I looked into Dixie’s eyes, her two deep blue pools of emotion, and the way she looked at me, I saw that Dixie had faith; she believed in me.

The shock and awe in her eyes grew even bigger as the car turned onto a road at the base of the palm. She gasped, seeing such riches and marvel, such wealth and opulence. It was as if the plane had been taken by a hurricane, and she was in some strange magical place, walking on a yellow brick road accompanied by Iqbal in the form of a lion and me as a tin man looking for a heart. In some ways, I envied Dixie. Her faith was enough for her.

The car stopped, and a beautiful black woman opened the door, wearing an exquisite black abaya and an embroidered hijab with golden thread.

”Peace be upon you,“ Neneh uttered with such a warm look and grace in her eyes as if she were greeting her favourite sister. I smiled. The teaching had already begun. I taught Dixie how to return the greeting, and after she said it correctly, Neneh smiled and waved her in.

”You must be parched after your trip. Come, I made you a fresh lemonade.“ Dixie followed the willowy woman, measuring her up and down, admiring her robes. Since Neneh put on her abaya, she only grew in stature. Her beauty only grew as it became rarer, as only her gorgeous face was visible, and the rest was left to the imagination alone. It was the most provocative statement of charms beyond the veil, a reward to be treasured, not flaunted.

It spoke of modesty, restraint, and respect—of the unspoken bond between men and women, celebrating the differences and the different roles we have in life as mothers and fathers, brothers and sisters. It was something to be celebrated instead of feared. It was a symbol of faith and a culture that revered women, where only the worthy man got to gaze upon a woman’s beauty. Instead of being oppressive, the abaya was a discerning robe.

I caught myself generalising again. Dubai wasn’t an accurate representation of eastern countries, but it served as a shiny beacon others tried to emulate, like Abu Dhabi growing a large mangrove forest in the desert or Doha in Qatar, which grew into a metropolis and a major communications hub, not to mention Saudi Arabia building The Line. Naypyidaw, a new capital of Myanmar, was built from scratch; Bangkok, a central southeastern Asia commercial hub; Singapore, the London of the East, from Hong Kong to Guangdong, to Shangri-La, to Beijing, and to Korea. The world was moving on at a staggering pace while the West was waging wars, slipping into irrelevance.

Perhaps that’s what made me think this way. Of course, the West is a complex and beautiful place, like London, New York, and hundreds of other places, Paris, Prague, Poland, and Portugal, with dozens of cultures, a real melting pot, but nobody could say they didn’t see a rapid decline, especially in the past few years, when it accelerated.

It was confusing and contradictory. Somehow it was immoral to prevent men from waving their penises in front of little girls in female toilets, but it was okay to legally ban women from wearing hijabs at schools while it was okay for the other girls to come in dressed like streetwalkers. It confused me, and I wasn’t alone. The ones in power sent us a message about what kind of world they wanted to live in. Not me.

”I’m starving.“ I caught that last bit. Neneh and Dixie were having a lively conversation, getting to know each other while my thoughts drifted. I realised at that moment, I was quite hungry as well, and I wanted to try a restaurant I found earlier.

Moments later, Iqbal drove us to Madinat Jumeirah. It was fun watching Dixie follow Neneh and look at everything. Her eyes were huge, moving from one place to another. Dixie had to examine everything, touch it, or smell it. It seemed to me that the girls forgot they were hungry and having too much fun exploring the open mall. One thing I noticed was that Neneh was careful with cash. She bought the best of things, but only what was necessary. All the fun little trinkets she looked at and liked remained on their shelves. She was the perfect person to manage the preservation of wealth. She was only eighteen, but she was trained to perfection to know the difference between what is valuable and what is meaningless.

We tried a different restaurant this time, an Arab-style grill. It tasted exquisite, with all those exotic spices I couldn’t recognise, and it had a strong scent of garlic. I would be worried about kissing someone, but luckily, the only two people I’d kiss ate the same. Neneh praised the food, while Dixie just mmm-ed, masticating her chicken like a hungry wolf. I was happy to see her appetite was as strong as ever. She even stole a few bits from my plate that I left for later.

The girls were so excited to run and explore that they didn’t even wait for the dessert. They just kissed my cheeks when nobody was looking and disappeared in the silent hallways, giggling like children. It made me smile. Both girls were barely eighteen and celebrating their lives. It made me feel both young and old at the same time.

The waiter came over, and I paid. He told me about some interesting shops along the way. I wanted to buy something special for my women—premium dates with nuts and chocolate. Apparently, there was a confectionery that sold them in many varieties. I was curious to see it and maybe have a taste. I never had a sweet tooth and prefer savoury, but this was interesting and unique.

I thanked the man and took my leave, turning left and right, following the corridors, doing my own walk without a focus or an agenda. A gust of wind brought the faintest scent of lilac. My body instantly reacted. The hairs on my arms jumped, and goosebumps adorned my skin. I felt my heart skip a beat.

Like by some unheard command, I turned and followed something green and elusive, something I convinced myself I only imagined. Then I saw her, like seeing a dawn for the first time. She was a woman unlike any I had seen before, and I knew that I had met perfection, a statistical impossibility, a perfect ten on the M-scale. Her beauty was so rare; no TV program or fashion magazine could even begin to describe something like that. The woman was so beautiful that she almost radiated.

My throat was dry, my eyes bulged, my head swirled, and my ears rang. What was I thinking about? I couldn’t remember. Everything that I was just melted, and without even speaking, I was in her power. I believed the stories now about Helen of Troy, about all the mythical goddesses from old tales.

She turned to me and said something in Arabic, like a muse from old Arabian tales. I felt a shiver inside me as the subtle tones of her voice strummed each and every molecule of my body, making them vibrate. There was no power in this world that could make me control myself around her. It was something powerful and primal, something I wasn’t even aware existed.

Men, I was sure, would go to war for this woman. They would lay down their lives for even a fraction of her attention. I tried to look at her and understand, but every time my eyes focused, there was another wave of beauty, from a lock of her hair to her perfectly manicured nails. But it was her eyes.

I had never seen eyes like that. They were sparkling green, like two emeralds reflecting the sunlight. She wore a dark green silk abaya with a matching hijab and some Arabic calligraphy verses sewn in pure golden thread by hand.

”Are you lost?“ the woman asked. Her voice went through me in waves like the sound of some sort of celestial instrument. I had to clear my throat before I could say something, nodding at the same time. Her smile grew bigger, and I saw her perfectly white teeth. They looked like polished pearls.

”Those who seek must ask Azza wa Jal for guidance.“ None of it made sense, but I didn’t care. I was mesmerised and enchanted by the sound of her voice.

”I was looking for the date shop,“ I said, and the woman pointed her hand down the corridor. She was young, in her twenties, yet her voice reverberated with the wisdom of ages. How she spoke and intoned pulled one’s mind into a world of wonder. I didn’t want her to leave. I would gladly stand there and listen to her speak, even though I couldn’t understand anything.

”What does it say?“ I pointed at the golden letters shown on her robe. Her eyes grew softer, like a person in love.

I couldn’t understand a word, but her voice enchanted me. The way she said it sounded like she was reading poetry. She turned to leave, and I was desperate, praying inside she would spare another moment.

”What is your name?“ She turned to me again, looking proud, and spoke. My eyes were focused on the way she moved her lips.

”I am Tasneem bint Rasheeda bint Uzma bint Asiya.“ Then, she disappeared. It took me a few moments to realise the most beautiful woman in the world was gone.

”Was she? Was she real?“ I asked, and a salesman smiled, with a bright spark in his eyes, nodding at me to confirm I wasn’t dreaming.

”Who is she? A princess of some kind?“ The man nodded, confirming what I suspected.

”She is noble born, my friend. This is her land.“

”You mean she is Emirati?“ The man laughed as if I said something funny.

”Didn’t you hear her speak? She speaks the ancient tongue. Her claim to this land is older than the written word. It is in her blood, the most noble blood. She is noble born. It is her birthright.“

I walked around, feeling like I was floating on clouds. A chance meeting with the most beautiful woman jumbled my senses. Never before had I dreamt someone this beautiful could exist. It was something that words fail to describe, a level of beauty and purity that defies comprehension. Most of all, I wondered what kind of man would deserve a woman like that. Something told me no one. That woman had only one master.

Like by some magic, I found myself in front of the store. I couldn’t remember the path I took there. I was lost, and I was found as if some mysterious hand had guided me. What did the woman say? Those who seek must ask for guidance.

I laughed. All of it seemed surreal, like a part of some fairy tale. If for no other reason than the beauty of that woman, Dubai became a special place. Where else could I find someone like that? She passed through my life, and only a scent of lilac remained. I knew now my life was complete. I would never see or meet anyone more beautiful than that.

When I looked at her, I didn’t just want her. My entire being desired her, but I wasn’t the one good enough for her, and neither was anyone. I was sure the woman had chosen her own way, and no man on Earth could change any of that, but she proved what I had learned from Dan and the others. There is such a thing as a ten on an M-scale, which is a mathematical improbability. One in eight billion people on the planet. The chances of meeting someone like that are so small that they are laughable. One would be better off gambling. This reminded me of the lottery ticket, and I laughed. Who is to say what a win or loss is if you have imagination? Maybe that’s what Tasneem was sent to teach me by some better angels.

What would you like, a middle-aged woman with a gold-coloured hijab asked. Behind her were dozens of different kinds of dates. Some were rolled in cinnamon, others filled with nuts and dipped in chocolate. Some were filled with dry figs, others saffron and sesame seeds.

”I want all of them.“ The woman smiled. She took several small paper bags and started selecting them for me. I took one and I couldn’t stop my smile. It was the best date I tried.

For some reason, I felt like having a coffee afterwards, so I paid and went into a nearby café, sat down, and enjoyed myself. There is something to life and its mysteries. Everything that happened got me thinking. Dan taught me social skills and how to talk to other people, which sent me on a journey of personal discovery and growth, but I couldn’t have done it without one key ingredient: imagination.

I heard a squealing noise and looked up wondering how did the girls manage to find me. I was hopelessly lost in the souk’s hallways while the two of them seemed to navigate it without a single issue.

When I first looked, it took me a moment. Dixie wanted to fit in, and Neneh agreed. She led the young American to the same shop where we bought Neneh clothes, and the kind saleswoman let her try her designs. The girls bought four abayas for Dixie with matching hijabs, black with golden thread. She wore her favourite one. I looked down and saw the girls had matching shoes. They looked incredible and drew attention from everyone.

”I got you some snacks but waited too long and ate them all.“ I reached into a paper bag to pull out one chocolate-covered date and took a bite. The girls squealed and protested, blaming me for eating their presents.

”Well, if you’re really good to me later, I might find one or two that strayed.“ I loved to watch them laugh and tease them. The girls were so happy and full of life. It wasn’t the shopping; it was the place. Somehow, all of us felt like anything was possible.

Chapter 37 - The games we play

I felt my muscles tense and opened my eyes, losing for a moment the track of myself. All I could feel was the sperm erupting out of my throbbing cock, being sucked out by someone’s hungry mouth. It took a second for the fog to clear and dispel the remnants of the dream I couldn’t remember before my eyes focused on two naked ladies kissing each other with my erupting cock between them.

Neneh and Dixie ate my cum with hunger. Judging by the erect nipples and a thin sheen of perspiration on their bodies, I imagined they had been at it for some time.

The memories of last night came back in flashes, how we got naked and took a shower, falling into bed together. Then I fucked them till I collapsed, barely scratching the itch the two had felt. What have I done? I kept asking myself, having created a perfect maze. I released two sex-starved kittens inside like Minotaurs of ancient Greek legends.

The two girls were so different yet so similar in many ways, especially when it came to sexual need and desire; both of them were sex-starved. The two literally fucked me to unconsciousness long after it was time to stop and rest. They tested my endurance, and I failed.

“Good morning, husband,” Neneh said, mumbling, barely containing all the sperm behind her lips. Before I could answer, Dixie solved the problem by sticking her tongue in Neneh’s mouth, giving her a nasty frencher like in porn films.

I felt my cock twitch at the sight. This was the proof I was an old pervert after all, or maybe just a man. I couldn’t think of any guy who would remain unaffected. I knew at that moment that all could go to hell. If I hadn’t extricated myself from the situation, I would have spent another day in bed, but I had plans and arrangements that were unavoidable. It was the most important appointment I’ve had in my new life.

With ultimate will and determination, I forced myself to get out of bed and hit the shower, leaving the two horny minxes to take care of each other. By the time I was done, the two came down to see me out, completely naked, holding their hands, making me wonder what would happen when the doors closed.

“Focus, Jim,” I mumbled to myself as the car pulled away, and I tried to focus on the lessons of the day. I would need all my faculties.

***

I waved at Dan and another guy as they walked over. Vertu concierge booked me a lounge at Bar 44 on the top floor of the Grosvenor House Tower featuring amazing views of the city and The Palm. I could almost see my rented villa from where I was. This bar was the best environment to discuss what I wanted, with soft music playing in the background. Dan shook my hand with a smile, introducing me to Grr.

“That’s unusual.” I almost chuckled.

“It’s actually Gearóid, but I got tired of correcting people mispronouncing my name, and now I’m stuck with it.” Grr was a third-generation businessman from Cork, Ireland, who inherited several factories. He came from the “old money” and was one of Dan’s old students.

Unlike most men, Grr only wanted one specific woman in his life, and he went through Dan’s training, learning and practising. Still, the woman was a beauty queen and a professional fashion model dating a footballer. It was a tall order to start with until Dan introduced him to his old friend, an inventor of the hooker game, the creator of the M-scale himself.

“Unfortunately, he doesn’t teach anymore. I tried to reach out, but he dropped off the planet,” Dan said. Grr was the next best thing, one of the best students who spent a fortune mastering the skill of skills and learning how to seduce the most sought-after and rare woman on the planet, the eights and nines on the M-scale.

“What about a ten?” I asked, remembering a mysterious woman in a green silk abaya.

“According to the M-scale, there can only be one or a handful of tens on the planet, as it reflects the absolute rarity and beauty, the same way as ‘one’ would reflect the absolute ugliness. You won’t find those either.” It made me smile. I wondered how Dan or Grr would react to meeting the mysterious Middle Eastern princess.

I measured Grr up and down. He appeared like just another guy, no expensive clothes, nothing even eye-catching about him. It went against everything that I learned from Dan or observed from anyone.

“So what happened? Did you get the girl in the end?” Grr’s face darkened, and he shook his head. Dan jumped in to add more context to what I could only interpret as Grr’s sadness.

“Remember, I told you that learning this stuff is dangerous. It changes you.” Of course, Grr got the girl and lost her because he realised he was in love with the idea of the girl rather than the woman herself. From the outside, he saw a finely-layered tapestry of a different variety, weaves beyond weaves, masks beyond masks, and he peeled them each with the ultimate care, only to find another below it. That’s when he got to the core and couldn’t handle the abyss.

I knew what Dan was talking about. For some reason, I attracted women damaged in some way. Perhaps my own damage attracted me to them, my quiet desperation broadcasting through my movements or the way I looked at them. I could recognise myself in them, and they could likely do the same. Birds of a feather flock together, they say. I could see why it turned the man insane.

Grr was born and raised by a loving family. He had a father, a mother, and two younger sisters. He went to the best schools, had all the money, the best food, the best cars, and the best girlfriends. Some could say he was spoiled. He never met a real challenge in his life, and when he did, Grr’s resources could make it all go away, but not that. He couldn’t fix the girl he pursued and went to the greatest length to get her, and finally, he had to leave her to keep himself sane.

This was the price Dan was talking about. Be careful what you wish for, they say, because you just might get it, and then you will learn something about yourself. I almost chuckled but managed to catch myself. I knew exactly what they were talking about. Some people have multiple layers below the surface to keep the dragon hidden.

Grr got the girl, and she meant everything to him. Then she went nuts and started breaking at the seams. He tried to change her, but it was impossible, and he wasn’t willing to change himself to adapt to the “new normal.“ Grr got out, leaving the girl how he found her, on her own downward spiral, searching for connection, and she fell.

I didn’t seem to have such a problem. Perhaps because I was damaged as well, or maybe due to my relentless analysis and willingness to adapt to everything and anything, focused on the silver lining. Some people are bears like Grr, and some are chameleons like me. Some are tigers, and some are mice; some are hunters, and some are hunted.

Whatever demons possessed Grr, I didn’t think he had a problem with women. He had a problem with himself. That’s when it clicked inside my head. It was the books Jack gave me to read. They steered my self-development and imagination more than I initially assumed. Somehow, they passed through my critical mind and went straight into my subconsciousness at the peak of my change. I no longer wondered about what it means to be a man. I became one without realising it, and I couldn’t explain it.

In the beginning, when I asked Dan, “What does it mean to be a man?“ he chuckled, knowing exactly the path I was going to take. Nobody can define what a man is in one sentence. The best anyone can do is list a set of attributes, but therein lies the danger.

If someone asks you to make a meal by just giving you a list of ingredients, and you mix it together, disaster is imminent. That’s why they say in cookbooks, “Add salt to taste,“ which means experience. This is what Montana did for me. It let me live through Carter’s life, touch his power and weakness, love and pain. Somehow, without my conscious awareness, it changed me inside.

I could see Grr had the knowledge and all the smoothness. His body language was well-practiced. His tone and voice were perfectly pitched to enter one’s mind and pass through the cracks, eliciting deep emotional responses well past the layers of consciousness. Grr was a smooth player akin to a spider, weaving and waiting, planting breadcrumbs, but he was unwilling to get his hands dirty. All of it hit me, what Jack said. Grr had no faith.

When I started on this path, everything seemed daunting; everything seemed like magic. Not so much now. I had only one skill to master and only one question to ask.

“How do I stop the reset?“ Grr’s eyebrows went up, and Dan gave me a slight smile.

“I didn’t know you got so far,“ Grr said, then took a pen and started to draw circles on the napkin. “To understand how we have to start from the beginning,“ he said. It was a journey down the rabbit hole, mixing the original knowledge with his own theories and observations.

I bombarded him with questions, structuring them as I was trained, in such a way as to lead me to a specific set of answers Grr himself might not have been aware of or saw them this way. The man was an amalgamation of contradictions, but if there was one thing I was sure of, it was that the man was a treasure trove of helpful knowledge. He just didn’t know how to present it well. I wondered at one point how the original inventor came up with that. Who was he in the first place? The mystery added to it, and I took mental notes and listened.

Somewhere, I was sure Freud and Jung were twisting in their graves. How someone took psychoanalysis and twisted it, almost weaponised it for his own purposes. It takes a deep understanding of personal trauma to see how it could be redirected in a more constructive way to turn people from obsessive self-destructive tendencies to something equally negative but valuable.

In my numerous attempts to understand how Cassie’s mind worked, I read pretty much all the required reading for a psychology degree graduate, plus a whole lot more, including the random psychobabble on the internet. I even spoke with my psychiatrist several times, and the consensus was—leave her alone.

This kind of resetting, self-destructive behaviour was indicative of early childhood trauma no amount of psychotherapy could fix. The best one could hope to achieve was long-term regression therapy to understand the problem, come to terms with it, and begin to heal.

“So there is no guarantee that the new persona coming out of it would be any better off than the current one?“ I asked my therapist.

“There is no way to tell.“ In fact, the emerging personality could end up being worse than the original one. Psychology wasn’t an exact science, but Grr was suggesting that it could be subverted. The deeply rooted behavioural patterns could not be healed but could be rerouted so that a fragmented personality could get attached to a different stable individual, thus replacing one anchor with another.

All of it would sound like a bunch of bullshit mumbo jumbo if the examples Grr pulled weren’t so much like the women I knew in my life and cared for. According to him, the trick was simple—penetrate the other person’s core psyche and attach it to yourself, so whenever the mind resets, that person seeks you rather than something else to feel stable and safe.

I wondered if something like this was even possible, let alone transferrable, not to mention the glaring, profound moral implications. It was obvious from the start that if one achieved such a feat, the affected person would end up irreversibly dependent, and if you left her, it could lead to a mental breakdown.

Dan was right; this changes you. Should one person have such knowledge, let alone teach it to someone? I understood now why the inventor vanished. He made an equivalent of a nuclear bomb and then taught it to someone. With this knowledge, a man could find a way to manipulate the most beautiful women into doing what he wanted, use them and discard them, leaving them more broken than they found them.

Lord Acton said that power corrupts, and absolute power corrupts absolutely. This seemed as close to absolute power as one could get, and I wasn’t sure if I could use it responsibly. What would stop me from using it maliciously? Sooner or later, I would get my comeuppance, like Grr, for example. I understood him better now. He allowed this power to corrupt him and was now paying the ultimate price. There was much more to the story about the girl he once loved, and I could read the guilt and pain on his face.

It made sense why Dan washed his hands from it and why he wouldn’t teach me. If I made a mistake and hurt someone, it would be on his conscience, but this way, it was between me and Grr. Perhaps Grr needed the money, or there was another reason at play. I was sure that if I had this skill, I would never teach it to another.

In a sense, Dan put me in front of a dilemma, perhaps to test what I was made of and the strength of my character. Would I just finish my drink and walk away, or would I dare tempt my fate? I was never much of a gambler, so I drank my orange juice and waved the waiter over.

“I’ll have a Mai Tai,“ I said, and Grr ordered another. Dan gave me a measured look and chucked.

“Sorry, guys. I’ve got other plans.“ We shook hands, and he was gone. It was just me and Grr now and all his knowledge, which I intended to suck out, learn and implement. As dangerous as it was, who could resist the power? It was once a life opportunity, and I wanted it. I was too invested by this point.

Grr smiled like he was pulling me to the dark side, paying for his own release from hell with the soul of another. He waved a waiter over and asked for some paper. Minutes later, he gave Grr an entire notepad with a hotel logo on top.

“Here we go,“ Grr said and started lying it all down. The idea was simple. Because of their unique beauty, the extraordinary women were exposed to unwanted advances from an early age, which continued well through their puberty into maturity. This resulted in a fragmented personality with its core still childish, then another layer for each fake persona she constructed to deal with the world she didn’t understand.

Breaking through it was pretty easy by following cracks, asking penetrating questions, leading their imagination deeper, and building trust.

“All this is a child’s play compared to what came next.“ Some women are so dysfunctional they present a danger to themselves and others. They are usually a carefully arranged amalgamation of weakness and strength, often presenting themselves as super-confident out of overcompensation for their insecurities.

“Trust is the biggest thing for them. That’s how you get them.” Grr launched into various techniques for building trust at every level, penetrating deeper, and doing the same.

“Sometimes, you can’t even keep them stable, so you must break and reassemble them.” Effectively, Grr was suggesting using deep emotional manipulation to rearrange another person’s perception so that he would become an integral part of her psyche. She would borrow his power and strength to supplement her weaknesses.

The problem was that any weakness on my part could act as a massive destabilising effect with far-reaching consequences. It would be terrible to do to another person, but I understood Grr’s logic. If a person was so unstable, leaning on another could make her stronger, thus masking or relieving some of the emotional pressure resulting from poor self-perception, and her life would seem better, at least for a while.

I was engrossed and fascinated. The depth of Grr’s knowledge was incredible. Whenever I asked something, he had an answer, but sometimes, we had to do a deep dive into the core of one’s identity. It made me feel like everything I did so far, and all I learned from Dan, was to prepare me to hear and understand this.

It would be tough to grasp some of the subjects Grr talked about if I didn’t go through a transformative process myself and witness firsthand people with such issues. It wasn’t just Cassie, but all of my women to one degree or another, but it seemed that Cassie’s issue was much bigger than the others. Then again, she was more beautiful than the other girls.

“Does this affect more beautiful women?” I asked, and Grr launched into all sorts of explanations using the M-method for grading looks. What he was talking about was pure genetics, the pseudo-random distribution of desirable traits in a sort of mirrored Gaussian distribution with zero to five in both positive and negative directions, plotted against a sinusoidal shape to illustrate the bell curves.

“Biology is a bitch,” he said and laughed. It was a self-loathing internal joke only Grr could understand. He was undoubtedly an interesting character, strong and confident, yet something was off about him. I couldn’t quite see what. We all have our cross to bear, and I could see Grr carrying a heavy one. My worst personal trait was that I had to know and understand everything, and it took me a long time to learn how to walk away. I didn’t want to understand Grr or his motivations. I just wanted his knowledge to fix a serious problem back home.

Luckily, Grr was a talker, happy to share anything, and I used it. We talked for hours, even during lunch, until my brain gave up. All this knowledge, thoughts, and impressions were swirling inside my head as my mind worked overtime trying to sort, categorise, and put things in the right places.

“How does one practice that?” I asked in the end.

“That is the hard part,” Grr said. “You can’t make an omelette without breaking a few eggs.” I hated the man at that moment, or maybe I hated myself and was projecting. The truth was, I knew what I had to do, but Grr was so cavalier about it.

“This knowledge comes with a price,” I remembered Dan saying that, and just like watching a war on the news, it felt so distant and detached. Not anymore. How does one master this knowledge without turning into a monster? There had to be a golden thread that would allow me to pull it and walk a fine line.

Maybe I bought into Grr’s interpretation too much and haven’t considered that his entire perception came from a dark place. Perhaps another teacher would be better suited to guide me through the maze. Some say that it’s not guns that kill people, and we need more of them. How about magic? At what point does it turn black? I could see how powerful the skill was and how it could turn me into a villain.

Grr and I parted ways before dinner, arranging a follow-up meeting in a day. I had an assignment to complete and report on so he could assess and correct me. I had three chances to learn it and three chances to mess up. After that, in Grr’s own words, I was on my own.

Iqbal took me home, stopping at the pharmacy on the way. I needed something to stop my tension headache. I was concentrated for eight hours straight, and my thoughts were abuzz with everything I had learned and analysed. Inside my mind, I tried to structure it, draw parallels, identify gaps, and interpret everything in a way I could internalise and apply.

The doors closed behind me, and the girls weren’t there. I called out to them, but nobody responded. It was getting dark outside, so I climbed up a floor to the master bedroom, thinking they got bored waiting for me and fell asleep.

I found the two of them just as I had left them. The bed was a crumpled, sweaty mess, with pussy juice and sweat covering every inch of it. The pungent odour of sex filled the room, almost making me choke.

Neneh and Dixie were on top of each other, their tongues exploring each other’s pussies, utterly oblivious to the world around them. They were lost in their own world of sexual fantasies, and it made me wonder if Neneh’s lesbian fantasies were just an experiment or if there was more to it. As for Dixie, I could imagine that after her life experiences, she would feel more comfortable bonding with women.

I stood there for a while as my cock hardened, watching the girls eat each other out to another orgasm and collapse. It was evident they had been at it since I left, and it made me wonder about their youthful stamina. Even in my best days, I wouldn’t be able to last all day like they seemed to do so effortlessly. The two insatiable minxes were something else.

“Welcome home, husband,“ Neneh suddenly said, noticing me by the door as the fog of her orgasm cleared. Dixie squealed and ran towards me, but she slipped and fell, her legs made of jelly and her knees buckling.

“Let’s have a nice bath,“ I suggested, needing one myself. The girls yelped with excitement but needed help getting there. It only took minutes to carry and place both of them in hot, bubbling water, adding some fragrant bath salts. I stripped down and joined them, and the two embraced me, one on each side. I couldn’t help but laugh as a scene from one of Mel Brooks‘ movies came to mind.

“It’s good to be the king,“ I muttered before putting my head underwater and shaking it around. It felt great. This was how life should be lived.

Chapter 38 - Kitchen sink

Neneh was still horny in the morning after I had eaten her to several orgasms. I had plans for the day, and I needed to look after myself, so I rummaged through the suitcases Dixie brought from the States, finding a wearable clitoral vibrator, attaching it to my wife and putting it on Max.

“You can’t take it off until I return,” I said. The mischievous me wanted some revenge. Neneh nodded, rolling her eyes, biting her lip, following my command. Dixie complained that I wasn’t fair, so I attached another one to her and gave her the same task. She was right. I should have treated all my girls the same.

It almost made me laugh as I got ready and went downstairs, took a snack to eat and got ready for the day. How life has changed, I reminisced. Sometimes, I couldn’t even recognise myself. It was hard to even remember the old Jim as my world changed with me in it.

Just before eleven, I stood at the brushed steel tube security barrier outside the arrivals section of Dubai airport, holding my takeaway paper coffee cup and scanning people. Paige’s plane had landed some thirty minutes earlier. Considering the time to go through immigration and collect her luggage, I was right on time.

Paige recognised me from afar and waved, broadcasting an incredible smile. By the expressions of all the men staring at her as she walked towards me, I could tell I wasn’t the only one affected by Paige’s beauty.

She was a rare gem, a so-called Instagram influencer with almost three million followers. Paige could only be described as a buxom blonde with incredible natural breasts the size of cantaloupe halves, tall, slim, and curvy at five-foot-ten. Unlike many fashion models, she had some meat on her bones, making her appear more desirable.

The girl was on fire, a natural dirty blonde seductress with a perfect face, pouty red lips of a man-eater, and beautiful grey eyes. In a word, Paige was stunning, easily on par with any of my women, almost on the level of Cassie, and certainly on par with Shay.

Paige advertised herself as a model, and YouTube was full of her swimwear clips with her massive breasts spilling from her bra. She was a stunning female specimen, a sentiment shared by all her followers.

What most people didn’t know, though, was that Paige was for sale. I connected with her on Instagram and offered five grand for two days plus the plane tickets, all expenses paid. It took her a few days to respond and negotiate. We settled on seven, and I got to do with her whatever I liked.

How does one practice a hooker game? It won’t work on regular girls, and I wasn’t going to try it on just anyone. If what I learned from Dan about the effects was true, I wouldn’t get stuck with someone I wasn’t at least attracted to, so I chose Paige. She fit several criteria that would make her a good candidate—beauty, external locus of identity, using her looks to earn money, and such. She was my first choice and the best candidate.

When I analysed her Instagram, YouTube, and other social media, I concluded that Paige would be an easy target. She was gorgeous but not too bright, most likely easily influenced and manipulated, as evidenced by some questionable choices she made in her past at the behest of her ex-boyfriend. I was certain that the man caused her irreparable emotional damage.

Paige was only twenty and not going to university. She focused all her efforts and invested herself into becoming a social media icon, but all her posts were about her body, stemming from the unfulfilled need for admiration and praise. The clothes Paige looked cheap, almost second-hand. I had no doubt that the men she chose were capitalising on that. In fact, I was convinced that I could have gotten her for five grand, as she only negotiated a higher rate to pump her own ego and a perceived value.

Someone did a real number on Paige at a critical time of her life and messed her up so badly that she sought strong and muscular men as her partners. This told me a story of insecurity, a need to be protected as well as admired by others. This made her a perfect training partner.

Is it stalking if you follow someone who publishes their info online? Most of Paige’s followers were men. In fact, I used the Instagram API to write a little program that would spit out a lot of statistical data, and as expected, over eighty per cent of her almost three million followers were guys. They didn’t follow her for cooking advice. Were we all stalking that girl at once? How about her boyfriend? I noticed several recent pictures with his hands or arms in the frame. Did he know where she was going or what she would do? Was he her pimp?

Page’s eyes were everywhere. The girl had no fear, just an incredible excitement of someone living the high life for the first time. I was wrong to assume the girl was dim. Something else was going on; she was incredibly naive. There is a difference between stupidity and a lack of intelligence. I could see Page’s eyes absorb everything with such clarity and interest that there could be no mistake about her lack of intelligence.

This reminded me of Dan’s story about a guy with two daughters. I could draw a parallel to the pretty one. Paige was likely pretty from day one and used her beauty to get what she wanted. Then something happened, and she created a shell, then another and another, projecting a look of a confused dumb blonde.

It is strange how we sometimes choose masks, and what’s even more bizarre is when we start to believe them. Sometimes, what you project reflects on the inside and changes you into the person wearing your own flesh suit. That’s how the fat man becomes fatter. He identifies himself with that image. Over time, it becomes comfortable, so all his efforts to change are mood-based instead of concrete plans and determination.

“I always dreamed about visiting Dubai,” Paige said, and I understood that. For a lot of Instagram personalities, Dubai is a rite of passage with the Burj Al Arab in most pictures. The girl would stand on the Jumeirah beach and take pictures, but none from the inside. It is too expensive and an extravagance.

A part of the deal that convinced Paige to travel was when I mentioned where we would stay. This would instantly elevate her photos and TikTok videos to a whole new level and establish her as someone who didn’t just pose but lived that lifestyle. The appeal of the limelight and being worshipped by the masses is irresistible to some people.

Paige was like a little kid trapped inside the body of a beautiful princess, and I had to admit it to myself; I felt more attracted to her exuberance than her looks. How the tables have turned almost made me chuckle. A year ago, I would give my left nut for even a kiss from someone like that, and here I was, objectifying her looks. She was an eight on an M-scale, which made Paige hotter than the average Victoria’s Secret model, most of whom would be mere sevens using the same metrics.

I watched her big eyes and gaping mouth as Iqbal drove us to the Burj Al Arab. Paige didn’t want to miss anything. She jumped and squealed as I brought her in and led her to our room. She couldn’t believe it. Immediately, Page started taking photos and videos of herself, and I smiled. Her first concern was how to please her followers.

Paige’s large hardshell suitcase was packed to the brim with high heels, bikinis, lingerie, and tiny summer dresses, all of which seemed slightly aged. None of her clothes were new, but they looked great on the phone after applying the suitable filters. This incongruence caught my attention and got me thinking. There was much more to this young lady than she was willing to show me.

God bless the internet and everything you can find on it. Paige sent me a photo of her passport when I was booking her tickets under the guise that I needed all the information to complete the booking. With her full name, date of birth, and some additional info, I could track down her family and friends. Paige was born in Des Moines but moved to Cedar Rapids when she was nine to live with her aunt Bessie, two older sons, Ricky and Dave, seventeen and twenty, and a younger daughter, Ann Margaret, age fourteen.

Bessie was a housewife, and her husband, Todd, used to play hockey for RoughRiders before getting married, getting injured, and joining Rockwell Aerospace. This was long before the Raytheon merger when he was made redundant and found a job with one of the cereal manufacturers. At least, that is what all the LinkedIn and Facebook pages revealed.

Whatever happened after was a mystery. I couldn’t dig up any information that would tell me what happened with Paige between ages ten and twenty and how she ended up in Riverside. It was the kind of a town people moved away from, not into, especially if they looked like Paige. There are many opportunities for a girl with such looks in Los Angeles, New York, or anywhere else. I was certain Paige had quite a story to tell.

“I’m going to take a shower,” she said and happily bounced off into the bathroom with a smile. She was teasing me, pulling my strings, making me imagine how she looked naked. I expected this was a standard modus operandi for an Instagram personality; all tease and no, please. I was willing to bet that, at least on some level, Paige counted on that, and if she could string me along for two days, she would be in the clear or perhaps open to negotiating.

“You must establish the difference,” I remembered Grr saying. His whole idea was that you need to jump out of the “customer” mindset and work with the girl on a different level. Paige came here because I paid to fuck her, and according to Grr, that would be the last thing I should do, open a back door and peel the layers instead, find the little cracks and gain trust, and work on her mind.

When I questioned him to the nth degree, Grr had to admit that it was the formula he used that worked for him consistently, but it wasn’t a part of the original knowledge. The inventor of the hooker game said something like that, but just as an example. There was no hard rule about it, and I was tempted to trust his judgment more than Grr’s, so I decided to experiment. After all, this was the first of the three dates I arranged for myself, and if I failed, I would have learned something valuable.

I took off my clothes in a flash and went into the bathroom. Paige saw the doors open, and there I was, standing butt naked. Even from this distance, I could see a shock on her face, a dark shadow passing across it, like some sort of disappointment, then suddenly it was all fine. She was sexy and smiling again.

“There we go,” I thought and entered the glass enclosure. I found a crack in the first layer. Paige looked into my eyes, probably wondering what I would do next. Would I kiss her or play with her breasts?

“Here, take this. Wash my back.” I handed her a soap and turned away from her. Five seconds later, I felt her hands explore my back, slowly at first but gaining confidence. By the time I turned around, Paige soaped up my cock and balls without any hesitance.

“My turn now,” I said, taking the soap from her hands, pushing her shoulder to turn her, and gently massaging her back. All the massage skills I learned came in handy. I could see the anticipation and stress practically melt away from Paige’s muscles. She liked it.

When it came to soaping her front, I paid a lot of attention to her perfectly smooth pussy and breasts. At one moment, I could see her eyes glaze over, and she bit her lip. I didn’t make her cum, just kept her aroused. It was easy to read it in her brilliant eyes.

Paige licked her lips with her perfect pink tongue, and her eyes drifted from mine to my lips and back. I got closer as if to kiss her, but I just brushed her lips with the corner of my mouth, going for her ear instead. As soon as I licked it and breathed into it, goosebumps covered Paige’s skin.

“I want to kiss you so much,” I said, and she nodded.

“You can if you want.” Her rapid breath came out like from a dog.

“I don’t kiss whores.” It was like I slapped Paige’s face. All her muscles tensed, and her eyes popped open. I could read the humiliation and pain in them, some anger as well.

“Come, I want to fuck you now,” I said, pulling her hand and handing her a towel, leading her to the bedroom, not letting her mind catch up with what happened. Before she could say anything, I pushed her onto the soft plush bed, covered in silk and high thread count linen.

“Spread your legs for me,” I commanded, and she moved her knees to the sides, giving me unrestricted access to her straight line with a bit of pink protruding from inside. I could detect no wetness there. Whatever arousal she might have felt was gone with my crude, tactless comment.

This didn’t stop me from jumping in and sticking my tongue deep into her pussy. Paige tasted divine; it was so clean and smelled nice. Clearly, she paid attention to hygiene. It took only a minute before Paige’s pussy was running like a river. I heard her moan as she gyrated her hips.

“Cum, whore, cum for daddy,” I said and attacked her clit. I could see the redness in her face, so I stopped licking her for a second, “You are my little whore for two days. I want you to cum, slut.” Then, I ate her again.

Paige’s orgasm hit her like a train. She bit her lip and arched her back, but I wasn’t stopping my ministrations, seeking to give her a bigger one. By now, I learned how to make women cum so hard that it feels like their bones would break. It was my signature move, and I often practised to refine it.

She mewed and turned her head from side to side, biting her lip and rolling her eyes. Her skin broke out in goosebumps, and her face was on fire. Paige squeaked, moaned, and gurgled, pulling on bedsheets with her fists balled so hard her nails were unglued. Every few minutes, she would contract and tremble, releasing a howling sound like a pack of starving wolves. She lost track of time, day or night, watching the seasons fly in front of her eyes until it happened.

Her body took over and balled up. Paige’s spine cracked when it extended and bent backwards. A strong blast of piss shot out like from a high-pressure water gun, narrowly missing my face as it shot across the bed to soak the rung on the floor and polished marble.

Before she had a chance to get down from her high, I put on a condom and climbed on top. Without excess ceremony or any reluctance, I stabbed her with my engorged thrill-seeking missile, feeling her still-twitching insides. Paige’s pussy enveloped me like a steaming velvet glove, smooth and slippery from all the juices she had expelled just moments earlier.

Without mercy or further foreplay, I jackhammered hard, trying to please myself while our eyes met and our gazes locked as if in arm wrestling for control. There was nothing else to say, no other word or procedure. I was a man, and she was a woman. The rest was self-explanatory. I pounded my cock into her pink supple flesh without care, rest, or mercy, and she loved it.

I felt her tremble below me as I kneaded her fat, perfect tits, feasting on her perfect pink puffy nipples that equally taunted and teased me. The sharp sounds of slaps mixed with deeper echoes of thuds filled the room as I rode her like a rapist escaped from a life sentence. Her guttural moans and growls mixed with high-pitched staccato squeals like hiccups answered my mating calls of unbridled lust and pleasure.

Paige came again as I sunk my teeth into her breast, sucking on it like a starving vampire. It was too much for her, and for the first time since I took her, she screamed. It sounded like a wail. Something broke inside, and the way Paige looked at me completely changed. It looked like I broke something, a fourth wall between her act and the audience, and there she was in her full gorgeous glory, a woman letting go of all the pretence and worries.

I lost myself inside her eyes. After she came again, even they smiled. Perhaps it was only imagined, but I saw a flood of emotions course through her face, and I screamed, feeling my balls squeeze and tighten. All those years when women like this were beyond my imagination, let alone reach, bubbled to the surface. I jackhammered hard, losing myself in that moment, pounding, kneading, and stabbing with all my stamina and strength until I felt Paige tensing again.

I screamed, and she howled. I fucked her so fast, as if trying to turn her pussy into pulp, feeling her pussy squeeze and pulsate. It was too much for any self-control I could muster, and I released an almost painful orgasm, punching my cock into her like trying to break through her external os and dump my baby makers right into her womb to seed her and spoil her for anyone else, to leave my mark on her and claim her forever.

I lay on my back, breathing heavily. This was some great sex with Paige. The woman was a dynamo, genetically engineered, bred for sex alone. She lay next to me, on her side, with her head on my chest, hearing my heart thump, wrapping her arm around me while I stroked her hair.

“You are such a beautiful whore,” I said and felt her shiver. Moments later, I felt something warm on my chest. She was crying but not trying to move away. This was the peak of my experience with this girl, so I pushed her on her back and towered above her, looking deep into her eyes and using my thumbs to clear her tears away.

“I wish you were a real person, someone I could love.” Instantly, her tears welled up again and rolled down her cheeks. “Remember when you loved someone so much that it hurt?” Paige’s eyes glazed for a second, and she nodded.

“It felt good, didn’t it?”

“Yes,” Paige whispered. Slowly, I started laying it on thick, reframing her mind like Grr taught me, connecting the vision of love and trust with the image of me. I made her go through her happiest memories, one by one and inserted myself into those stories.

“If you closed your eyes and thought how good it felt to be embraced and loved by your father, you will begin to notice how it feels the same when I hold you this way. Take a deep breath and smell me. It is the same smell. Isn’t it?” Paige didn’t say anything; she just nodded, lost in her memories.

Using a deep, consistent tone, I fed her memories, replacing the most precious ones with me at its core.

“When you look back at the time you were perfectly safe, that deep feeling of trust and security, you will notice that memories somehow faded and lost their vibrance, turning grey over time.” It took me a few hours to take Paige through her emotional journey, leading her imagination and showing her how she could be happy with me and trust me.

It was a despicable concoction of Neurolinguistic programming, manipulation and psychology, pushing Paige into a mental trap, making her visualise me as someone she could love and trust, someone whom she could turn to for protection. Half of me didn’t believe it would work, but a mind is strange. People want to be seduced and hypnotised. They are complicit in being manipulated.

What I used on Paige wasn’t hypnosis the way we learned to think about it. She wanted to go back and relive all those beautiful, soft emotions from a decade ago and feel loved and safe. She wanted to experience the world as that child, before puberty, before anything happened, as a person she would become. We all have that to some extent, even those raised in a loving home with a balanced mother and father and strong spiritual component.

The modern world is an eccentric place, and it is rare to find someone without any psychological issues. Paige had plenty like most gorgeous women I met, maybe not as much as Cassie, but more than most ordinary people.

Little by little, I made Paige journey through all her beautiful moments, inserting myself into her thought process so that whenever she looked back, she would see me standing there, shining brightly in a sparkling rainbow of colour while the original memories faded.

“I am starving,” I said and chuckled. “Would you like something?” Paige almost jumped and squealed. I did what I could, using all the techniques I learned from Grr to lock in her psyche. What was left was “the reset.” I had to pull back and give her mind some time to process and internalise everything, hoping it would at least affect her a little.

“This stuff might not work at once,” Grr said. “You might have to repeat all of it differently to try different modalities.” It made sense. Most people are visual, others respond to the words; for some, it is olfactory, and another is kinaesthetic. This was why I hit everything at once, hoping something would stick and Paige wouldn’t reset.

“Don’t celebrate too early.” Grr’s words of caution echoed inside my head. He was right. I should buy my time, observe and wait. I played with pop psychology before and even watched videos by some random guys who were convinced it worked for seducing women. I doubted that. I even got my master’s practitioner certificate. From my personal experience so far, one needs to put one’s mind into a specific state, similar to hypnosis, be willing to follow along, and not just be compliant but also complicit for it to work.

This is how far I went with Paige and took her on a journey. Most of it wasn’t even remotely related to tactics, but understanding the structure of her emotional states and how they were connected and relied on each other. It wasn’t about rearranging her house of cards, just painting the walls and putting my posters there, like I used to as a kid, Alice Cooper, and all the other musicians I admired.

Even after so many years, when I listened to Pink Floyd or Iron Maiden, I was transported back to the early days, and all my favourite memories greeted me. I was hoping what I did with Paige had the same effect, but I had to wait for her mind to reset and see what stayed so I could repeat it some other time. Rome wasn’t built in a day.

Grr advocated a different approach, rolling in with a bulldozer and knocking everything down, using something akin to emotional blackmail to get the girl hooked.

“Fear works well. You should learn how to use that.” I preferred a more subtle approach. Fear is a powerful emotion, but I didn’t mind investing the time. Besides, I didn’t want a person to be a mirror of what I wanted. I wanted Cassie to be herself around me instead of telling her what I liked. I liked Cassie for who she was. Her uniqueness added to mine. There was clearly the light and the dark side; even using this knowledge was walking a fine line, which I might have crossed with Paige.

It took Paige forty minutes to dress up, put on her makeup, and make her hair. She was stunning and smiled, seeing my eyes. We left the room, and a minute later, she put her hand into mine. That was new. I didn’t ask for it or encourage it in any way. It could have been a fluke, so I just casually went on, but she took it again in the car and rubbed her fingers against mine when looking outside.

People say that eyes are windows into the soul, and I agree with that, but the hands are a dipstick one could use to measure an emotional state. My wife would hold my hand like a cold fish and drop it along the way. If I knew back then what I learned later, I would have saved myself years of failed marriage.

During my journey, I noticed that girls held my hand and rubbed it with their fingers, which meant they were seeking some sort of intimacy, possibly emotional attachment. In most cases, it was completely subconscious, but for a girl to subconsciously seek out a hand was a big one. It implies a deep familiarity with the person, something I didn’t have with Paige. Of course, all of this could be faked. Still, judging by Paige’s facial expression and wondering eyes, her mind was miles away, looking into the world, soaking it in with her senses.

Iqbal took us to the Mall of Emirates, and we walked hand in hand, looking through the shops, all hunger forgotten. I got Paige a few small gifts, a cute bracelet, and a necklace with a small crystal teddy bear. She squealed and kissed my cheek like a child. I could tell she was having a wonderful time.

A waiter got us a nice, romantic seat beside a water feature. I was watching Paige try camel meat for the first time. I didn’t like it much, but she loved the experience, taking at least a dozen photos of the plates to share with her followers.

From the corner of my eyes, I watched her give me measuring glances. She started to say something several times, giving up in the end. I let her be, and the process continued. We had sex already and saw each other naked. There is little mystery between a man and a woman after sex happens. You know she accepted you, and you accepted her. The rest is just nature. I let it take its course, helped and steered by our conversation.

“Jim, I wanted to tell you something,” Paige started. “I am not a whore, you know.” We had a liftoff. Her mind managed to process everything that happened.

“Why did you have sex with me?” She couldn’t explain it, but I could. She planned on stringing me along and playing me for a fool. So far, no man has managed to resist her charms. Guys were simping for her online, sending her money and gifts without anyone getting this far or escalating this fast.

Paige was used to getting what she wanted using her charms. She was confident that after we went for lunch and dinner, she could develop a headache or something. I would understand, thinking we had another day. Of course, this would come to an end, and I would offer her whatever she wanted. I imagined that’s how it worked in her world, but it was only a piece of the puzzle.

“Is it because of your boyfriend?” By the expression on her face, I could tell that I had hit the nail on the head.

“We broke up,” she said. Paige told me the story, but I read between the lines. Her boyfriend was responsible for most of her photography and online presence. He was the fabled “photographer,” and she was the talent. Somehow, he found her in the middle of Iowa and brought her to California, promising the LA.

It turned out Paige got what she wanted, but the price was steep. She and her boyfriend had already broken up a dozen times, but never like this. I made her an offer she couldn’t refuse—money, travel, and the city she always dreamed of. Her boyfriend knew what would happen, but his usual tactics didn’t work this time; the two ended up breaking up again.

All this could be some sort of an accident, a cosmic joke of sorts, but I was willing to bet that Paige provoked that fight so the two would break up, and she could have an excuse for having sex with another guy without being labelled as a cheater. There are layers to everyone, a good Jim, an evil Jim, a confused and hurt Jim, and like that, like onion peels. Who was Paige, really? Who am I? Who is any of us at any given time?

“So what happens when you go back home?” Paige shrugged. I knew the score. She makes peace with her boyfriend, and life continues in another cycle.

“Or, you can stay here.” I saw Paige tilt. She blinked a few times, and then her face returned to the smiling mask she had worn just moments before.

“But how?” That wasn’t a “no.” She was fishing. I didn’t want to spell it out for her. It is good for people to use their brains for a bit.

“Let’s have an ice cream,” I said, waving the waiter over and paying for the meal. I remembered Iqbal told me about this place, a miniature shopping mall in Dubai greens with a make-your-own ice cream by choosing a flavour and adding chocolate, nuts, or whatever, then eating it from a freshly made cone.

It was practically next door, about a minute’s drive, and I ordered hazelnut and chocolate while Paige went for more colourful choices. On the same line, outside was a cafe and a park where they served various fruit smoothies. I chose the “love juice,” a mix of orange and a few other flavours and sat down. The weather was beautiful and hot.

A guy from the shop brought us a Shisha, a water pipe with all sorts of flavoured tobacco, and Paige chose an apple. The man lit it and took a few breaths before passing it on to the young lady with a smile. She had never tried it before. Like anything else in life, new experiences can be addictive.

After a few puffs of apple tobacco and a few sips of juice, Paige seemed more at ease with me and more talkative. She opened up about this and that, and I listened. Paige shared her life with me, and I took mental notes, occasionally asking questions and steering the conversation. She clearly needed to get things off her chest.

“Oh god,” Paige caught herself at one point. “I never told this to anyone.”

“I feel really comfortable around you,” I said.

“Me too. Like we knew each other for a long time.” I had heard this before. I have learned to interpret Paige’s body language. Her eyes would go to the side and up when processing something emotional. The NLP guys call it the “eye accessing cues,” which are unreliable and have little scientific evidence. Still, if you observe someone closely, it becomes easy to watch for them.

I spent months obsessing and gathering knowledge from wherever it came, supported by Dan and any other source I could find. He asked me for a year of my life, and I was committed to giving it, so I focused all my free time and energy on doing this.

What is the point of going to school if not to get the best grades? I used to look forward to all my tests back when I was a student. It wasn’t about competing against someone, not even myself, but rather about assessing my own knowledge and understanding and learning how to learn things.

All this effort was already paying dividends, and all I needed was to master this one last bit, and the rest would be easier. The waiter came, and we left, heading back to the hotel where Paige took a shower and changed into an exquisite evening attire. I showered separately this time to avoid getting into another sexual adventure.

An hour later, we sat in the sky view bar, exquisitely decorated and fun. The waiters brought olives and appetisers with our drinks. I had a Mai Tai, and she had sex on the beach.

The night view of the city was breathtaking, and for half an hour, Paige took pictures. We ate steaks, and they were perfect. Then we talked. I didn’t know if it was the setting, but Paige took my hand into hers and rubbed it. This felt natural to me, and I enjoyed it.

Paige liked to talk, share her opinions, and tell stories from her life. All of it was innocuous, simple enough to entertain without carrying any meaning or relevance. It appeared to me that she was talking more to entertain herself, which was a strange habit and almost a flaw of character, but we all have our quirks when feeling comfortable.

I didn’t try to guide her or influence the flow of her stories, thinking that perhaps this was Paige’s way of processing complex mental context. Never before had I even attempted doing something so heavy-handed to someone. It was Grr’s structure laced with a systematic hard-core influence, almost brainwashing using hard mental pressure, except that I didn’t go negative. Grr liked to play with fear and loss to up the stakes. I didn’t think it was necessary to do that.

We had a perfect day that started a bit rough with sex, and I did it on purpose to remove the most important obstacle. Whatever happened next was just a fun time between two people without pressure. I was showing Paige how good life could be if she chose me, keeping it low-key.

My problem wasn’t getting the girl. I had learned how to do it from Dan. I had a very specific issue with them, and that was this bloody reset. Grr and I had different approaches and different needs in life. Blindly copying the man wouldn’t achieve anything in my case, so I let it go and focused everything I learned on building comfort and trust. I wanted when Paige resets to not return to her usual self and shut me out like Cassie did every time.

Throughout the day, my relationship with Paige grew more comfortable to the point where she had no reservations about me in the evening. She was smiling and giggling like a child when tickled, behaving like a little kid, slowly and surely bringing me in. This was as far as I went with Cassie; the next day, she reset to her usual distant self, and the game would start again as if all we did the day before had evaporated.

It wasn’t the sex and the intimacy, but that connection, the look in Cassie’s eyes and giggles. She would let me in just to purge me in the end from her system. Cassie trusted me enough to let her inner child play with me, and then the next day, it was back to her outer shell.

Paige looked at me this way now, with her open grey eyes and the face of a kid shown a chocolate. She asked me to guess what hand it was in. I just sat there, listening, letting her talk, and she was seducing herself, finding a way through her own obstacles. Paige wanted me to be everything she imagined.

The last time I mentioned her boyfriend, I could see Paige’s eyes dim and her cold exterior come up. The man had some strange hold on her, but not the little girl inside. I doubted she loved him, but there was some sort of weird interplay, some dependency.

If I were a betting man, I would wager that the man used financial dependence to make Paige fall into line and obey, then used the sense of familiarity, enforcing the thoughts of her helplessness, going back to Iowa or becoming a prostitute without him. The devil you know is better than the one you don’t kind of thing. It wouldn’t surprise me. Many men used similar power exchange tactics to keep women in line. Women did the same thing with men, but they used emotional blackmail, like telling the guy, “If you leave me, I’ll kill myself.”

At one moment, Paige looked deeply into my eyes as if she were looking for my soul inside, and our gazes locked. We breathlessly stared at each other for what felt like minutes, and then she squeezed my hand and whispered, “Take me home.”

Only moments later, I was closing the doors to my room when Paige dropped her clothes and stood naked in her high heels in the hallway. My eyes scanned her body like a photographer, and I immediately noticed her thighs were wet. Paige was turned on like insane.

I pulled her hand and took her face in my hands, locking our eyes. We stared at each other for one endless moment, like two marble statues. Her warm breath came out in tiny gasps. Paige was trembling inside.

“When I first met you, I only saw your body and wanted it. Now that I see who you are inside, how you look doesn’t matter. I feel you now.” I lowered my lips to hers, and we kissed. I felt her body tremble and shiver before all her muscles relaxed. All her tension was gone, all her fear and doubt evaporated, and I smiled. This is what Dan called “a reframe.”

Chapter 39 - Quiet before the storm

Paige yawned, stretching her supple body in the sunshine. I loved watching her big natural tits move in concert with her ribs and her muscles. We stayed up late last night, doing the unspeakable acts to each other. It felt like I spilt a pint of sperm inside her, and she took it all.

“Come on, we’ve got to move.” Paige opened her eyes and gave me a big smile, waving me over to bed. She pulled my hand and climbed on top of me, giving me a big, fat kiss before running away, giggling.

I heard the shower run, and I smiled. Paige hasn’t reset yet. It was a small victory, but it made me think about what exactly the thing that did it was. I threw everything I learned from Grr, including the kitchen sink, hoping something would stick. It was a scattershot approach.

All I got was proof that it worked, but it was too coarse-grained to analyse further. I was content with the result, but it only emphasised how far I was from mastering the subject. At least it gave me a range of questions and topics to raise with Grr, hoping to focus his mind on filling in the blanks and explaining what happened.

A delicate floral scent wafted in from the bathroom side. I turned my head, and there she was, standing in the archway, wearing the proverbial emperor’s clothes. Paige was at ease with me, and there were no signs of reset yet. I waved her over, and she jumped on the bed, hugging and kissing me like crazy while I breathed her fresh scent. She smelled so lovely, almost virginal. If I closed my eyes, I would imagine an entirely different type of woman.

“Come, let’s get ready,“ I said, pulling her off the bed. She complained and pouted, spreading her legs wide.

“I am horny,“ she moaned in a husky tone, using the fingers of her hands to pull her pussy lips aside and show me how wet she was inside.

“Have you ever had sex on a beach?” I asked, and Paige shook her head. “If you are a good girl, we could have sex in the desert tonight.” Her eyes popped open like a cartoon character, and in one fast ninja move, Paige was on her feet, getting dressed.

It was quarter past eight, and the car was scheduled to arrive at nine. We had just enough time to get dressed and eat a light breakfast. Paige dressed comfortably and took a small backpack loaded with a change of clothes, a towel, and a pack of wet wipes, but there was no sign of condoms.

“This is so wonderful,“ Paige said, observing a massive buffet breakfast with a variety like she never saw before. “I could stay here all day and try everything.“ I bet she could indeed; the hard part with too much choice is dying of hunger. It makes you a Buridan’s ass.

One of the waiters approached us to save Paige from herself. She had already eaten one full plate and was planning to get another. The car arrived and was waiting outside. I thanked the man and dragged Paige away from the table. She still snatched two ripe red delicious apples as we passed the fruit basket.

It amused me to observe the remarkable transformation of those seemingly untouchable super, hot women once they felt comfortable. The difference was night and day, as if they had reverted to being just happy and giggling children. Perhaps it was because of my age; I could easily be their father. It never really mattered. They say that age is just a number, but I don’t think it is correct. It’s not just a number; rather, the age doesn’t really matter.

People condemn the relationships of older men with younger women, calling it predatory, but when the reverse is the case, and the woman is older, they call it empowering. The key thing I took away from listening to everyone is that it was all a pile of nonsense. The best thing I did was stop watching the news and not participate in social media. They were all regurgitating the same lines anyway, complaining and anathematising stuff they didn’t have access to or never experienced. A famous Czech writer, Karel Čapek, once said, “Just imagine the silence in the world if people talked only about what they knew.”

A large white SUV waited for us with two women wearing abayas at the back.

“Paige, meet Neneh and Dixie,” I said when opening the doors. There was ample space to sit between them, while I opted to sit in front, next to the driver. A brief awkward pause followed the introductions, then Dixie said something and Neneh joined in. Five minutes later, the girls were giggling silly, like they had known each other since kindergarten.

I spaced out a little, watching the city vanish in the distance, and fine sand particles encroach on a lengthy highway. At first, the walled villas replaced the skyscrapers, then the palm farms came, and finally, there was nothing but sand.

Something rose inside me. I have seen many pictures and movies depicting the desert during my lifetime. None of them did justice to the endless ocean of yellow and golden, so peaceful and still, so incredibly quiet, awe-inspiring, almost spiritual in its grandiose presence.

I could see that the view had the same effect on the girls as they quieted, fixing their gaze toward the sands and opening up to something primal inside. Until this moment, I couldn’t understand why one would wish to live in such an environment. There was something almost spiritual about this place; its vastness was so beautiful and captivating. The only word that could aptly describe it was magic.

The driver stopped to deflate the tyres a little so they would have a better grip against the shifting surface. Then we swerved off the road for just a minute before we were lost. Movies and books fail to describe how easy it is to get lost in the desert. We couldn’t have been far from the road, but it vanished. All I could see was the endless ocean of golden sand, like an ocean with massive waves frozen in time, covered by sparkling fairy dust.

“Hold on to something,” the driver instructed before driving over the dunes, up and down like a rollercoaster ride. The girls screamed and giggled, and I was mesmerized. Inside my mind, the memories flickered of how I learned not to fear life. How far have I come? Relish the thought and the experience. The old Jim was gone, and I became someone else, someone who could put his fears aside and live my life right in the moment. It tasted like freedom and smelled like an adventure.

We went up and down for a while, putting the powerful car engines to the test until we stopped at the top of a dune and walked out. Standing on the sand felt strange, so unlike anything I had imagined, certainly not like a beach experience. It was the quality, how it felt in my hand, and how the desert smelled. All of it assaulted my senses at once. It was the difference between living and merely being alive.

Dixie squealed and threw herself to the ground, rolling down the dune, screaming and giggling at the same time. She called to the rest of us from below when she stopped, but nobody wanted to look like her, completely covered in sand.

From the back of the jeep, the driver pulled out a small surfing board and offered it to us. I was contemplating the wisdom of it, but Dixie screamed, “Me, me,” purple in the face, running up to have a try. The rest of us pulled back a little, watching the crazy girl take her medicine, swooshing down the same way she climbed, only to flip and smash her face into another dune.

“This is awesome,” she screamed a few seconds later, just before we started to worry about her health. This caused an avalanche, and all of us tried it. I learned one thing that day: Sand surfing, and I wasn’t compatible with it. At least I could boast of having tried something unique.

I lost track of how often the girls went up and down, laughing and giggling like children, while I watched them leaning against the car. It was a brilliant experience, one of my best memories. All who have visited Dubai and never tried dune bashing have missed something incredible.

The girls were at it for a while, but the dry desert heat wore them out. The sun was setting in the distance, and we all held our breath, watching another of this world’s wonders. Everyone has seen an ocean sunset, but watching one spread across the desert, painting the sands with the blood of stars, took our breath away. It made me feel like I was touched by the finger of God.

We cleaned up as much as possible, and then the driver changed the pace. Instead of a wild up-and-down ride, he drove us slowly from one dune to another. I wondered how the old Bedouins from Arabian Tales learned to navigate this endless place.

Only twenty-some minutes later, we saw an incredible sight: a wooden fence surrounding a recreated traditional settlement with men and women wearing national robes, sitting on pillows on a massive carpet. Women were preparing meals while the men helped. Some offered to guide us around to check out the trinkets.

I was less interested in the tour and more in the culture. I could feel the texture of a vast, colourful carpet under my bare feet while admiring its intricate design, wondering how they made one so large. Never before had I seen a carpet of such size, and I was pretty sure it was handmade.

Everything in this place was designed to stimulate the senses. The gentle difference between stepping on sand versus stepping on a carpet, the scent of exotic spices mixing with the incense, made my mind swirl and my mouth water.

We sat on the cushions and ate our food, watching a belly dancer. It made me wonder what was in the drinks they offered to make her look like she moved akin to some goddess. Even the clinking sound of little brass coins adorning her waist added to the experience. It made me understand that these simple people had an intricate taste. To them, it was part of their history, but to me, all of it looked like a hedonistic celebration of life, where the slight is greatly magnified, and each taste is nurtured.

Time seemed to blur into the distance. At one point, I realized I was smoking a water pipe. The distinct scent of apple mixed with strawberry added to the taste of the evening. I drank something sweet that I thought was coffee, much more flavoured than any I had tried before.

I could tell the girls were having the time of their lives, equally enchanted and mesmerized. This journey would have been more than a success if it had just been for seeing the desert at sunset. All of it combined opened something hidden in me. It taught me the difference between being alive and living.

Late that night, or early in the morning, depending on how you look at it, the car dropped us back at the villa, and we staggered in. None of us had a drop of alcohol to drink, but we were drunk on life and a fantastic experience once in a lifetime.

Somehow, with the willpower I didn’t know we possessed, each took a shower in a separate bathroom, and then we all piled up on one luxurious, oversized bed. Sex was the last thing we thought about, looking through a glass wall at the stars reflecting against the waves. Life has its own little pleasures, and we all discovered one.

Neither of us wanted to talk lest we disturb the memory of a perfect day. Such deep impressions would last us a lifetime. I looked at Paige, and she was committed. She reset all right, going back to her old mental self, but I could read her eyes. I was in, not out. She made all of us a part of her life.

***

Grr chuckled, sipping his early morning shake through a straw, looking at me like a fat cat that had eaten a dove. At that moment, I found him repugnant, playing with a purple straw with his tongue as if suckling on it, acting superior. He was the highest order of asshole, feasting on the story of what I had done with Paige and how I had thrown everything he taught me and more at her, hoping something would stick. And it did. There was something fundamentally wrong with Grr. I could see it in his eyes. It made me wonder if learning those skills from him was pulling me to the dark side.

We were talking about people’s lives, moreover about the vulnerable ones. Was I fooling myself, thinking I could learn the dark arts and use them for good instead of evil? I was Dan’s and Grr’s student, but I was also a student of life. “Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it,“ were the words etched in my mind, straight from the pen of the American philosopher George Santayana. By choosing this road, was I falling into a trap? “Everybody likes to get as much power as circumstances allow, and nobody will vote for a self-denying ordinance.” The words of the prominent British historian and politician Lord Acton warned about that.

He also said, “Power tends to corrupt, and absolute power corrupts absolutely,” and that absolute power demoralizes. Was I already too deep in my trap? Was all of this inevitable? Is this the price one pays for power? I wanted power for my own purposes. Was I deluding myself into believing I would be any different? I hated Grr like my own distorted mirror image. Is this what I would become? Was Grr like me in his previous life?

It was clear that I had to make a choice, and mine was already made. I made it one step at a time, building a grandiose sense of self and lust for power. In the end, I had to commit to the path. As Lord Acton said, “Great men are almost always bad men,” and I had to learn to live with that.

I saw Grr’s eyes follow my internal struggle. A tiny smile in the corner of his lips told me precisely what I suspected. I had already crossed to the dark side, and the only thing that remained were shreds of someone long forgotten, a person I once was, believing in fairy tales. Life is a battle for one’s survival. The world is not a nice place.

“I like what you’ve done there, but we need to discuss making it more effective. I need to teach you how to look for the right signs,” Grr started, casually brushing my internal turmoil aside. “Your feelings are irrelevant,” he dismissed the entire premise when I tried to bring the subject back. Clearly, Grr had no interest in introspection or morality. He called it pointless self-flagellation and a hallmark of weakness.

“Let me show you something,” Grr pulled out his phone and tapped for a few seconds before turning it towards me. It was a nature video of a lion in the middle of the savannah eating a still-live gazelle, screaming in pain. I lifted my hand, turning my head away. It was terribly distressing, and I felt terrible. Grr only laughed, amused by my discomfort with violence.

“You are a hypocrite, Jim,” he said through a chuckle. “I know you love your steak medium rare. Do you know how your beef is farmed? How about the milk you drink in your latte? Do you have any idea how bacon or sausages are made? Leather belts? Shoes? The upholstery of your car?” Grr kept laughing at me, having a good time. He waved the young blonde waitress over and ordered another smoothie and a refill for the coffee. When she came over carrying a tray, Grr winked at her, tipping her a hundred bucks.

“I think you’re pretty,” he said, and the girl blushed. She was in her early twenties and looked innocent. “I’m a rich man,” he said, holding her hand. “I’m prepared to give you a thousand dollars to spend a night with you, and if things work out well, we could make it into something regular.” The girl’s face turned beet red, and she pulled her hand back, almost running back to the bar while Grr and I continued the conversation. He was teaching me to be an asshole.

Grr waved to the waitress some twenty minutes later, signalling for another round. She came over with a tray, and as she served Grr, the girl slipped him a napkin with her number. Grr smiled at her and patted her butt as she turned to leave.

“See, Jim, there are no victims in this life, only power and weakness. You must open your eyes to the real world, Neo,” he said, quoting ‘The Matrix‘ with a chuckle. “Just like with lions, the world is what it is. Some people are wolves, others are cattle. Say moo, Jim, or bite your tongue. You’re a wolf in sheep’s clothing, but you are not fooling anyone. This is your problem, Jim. You reek of incongruence. Abandon this romantic notion that we are all people.”

Dan was right. It was a slippery slope. He warned me of the consequences, which only made me want it more. It taught me a valuable lesson about how the devil negotiates. “Here’s an apple, young man. It contains all the world’s knowledge, but you shouldn’t eat it, the most delicious fruit in the garden. It is forbidden.” What perverse god places the irresistible temptation inside the garden, then tells you to stay away? The same was true with Grr. I wanted the power he had, and just like that, I fell from God’s grace and sunk my teeth into it, the forbidden fruit of power. As Lord Acton once said, “Despotic power is always accompanied by corruption of morality.”

The truth was, I assigned blame to Grr because it was easier than dealing with the dichotomy of my own existence. The Jim I used to be faded at an alarming rate, but particular moral views were difficult to change. Most people had no moral issue hurting others and exploiting the system, living in a world parallel to the one presented on TV and in newspapers. The illusion of a society perpetuated every day hinged on the believers. What happens when you reject it and start using your head for some actual thinking based on numbers and facts? You expose the miracles for cleverly orchestrated tricks delivered by a master prestidigitator.

Grr was right in the end, and I had to take my bitter medicine. Sheep and wolves, the world explained at its very simplest. Just look at the government, running the country in the name of the people. A five-year-old would do better than their piss-poor job. It is all relative, rulers and the ruled, all wrapped in warm fuzzy language lest we make the mistake of telling what we mean to each other. It was all a trap, and I refused to play against a stacked deck of cards. Sheep and wolves in the end, and it’s up to you to choose one or another.

“Jim, Jim,” I heard on the other end. My head was in the clouds since I left Grr to his waitress. I sat in a car, drove to the airport, and waited. If someone asked me how I got there, I would have to make up a story, as I couldn’t remember. Meetings with Grr were always intense. He was breaking my mind the same way he was breaking resistance, worming his way into my head, finding cracks and crevices. The only difference was I knew what he was doing and let it happen.

Isabel recognized me from afar. We never met, but we Skyped online, and she looked impressive, much prettier than what I saw in the picture. Isabel was about five feet nine inches tall with a slim frame and green-grey eyes. Her hair was light brown interspersed with blonde, flowing straight to the small of her back. It was her face and enchanting smile, exposing a row of perfect pearly whites, that captured my attention for a moment before my gaze dropped down, forced by the gravity of two perfect mounds.

The girl went overboard with her breast implants, turning a gorgeous woman you’d want to marry into a woman you’d want to fuck, the nasty way, slapping her tits and choking her neck. Isabel gave me a knowing smile. She knew her effect on men and secretly enjoyed her power over them. That’s why I chose her, a perfect seductress.

I found Izzie on a sugar daddy website, a smoking hot Colombian babe that somehow made her way to Spain. It was no mystery. A woman like this could wrap any man around her little finger. Her mask was perfect, hiding a wall of spear and stone. Someone somewhere did something to this girl to turn her into an ice princess. Lucky for me, she was for sale. I just had to match her number and fly her over. The real question was: could I break her ice and win her over?

Grr explained in a long monologue, “You should drop that NLP bullshit and focus on real skill. It is a crutch, doing you a disservice.” I had to accept that. I was using too much pop psychology, focusing on the wrong things. At the end of the day, I was an IT guy with numbers and maths running my life. Of course, I leaned towards NLP. It gave me a logical structure to approach everything, putting me into a corner and turning me into a social robot processing input and output, request and response. Isabel came here to help me with that, to practice the real skill and shake that monkey off my back.

“This is so beautiful,” Izzie gurgled, wrapping her arms around mine, nibbling on my ear as I drove. This girl was a challenge, I thought to myself. From the moment she landed, she played the game. All that she did and said seemed so smooth and flawless. There was no doubt in my mind that all of it was well rehearsed.

To test my theories, I pulled her hand and placed it on my semi-erect member. Izzie didn’t bat an eyelash, moaning into my ear and massaging my cock through my pants. I let it go like this for a minute before unzipping my trousers. She took the hint and released her safety belt. I was driving at the speed limit a minute later while Izzie bobbed her head. I had to concentrate. She was a virtuoso on a fleshy flute. Ten minutes later, I painted her tonsils with my nut butter, and she swallowed.

I expected Izzie to pull back, but she kept her head in my lap, gently sucking my semen, brushing my cock head with her soft tongue, feasting on the little trickle until all of it was gone, and my cock started to twitch again. She giggled and zipped my trousers back, kissed my cheek, and took a chewing gum.

“Thank you for feeding me, Daddy,” she said, making an innocent face. I knew little about Izzie’s past, but one thing was sure—she was well-trained. It made me think about how powerful men find their way to get what they want. Perhaps Lord Acton was right in saying, “Great men are almost always bad men,” and I believed that.

In some other world, in some other time, a girl like Izzie would be nurtured and loved. Instead, the men in her life revelled in dragging her down, turning her into a sex object, and discarding her when they were done. It was the age; it was the time. We lived to see the liberal days, the pinnacle of democracy. As Lord Acton said, “The common vice of democracy is disregard for morality,” and I was part of the problem. This is why all this fuss with Grr. I knew what I wanted but didn’t like the way I looked.

“It is the programming,” Grr said. “That’s how they keep you in.” We are all told who we are, what to do, and how to act all our lives. It is invisible, finely ingrained to suppress our animal instincts and keep us calm, docile, and obedient, a perfect worker bee and taxpayer. At the end of the day, that’s the only thing that mattered to them: take our money to finance the government while the real power cavorted in their little ascot mansions behind a moss-covered stone fence and seemingly impassable thickets, all of it saying, “stay away.” There are two worlds: the one for the plebs and the one for the elite.

What was first, the chicken or the egg? Did the morally bankrupt gain power, or did the power bankrupt the man? Power corrupts, indeed. Nothing could be a better example of this than Izzie. She was a product of unscrupulous men, and here I was, the last in line, waiting for my time to play, to add another scar to her mental self, to destroy her a little more, to bend her to my will and do what I wanted.

I don’t know if other men get high on that power. I clearly didn’t enjoy it. For me, it was a bitter pill, a medicine, a means to an end. You can’t make an omelette without breaking a few eggs. Izzie was already broken in like a prized horse, and I came to inflict my own damage, but I disliked it. I disliked who I had to become to achieve this.

Grr was wrong. He was right about many things but wrong about the power. I read a lot about Eastern philosophies and came to the conclusion that if you take with one hand, you should give with another. Always leave people better than you found them.

What I was about to do with Izzie could be seen as despicable. No more NLP, no more crutches. To learn this skill, I had to be an asshole, but unlike Grr, I had ulterior motives. I didn’t want a woman to play. I played the long game and chose Izzie for a purpose, not just because she had sexy tits and looked cute. We spoke online for days, vibing, exchanging stories, and learning about each other. I wanted to know everything about Izzie’s life. None of this was a coincidence. Never waste human potential on sex. There is no point; it is a waste. What I would do with Izzie was reprehensible, but it would change her life as much as mine, taking something from her and giving her something of mine.

***

“You did well, Jim,” Grr said with a chuckle a couple of days after I met Izzie. She fit right into my new structure, making best friends with Paige. The two had a lot of similarities, as both of them looked like models—not the skinny, runway ones, but the fancy glamour babes.

“Each to their own, I guess,” he said, referring to how I integrated Izzie into my life. There was no point trying to explain it to Grr. He wouldn’t understand it. I had a plan with hundreds of moving parts, all of it seemingly chaotic but falling into place. It was just how my brain worked. I could envision actions and consequences, like a game of Go or chess.

“Now that you understand how it works, you are ready for the next level.” Over the past couple of days, I made peace with my conscience. Izzie cried, hugged me, and told me about her life. She even thanked me for all that I had done for her and explained that the money was for her family in Colombia. There are always levels for everyone. When she figured out I wouldn’t discard her like everyone else, Izzie broke into a hysterical fit, with all of us hugging her in the end. It is true what they say: Latinas can be passionate.

I spent the entire day talking with Grr about his knowledge, sucking out everything he even suspected. We were coming to the close of our time, and I wanted to extract the tiniest clues. There is no point in learning if you’re not going to be a good student.

Perhaps it was a tad obsessive, but I wanted to master this skill, not just for Cassie but for myself. I had a plan, and it required some aspects of this. Perhaps I was changing, but I needed to learn how to be aggressive. Manipulation came easily to me; I had the best example all my life. Aggressiveness in a non-physical way was my weak side, and I was learning a lot.

The following day was the final exam. I met the girl at the restaurant inside the Burj Al Arab for lunch. She was already in town, travelling with her boyfriend. Sandi and I have been talking for a while. She liked introducing herself as a famous influencer, but her social media pages were sparse. The fan page, on the other hand, was bursting with subscribers.

Sandi was a challenge. She made plenty of cash by showing off her tits, pussy and asshole. To her credit, that’s all she did, and why would she do more? Many men were ready to pay for a direct line to a perfect female specimen. Sandi was five-feet-eight and built like a racehorse without a touch of fat, only skin, meat and bone. I marvelled at her content. The girl certainly spent all her time eating correctly and exercising. The only thing out of perfection with her body was her bulging fake tits, expertly done. Clearly, Sandi had enough money to pay for the best. Talk about investing in yourself.

As much as I loved slim, sexy women, the one thing that captured my attention with Sandi was her beautiful baby face. She was twenty-one, but her face lost none of its girly cuteness despite the magical deep blue eyes and plump rose-red sensual lips for the kisses. I think it was the freckles adorning her cheeks and her perfect button nose, another win for plastic surgery experts.

Sandi was a blonde who liked to play dumb and seductively twirl her hair, letting it fall straight, uneven, covering half of her back. She didn’t fool me. It was the way she looked at me that reflected intelligence. The pictures on her social media showed her everywhere, eating at top restaurants and inside fancy luxury cars. I chose Sandi on purpose. For her, money wasn’t an object. Even the man she dated at the moment was younger than me, better looking, and wealthy beyond my means by the look of his yacht.

I set myself up to fail on purpose by choosing the woman for whom money isn’t a chip to bargain with. In this game, I played with a handicap; I was neither rich nor good enough nor below her standards. It was a theory I developed looking at Cassie. She could have any man by snapping her fingers, yet she chose me for her reason, which meant everything. Unlike what Grr believed, the strength of a man is not skin deep; it goes further.

I had never met a woman like Cassie. She would have never been interested in him. No matter how messed up she was, and no matter his skill. Cassie had her own measure of value, which taught me this secret. I could still adapt what GRR taught me for my purpose. Instead of emphasizing my power or wealth, I could purposely diminish that, laugh at it in a way, asserting my own sense of value, and invade Sandi’s reference frame, forcing her to speak my language.

I expected to fail, but it was a crucial experiment. I had no idea if it would be possible to do something like that. Hence, the NLP and other pop psychology the man avoided. I knew it was all a bunch of nonsense, but how do you describe an electronic calculator to a caveman? All that people did was describe something incomprehensible, focusing on the effect without understanding how it worked, like in astrophysics—we can observe and describe dark energy, but we don’t understand it. I was hoping for the same effect, to learn the essence of something indescribable.

“I know this place. They have a great steak,” Sandi started, and I parried.

“I’ll take your word for it. I prefer that place down the road with Arabic chicken and garlic. It’s cheap and tasty, always packed. I chose this place to impress you. I’m sure you’re used to guys of a much higher calibre than mine.” I delivered my line, watching Sandi’s pupils dilate. Her face froze, and I could almost see the cogs in her head switching into race mode.

“Good going, Jim,” Grr’s voice came from the back of my mind as I saw a crack appear. “All you need to do now is worm yourself in, tapping in the darkness left and right until the next layer.” Grr loved the onion metaphor as it closely resembled how the brain worked.

Sandi gave me a nervous giggle before suggesting we should go to the other place. I tipped the waiter and led Sandy into the car, buying an ice cream for her along the way. Her eyes sparkled. I gently kicked her hand, and the ice cream touched her nose. She flashed an angry look at me, but I laughed, cleaning the ice cream from her face with my finger and having a taste.

“Mmm, tastes like chicken,” she laughed.

“Here, have some more,” she said, rubbing the ice cream against my lips. Before she could react, I pulled her in and gave her a kiss, then pretended to run away. She wanted to jump at me but lost her balance. I caught her in time and carried her to the car.

“You’re not very good at walking, are you?” I said with a smile and a wink, and she pouted. I could see she was upset and about to leave and cancel the date. Upset is better than what she was before. I changed her mind and broke her composure. All of this was unintuitive, but I was likely the only guy who tried that, already different. My old roommate from the university, who was incredibly successful with women, once said, “Women’s idea of romance is chasing guys that didn’t want them.” I laughed then, but I wasn’t laughing anymore. It was all Grr’s knowledge condensed into a single sentence.

The key now was to not push it too far, make Sandi laugh, and then do it again. This stopped looking like a date the moment the ice cream landed on her face. It was unpleasant but different, like sawing a shirt with multicoloured stitches. Sandi’s ego puffed up, wanting to leave, but something else was curious enough to make her want to stay. I guessed it was her intuition combined with intelligence.

“I never cheated on my boyfriend,” Sandi said with a faraway look in her eyes. It was late at night, with the city lights illuminating the high-rise. Her body was covered in sweat despite the air conditioning blowing hard, and her skin broke out in goosebumps wherever I touched it. Purposely, I wet my index finger on Sandi’s tongue, then slid it down her skin, enjoying watching her shiver and tremble.

Halfway through the night, she said, “I never told anyone this, not even my best friend.” It was a sign. I wormed my way deep into her psyche, pulling her to me and pushing her a little so that she wanted to get back into the game. I was new, excited, and safe. As I could have easily been her dad, I was there to capitalize on that. When she took my hand in hers and examined my fingers, I let her do what she liked with a suppressed smile. Sandi examined my hands, comparing them to her father’s or some other significant authority figure. It took me a while to accept that many gorgeous women are broken inside, and I was there to capitalize on that.

Throughout the night, I saw Sandi look at her phone. Each time it vibrated, her face turned darker. Clearly, the man, in the end, knew what was happening. His girl was monkey-branching. The same could happen to me someday, but I was willing to bet it wouldn’t come to that. I used everything Grr told me on Sandi; there was no power, no influence, and certainly no money.

At the end of our dinner, Sandi wanted an ice cream again, for which she paid from her own pocket, then stuffed it onto my nose, giggling like a child. She sat in my lap and licked it off, feeding little pieces into my mouth with her warm tongue while my middle finger massaged her asshole in tiny saliva-covered circles.

“I am going to fuck your ass for that,” I said, and she squealed.

“No! You won’t,” she said with a serious look on her face. Twenty minutes later, as I was pumping my cock into her tiny orifice, she moaned and begged me to do it harder. It turned out that her ass was sensitive, and she loved to be buttfucked.

“No, don’t cum into me,” she squealed, noticing my increased tempo and heavy breathing after flipping her on her back and jackhammering her pussy. “I’m not on the pill.”

“I don’t care,” I said as I grunted and sprayed my sperm, basting her ovaries. The way she looked at me, the way she pulled me in, told me everything. We were past that point. I did something no other guy wanted. With a few powerful blasts, I made her mine. The real question was, would she reset the next day?

It felt like a win, but I cheated just a tiny bit. I didn’t just pick Sandi for her body alone. I studied her, reading her posts between the lines. Everyone has buttons to press, even if they are unaware of them. I was pretty sure that the same approach I used on Sandi would miserably fail on others. It was another lesson to act strategically and plan all my moves. With Dan’s knowledge and various sources, I applied Grr’s process, playing on her dreams, fears, and insecurities. The girl was well off financially, having invested her earnings smartly, only to discover the truth of universally shared advice: money doesn’t buy you happiness.

***

Imagine Sandi’s face when I introduced her to the rest of my women. She froze and pouted, her eyes glazed, and she was chewing her lip like a toddler. This, of course, was part of the process. Neneh jumped in at the right time, taking Sandi’s hand and introducing herself. It took some time for the girls to vibe, and the villa helped.

“This is so amazing,” Sandi exclaimed, commenting on our private beach and pool. Izzie joined her for a swim. She was happily settling in. I had a plan for all these women, not just stroking my ego, living a teenage fantasy of having a harem. It was all part of the plan. It was all coming out just fine.

Later that day, we took a few cabs for a shopping spree. The girls loved the gold souk with dozens of shops selling diamonds and gold. I bought each a tiny necklace, got a fancy watch for myself, and a simple design with little diamonds around it.

We only had a few more nights together before I had to leave and join real life. It was an evening to remember with fine food, wine, and cakes. The girls were doing fine, even the three new friends. They mostly stuck together, finding a lot in common with each other. One was an Instagram prostitute, another was a sugar babe looking for a customer, and the third one sold her explicit videos and pictures, all of them, in their own ways, sex workers.

“Congratulations,” Grr said the next day. He was proud of me for using the techniques he described. I wired the rest of the cash we agreed on to his account and spent the rest of the day covering the tangents while the girls ran around town with my credit card, buying little things here and there. I wasn’t worried. Neneh was a great financial manager.

We parted ways, hopefully forever. I learned much from Grr but didn’t want to see him again. He made me face my dark side, and as thankful as I was for all he had done, I resented him for it. Of course, I projected, but blaming others for our mistakes is always easier. I sought power and knowledge and got what I wanted, but it changed many things, as Dan warned.

I needed these skills for what was to come. Not just to get Cassie but much, much more. Lord Acton said, “Great men are almost always bad men.” Grr helped me discover my inner darkness and helped me force myself to step beyond the line. Being good or bad is a relative concept dependent on the observer. I would need some badness, thick skin, and a tough spine to do what I planned. I wanted Cassie with all my desire, but there was one thing I wanted much more.

Chapter 40 - So it begins

The flight back to London went in the blink of an eye. In many ways, it felt like a trip back in time to an older city and some older culture where locals used paper to wipe their asses. Nothing brings it home clearer than living abroad for a while, stepping outside carefully prepared tourist trails, and peeking behind the curtains. Still, my entire life, I could never imagine myself as anything but a Londoner, and the week in Dubai changed that.

Lamin picked me up with the car as usual, took my suitcase, and rolled it into the back before sitting silently and driving away. There was nothing to say. Lamin and I stayed in touch while I was abroad. He was telling me about his trip from Africa and passing on regards from his family, parents, and aunts.

My mind was far away, focused on my plan. There were too many loose ends to tie up and so little time. The trip to my apartment took only forty minutes, which I barely noticed, as my head was in the cloud, and my entire focus was on the future. I had one chance to play my hand, which had to be perfect.

When I entered, the apartment was empty, and I knew why. The girls had jointly decided to stay at Amy’s place. It was much more spacious and decorated the way they liked it. I was beginning to suspect they also gave me some space. Everyone needs some “me time” to take a deep breath and organise their thoughts.

I took a long shower and changed my clothes. It had been some time since I had been able to take care of myself. With all these women making me their main purpose, it was hard to find time to just sit and let my mind rest. Finding the girls some outlet was another item on my to-do list, a mission of sorts to occupy their minds instead of focusing all their attention on me and ending up disappointed.

I dreaded the moment I checked my messages, postponing it until I got home. Just as I thought, the shit hit the fan, dozens of texts and voicemails, each worse than another, a wretched concoction of sweetness and bile.

It was the worst of humanity, the excrement of a dead relationship. Dan taught me a valuable lesson. A relationship isn’t over while you’re still picking up the phone and checking messages. It only changed its form from bad to worse, and I was there, wishing Tina would die, but I had to deal with it for the sake of my children. I had a plan, and I was working on it. Just a little longer, and all the little blocks would fall into their places.

Predictably, Tina complained about money, interspersed with threats. No matter how much I gave her, it wasn’t enough. It would never be enough for someone with an insatiable appetite and no self-control when it came to spending what she never earned.

I found it hard to discern the truth from lies. Tina was a skilled orator when it came to spinning tales. It turns out something was wrong with her car. The mechanic said someone likely poured sugar into her gasoline tank, and the entire engine would have to be replaced.

The insurance company didn’t want to hear about it, denying the claim outright. They said this wasn’t covered at first, then came up with a range of reasons to reject the claim. Meanwhile, Tina took up a mortgage on an already paid-for house and pissed the money away, landing in debt.

Without a stable personal income, her entire plan was to extort me for more. “It’s for your children,” she said as if they needed so much cash. I gritted my teeth in anger for a few minutes, then shut it all down, promising comeuppance. I planned to change all that, but it would have to wait.

If there was one thing I mastered over time, it would be the ability to deflect and compartmentalise. My psychiatrist taught me the techniques, which I perfected over time, learning how to do it from others. Life is not a domino game, no matter how much it looks like that.

Loud squeals of joy echoed around the place as soon as I entered the corner apartment. Four young women lunged at me, competing with each other to see who could bring me down faster.

I staggered to a large leather sofa and collapsed there in an origami of human flesh. The girls kissed me like crazy, barely allowing me to breathe. They were so excited to see me again after my ten-day holiday in Dubai. Somehow, it seemed like it was longer. What did Albert Einstein say? Time is a relative concept.

The girls dragged me to the dining room, sat me down, and served me some food they jointly made. I almost laughed. While I was away, they decided to save money and cook instead of dining out. I took a bite of homemade macaroni and cheese, which was edible but little more than that. Still, I loved their thoughtfulness.

“How do you like it?” Callie was the first one to ask. She almost puffed up in pride.

“I didn’t know you enjoyed cooking so much.” I deflected. “How about I sign us all up for cooking classes? It could be fun.” Everyone squealed and jumped. I successfully changed the subject and asked for more, but they brought something else with the rice they had prepared.

The girls were grooming me for something. I could see it in their eyes, how they stared at me and analysed as if they had done something wrong and were buttering me up for a big sale. Finally, when I pushed my plate away, feeling stuffed, Rylee took over as the oldest. She recently celebrated her twenty-second birthday.

“Jim, we have to talk about something serious, but I want you to promise you won’t be mad.” I made a serious face, and I wanted to laugh inside. There is nothing the girls could do wrong that would piss me off that much.

That’s when Amy burst out in tears and jumped into my arms, hugging me for dear life.

“I’m sorry, Jim. I’m so sorry.” I looked at Rylee, and she gave me a clear blue stick, showing positive.

“It is all my fault. I didn’t even think about the pill.” Well, I did and never mentioned it, leaving it to the girls to decide how to deal with whatever might happen.

“Please don’t be mad. I am sorry, Jim, but I don’t want to get rid of it.” Somehow, the girls came to the conclusion that since I had two boys and had never talked about children, I wouldn’t want more in the future.

“Amy, Amy, calm down.” She looked up at me with her beautiful blue eyes full of tears. “Do you want to keep your kid?”

“Yes, yes, I do. But I don’t want to lose you.”

“Why would you think that you would lose me if you got pregnant?” Everyone shrugged. It was another one of those moments of miscommunication.

“Amy, listen. Having a child is the greatest responsibility anyone could have, but it is also the greatest gift a woman could give a man. Just for the record, I want to have more children. You are so wonderful and beautiful; I would be a fool not to want a kid from you, another one later, and another, as many as you want to give me, my little angel.” That caused squeals and sobs from everyone as the girls decompressed.

All of them came to hug and kiss me, sobbing as if someone had died. I looked at Tara, and she cried even more as if something terrible had happened. I looked at her with an unspoken question, and she broke down.

“I don’t think I can have children.” Ah, that old chestnut again. After her operation and the follow-ups, doctors confirmed time and again that everything was fine and she should be getting pregnant; she just hadn’t caught it yet.

“I’ll tell you what. We’ll count your fertile days, and we’ll make sure to have a lot of sex. I’m sure the others will help.” All the girls nodded, hugging Tara in support like sisters. “And if after six months you don’t get pregnant, I will take you to the hospital for IVF.” Tara joined the hug. It was easy to understand that after discovering Amy was pregnant, all the girls caught a bit of baby fever.

“Hmm, Master?” Tara always told me that when she tried to emphasise the importance of something, she said it as if the word sounded formal in some way. “Today is my fertile day.” Tara made an innocent face, and I burst into laughter. Soon enough, all the girls were cheering, knowing what would happen.

***

The days turned into a predictable, steady flow, but coming back to work felt weird again. Somehow subconsciously, I said goodbye to the office and was coming there just to wait and pick up my paycheque. I was coming closer to my plan each day, and each day I went to the office, there was another grand in my pocket. I grew to look at my work as the means to finance my budding enterprise.

I would come, get a cup of coffee, sit in my office with my laptop, and busy myself with my projects. For the first time in my life, I was doing precisely as it was worded in my contract—coming and leaving at the exact time and taking exactly thirty minutes for my lunch break, not a moment longer.

Dick and I still haven’t met to discuss the handover. After the stunt I pulled where I accused him of sexual harassment, he was reluctant to meet me in a closed office lest I accuse him of sexual innuendos or something else that could mess up his career. Even the little I’ve done blemished him for the management, so he played his game, trying to find a cause to fire me without taking the blame.

We tap danced to the game of musical chairs where the one left standing, in the end, drops out. It would be me anyway, but I could play this for the next few years until they made me redundant. My job was safe as long as I was the only one who knew how to patch the live system. After their little dog and pony show instigated by Dick’s tactless approach and my heavy-handed response, nobody would challenge me for a while. Still, slowly, over time, they would build their case until the day I was handed an envelope and shown the door. I wasn’t going to let that happen.

Lamin would wait for me in the car after work with Amy inside. Since getting pregnant, she has been going insane. One day, she waited for me in the back seat of my Maybach completely naked and rode me all the way home until I filled her with sperm two times.

“I can’t get any more pregnant than I am,” she said. It made me laugh. She was just a horny teenager with a child growing inside. Deep down, I was ecstatic and in love. This beautiful, wonderful girl would be a mother in no time. It felt like another chance for life, and I was determined to do it right. I often lamented my plans, but being a dad trumped it all. More than anything, I wanted to just be a father, and there would be no mistakes this time.

I thought the American girls would get bored after some time and make their way back to Tampa, but I was wrong. They loved London and their new lifestyle. Since arriving in England, they have had over a hundred thousand new followers. Apparently, travelling around the world and posting fun pictures attracted many people, and the girls were by now experts in doing that. They even hooked up with Paige online and made shoutouts for each other. It was obvious to everyone that life is better when you’re a part of a tribe, and now, with a baby on its way, all the girls were going a little nuts.

Rylee and Callie turned into proper little minxes. They would insist that I take them to all sorts of places, where they would find a way to ask for more sex, not that I complained. Their favourite place to hang out was The Chamber. It was a cosy little bar with a regular clientele. Who’s who of London’s powerful and connected visited there, and the two American girls loved networking above all else.

I haven’t seen Cassie since I arrived. Before I left for Dubai, she used to pop in unannounced, have passionate sex with me, and then disappear for a few days, leaving me feeling confused and a little objectified. The society sent me a bunch of invites, but I was busy with other things, or it was too far. My plan was simple—take Cassie with me and use what I learned from her to stop the reset.

Maybe I deluded myself, thinking it would be better for Cassie to be with me and to stabilise her life, but what did I know about it? She never said anything about herself I could consider a genuine life story. Cassie typically avoided the subjects where she had to reveal something from within herself. There was a clear cut between how she thought and how she acted, and she always kept cards close to her chest. I wanted to believe Cassie trusted me. After all, why would she come to me like this? But you never knew with Cassie. She did what she liked, like a snake slithering into one hole to emerge from another.

“You should move your desk into the movie room,” Pierre said, laughing. The American girls pulled me into it for some action every time we visited. It happened so many times that it became a club joke. “Here goes Jim with his two nymphomaniac girlfriends.” What could I do but laugh at Pierre’s blatant attempt at humour and subtly telling me to cut that shit before I developed a reputation for it?

Someone from the side, looking at my life, could say that it seemed extraordinary. It became ordinary to me. This is how I lived. There are two kinds of people: those who take heads on the challenge of life and those who just submit and do things they are told. In some other life, which faded into history, I could remember a guy who vaguely resembled me as the second kind. Where did it get him? He was dead for all I cared. He died that night when he bought that losing lottery ticket. His loss, my gain. It was my birthday.

I understood it logically; not everyone wanted to be me. Not everyone desired what I did, and not everyone was ready or able to invest as much as me, but to not even try because of some excuse was to surrender to the torrential flood racing through the streets, pulling everything that wasn’t fixed or prepared to swim. There are only two choices in life—swim or surrender to the elements.

Those who sit idly and complain about their life, blaming the system for their misfortunes without taking any action to change their circumstances, are destined for misery. If only there was a magical pill that could solve all their problems. If only one could simply take a pill and instantly lose weight. People live in a world of their own imagination, believing all the nonsense that society feeds them. It’s no wonder that everyone is feeling depressed. Either take action or stop complaining about your life.

I was feeling quite irritated as I flew to Frankfurt. This was my final paid vacation and my only opportunity to take a risk and gamble everything, like playing Russian roulette with five bullets in the chamber and only one empty slot. In American football terms, this was what they call a Hail Mary shot, with the ball in the air as the game clock ran out.

I timed my arrival perfectly, landing at ten in the morning, going through passport control, and taking a taxi ride. By eleven, I was already at the Oasis. They had just opened and welcomed me inside.

“Mr. James Allen?” asked a receptionist. I nodded and handed her my new business card, which displayed the corporate address in New York and my position as CEO and president. She examined it and seemed suitably impressed, then gestured for me to proceed and introduced me to Heinrich, the manager.

Heinrich and I had exchanged lengthy emails for months, but this was our first face-to-face meeting. I could see him sizing me up and smiling. I passed the visual test, and he invited me into his office. He signalled to his secretary to bring us two coffees.

“I must emphasise, this is quite unusual,” he remarked. I smiled and pulled out an envelope containing neatly arranged Euro notes, sliding it across the table.

“Is there any issue I should be aware of?” I asked.

“No, sir. Everything is fine,” he replied, counting the cash. I enjoyed doing business with people like Heinrich. They only cared about the money, which was a sensible approach to running a business. After all, the purpose of a business is to generate profits for shareholders, unlike the stakeholder capitalism that the West was trying to promote, sacrificing short-term gains for long-term nonsense. The West was heading towards disaster with their Hitlerjugend preaching Karl Marx doctrine in their Dr Evil accents about the need to sacrifice for the benefit of those in power. Fortunately, as long as money spoke, all this nonsense remained just that while there were guys like Heinrich around. He stood up from his chair, secured the cash in his safe, and motioned for me to follow him.

“Please come with me, sir,” he said, leading me through a side door. The Oasis was one of the finest FKK clubs in Frankfurt, frequented by some of my company’s management.

FKK stood for Freikörperkultur, which loosely translated to “free body culture,” or in other words, a naturist club. It was a large building on the city outskirts, surrounded by farmland and adorned with gaudy statues of ancient Egyptian and Greek gods on the grass. The compound was enclosed by a ten-foot grey concrete and brick wall. The establishment was exquisitely decorated with marble, leather, gold, and silver and complemented by iridescent lights and neon accents.

The place was a massive fancy spa for men with multiple indoor and outdoor pools, bubble baths, saunas, steam rooms, and plenty of seating, bars, and entertainment. It was where men gathered to socialise, relax, and yield to their decadent urges. It was also filled with sex workers. The girls of all shapes and sizes, handpicked by the management, would come and work there, entertaining their customers at a rate of fifty euros for half an hour or a hundred for an hour.

Since prostitution is perfectly legal in Germany, gorgeous girls from everywhere would come in to work through the weekend, have encounters with up to fifty guys, and then go home to their boyfriends and families with pockets full of cash. This was going to be a memorable weekend, as the club managed to make a deal with a famous American porn star to come and perform and offer autographs for the fans. It would be supplemented by a famous female DJ who played naked, and a well-known French chef would prepare the meals for everyone.

All the tickets were sold out long in advance, and the club would be packed with gorgeous women specifically chosen for the event. Some were even transported from their countries just to participate. It was a big deal, and all the VIP customers were invited.

My deal with Heinrich involved getting the list, so I was unsure who was coming. The club had many small rooms with beds where the customers would take the girls to engage in some vigorous sex. It also had several VIP rooms that cost thousands a night, with massive beds, private bubble baths, a sitting room, and even an office reserved for upper-class customers happy to pay for something better.

Those rooms came with their own girls in a tiered system. The top babes were for VIP clients, while the rest were for everyone else. Everything was ready, and I was excited. The place looked much better than I imagined, judging by the pictures.

By midday, all the girls had arrived, put on their skimpy bikinis, and lined up. Heinrich liked to give a pep talk to everyone to explain the dos and don’ts, reiterate the rules, and remind the girls what was expected of them. The money I paid got me direct access to that.

About a hundred girls were standing in a circle, watching Heinrich as he went through his spiel. I watched the girls, on the other hand, paying attention to the VIP ones. All six of them were stunningly beautiful, and the rest were still cute and sexy but kind of average, except one. I almost missed her, hiding at the back, looking at the floor, trying to make herself look invisible.

“Girls, let me introduce you to Jim. He is our VVIP,” Heinrich said, pointing at me, and all eyes but one pair stared at me. All the girls but one stood to attention, throwing me their best smiles and pushing their breasts up, hoping to land a sale.

“I’ll take these six for the night,” I said, pointing at the VIP girls. Everyone gasped; I had never before witnessed a man get girls like that. The rest of them looked down, about to move away, when I interrupted them.

“And one more.” The girls watched me approach the shy one hiding at the end.

“What is your name?”

“I am Anya,” she said with a very strong Eastern European accent.

“Where are you from?”

“I am from Ukraine.” I took her hand and pulled her towards the others I chose. Heinrich wished me a pleasant night and went his own way while all the girls but the seven I chose stood beside me. It felt awkward to stand there in a pinstripe suit surrounded by almost naked women.

“I’ve got to change into something more comfortable. Let’s go upstairs to the VIP room and order some champagne.” The six girls squealed, but Anya remained quiet. I selected the best room and led the girls there, even though I paid for all the VIP rooms for the night and kept them locked. No matter how hard the other guests tried, those rooms would remain for my exclusive use.

There was a knock at the doors, and the girls let the waiters in. They carried three ice buckets with champagne and a large silver plate with hors d’oeuvres, compliments of the French chef. All of us were hungry, having skipped breakfast, except for Anya, who looked at me with quiet desperation in her eyes. It wouldn’t take a genius to figure out that she didn’t want to be there, participate in any of this, and the last thing she had on her mind was sex.

People don’t get into prostitution for fun. It is usually the last option at the end of the rope. I tried talking to Anya a little, but her English was terrible, almost unintelligible. Anything more than the simplest of sentences was impossible. The girls watched me change before them, hanging my suit into the wardrobe and folding my underwear. All of them were interested in seeing me naked to evaluate a man who would be fucking them. Only Anya looked to the side while her face blushed.

“Would anyone like some chocolate?” Anya’s eyes perked up at recognising the word.

“Me, me,” the chorus of girls responded while I put on and tied the bathrobe.

“I’m going to get some. Why don’t you get rid of those silly clothes and start the bath.” The girls giggled and started pulling the strings of their swimwear while I went down and followed the maze into Heinrich’s office.

“Is everything okay?” he asked with raised eyebrows.

“That Ukrainian girl, Anya. What do you know about her?” Heinrich sat down at his computer and sifted through his emails.

“Not much. Is she a problem?”

“No, all is good. Can you email me what you’ve got on her?” Heinrich nodded, and I made my way into the kitchen.

“I would like to talk with the chef.” A tall, slim man appeared, looking at me with concern.

“I just wanted to meet the master of hors d’oeuvres. They were the best I tried.” Immediately, the man smiled, mumbling something in a mixture of English, German, and French. This wouldn’t work, so I pulled out my phone and used a translator.

“I have a very special party upstairs and am waiting for some very important friends. I will pay you a thousand euros plus any expenses to prepare some special delicacies, anything you want, for us. Impress us with your skill.” The man almost hugged me from the excitement, blurting something out and nodding his head. I bowed to him, then pointed at the food, kissing my fingers to let him know it looked excellent.

By the time I got back, all the girls were naked, sipping champagne from the flutes inside a bubbling hot spa, except for one, Anya, who was still dressed in her black bikini swimsuit, standing like a mushroom, trying to figure out what was happening.

“Here, take this,” I passed a tray with chocolate mousse desserts to her, and she immediately made herself useful and placed it on the table, along with a bowl of ripe strawberries. Once you bribe the chef, everything is permitted. I saw where all of this was going. The girls were having fun, but Anya was panicking. I gave her a champagne flute and filled it to the top, as well as mine. I clinked her glass and made her drink it all, then topped it up again.

While she sipped her drink, I went from girl to girl and refilled their drinks, giving each one a strawberry. The girls cheered, clinking their glasses, while I turned to Anya and took her flute away. She was nicely warm and red on her face. I placed her hand in mine, then pulled her to the bedroom and dropped my bathrobe. Her eyes popped open, and she stood there frozen, staring at me like I was some monster.

I used her disorientation to pull on her bikini strings, and they peeled off and fell like brown autumn leaves. Anya tried to say something. I just grabbed her neck with my hand and pulled her towards me, then kissed her hard, pushing my tongue into her mouth.

It was hard to imagine how Heinrich didn’t see it, perhaps because she kept quiet and her head down. Anya was gorgeous, beyond stunning, but her frown ruined it all, and her posture broadcasted, “Leave me alone,” a strange choice for someone who willingly chose to be a prostitute. Like always, there was much more to the people than meets the eye, especially in women as beautiful as this one.

Anya had a thin and soft frame. Her arms and body were small and perfectly shaped, but she didn’t look like muscles and skin; she looked cuddly and incredibly sensual. Her large natural tits rode high on her chest like two soft and perfect cantaloupe halves with pink nipples peaking in front.

It was enough to make any man gasp and ignore everything else, but that would be a mistake. I could explain how others missed it. I lifted her chin with my index finger, and there she was, the sensual goddess.

Anya’s face was oval with big soulful eyes, a mixture of green and grey, looking almost frightened. She had a perfectly straight, cute button nose, but her lips were naturally thick and kissable. That’s why I kissed her as soon as I had a chance. I saw them for a second and fell in love. I was drawn to those ruby pillows of pleasure, enchanted by their warmth and softness.

This would be enough for any man, but Anya had much more to offer. Her dark, straight chestnut hair fell on her sides, covering the upper halves of her magnificent breasts, making me wish to brush it away and nurse on them. Her skin was smooth and flawless, and her waist reminded me of an hourglass, extending down her cute bubble butt, not too big, not too small, just perfect as it was into her thighs that never met, and her long, smooth, feminine legs.

Anya was a perfect fit for magazine covers, but she also seemed scared and incredibly naive. I didn’t need a guide to tell me she was out of place. Whatever situation put her there must have been dire, but it was too late. I saw her and wanted to make her mine. After Dubai, many things had changed. I looked at the world from a different perspective.

Dan was right; it broke something inside me and put me back in a different way. Grr taught me dangerous knowledge, which was dangerous for me and everyone else. It gave me power no man should have. It reminded me of what Lord Acton said, “Power tends to corrupt, and absolute power corrupts absolutely. Great men are almost always bad men, even when they exercise influence and not authority.” I wondered how bad did hooker game make me as I was about to exercise both with this girl that seemed lost in the trap of her own choice.

If I believed in what Lord Acton said, the inverse would also be true—for one to become a great man, he would have to learn to be bad and exercise his influence and authority for his own benefit. It puts so much into perspective and explains so many things.

Without speaking a word, I pushed Anya onto the bed and kissed her passionately. She tasted delicious, and I could feel my cock throbbing with anticipation of exploring her innermost depths. Anya was scared but aroused, and as we continued to kiss, I could feel her body relax, and her hips rise to meet mine.

As we began to have sex, I noticed how she moaned when I grabbed her neck and squeezed her breasts. Anya liked the rough sex and maybe humiliation despite her body language. At the throes of her orgasm, she only wanted it more, harder, and more brutal, and I gave it to her, letting it all out and pistoning my cock so hard that I heard my balls slap.

She moaned, screamed and squealed, and came again and again. Three orgasms in, and I was ready to blast, so I pulled my cock out, aimed, and spilt my sperm all over her face. Anya closed her eyes and squealed, afraid that I would get some of my sperm into her eyes.

After my orgasm subsided, I lay next to her and gently kissed her on the lips. With an index finger, I scooped the sperm from her face and gently pushed it into Anya’s mouth. She first resisted, but after I forced the first finger inside, she left her mouth open, letting me do what I liked. On the third scoop of sperm, I could feel a shudder. Anya was sucking my finger and rotating her hips at the same time. She was fighting who she was with how she felt and losing the battle.

When I heard her pant, I knew it was time to reel it in, so I slid to the ground, put my knees on the carpet, and buried my face between Anya’s legs. She squealed as I feasted on her clit like a starving toddler. She screamed only a few minutes in, pulling the bedsheets with her fists, but I persisted with a smile. I knew that I had caught a big fish. It was time to reel it in, so I licked, getting Anya primed for the big one, possibly the orgasm of her life.

I walked out of the bedroom naked, leaving Anya crying on the bed. She needed some time to sort out her emotions while I handled the other type of business. All the other girls were sitting on sofas, eating food brought by the chef. Undoubtedly, they were enjoying it. I thought about how little was needed to make people happy.

The girls saw me sit behind a dark mahogany desk and recline in an expensive-looking leather swivel chair. I pulled out the laptop and waved the girls over. All six stood on the other side, like in a principal’s office.

“Let’s talk business,” I started, and the girl’s eyes widened. “I bought you for the night to fuck you as much as I want.” All of them nodded in agreement.

“I want to make an additional deal, and I am willing to pay you a reward double what I spent. You could walk away home with three times as much cash if you help me with what I want.” They all nodded, interested in what I was about to tell them.

For the next twenty minutes, I spoke and explained everything. The girls spent another twenty questioning me about every detail before we had an agreement. To ensure I wasn’t bluffing, I pulled out a bunch of cash from my suitcase and put it on the table, letting them see it before locking it in the safe.

“You do this for me as agreed; this cash is yours, right here.” The girls nodded and smiled like a band of conspirators, getting ready to blow up the House of Parliament—remember, the fifth of November—tonight I would light the bonfire, and we wouldn’t fail.

“Now, who wants a bubble bath?” All the girls stood up with a smile. I walked to the tub and sat in it while one of them switched it on, and I closed my eyes, feeling the jets knead my back muscles. The girls brought drinks and snacks and sat on the other side, chatting lively in their own languages, enjoying the little life they had. All of them worked hard for their money and had dreams and challenges. I wouldn’t add to their misery by treating them differently, except for Anya, of course.

I saw her standing in the bedroom door, looking at us. She put on her bathing suit again to cover herself. Our eyes met, and I waved her over. I offered her a hand and pulled her inside. She sat beside me, and I gave her a cup with a chocolate mousse. Her eyes got big like a kid, and she scarfed it down in a second. That’s when I gave her another and a glass of fresh orange juice. She ate and drank this one slower.

I held her hand below water, and she squeezed it while she drank, looking at the girls chatting and having fun, unable to understand anything they said. It seemed to me that Anya felt closer to me than the others. At least we shared something deeply intimate despite her reluctance. Communication was a huge issue, making it impossible to relate any idea or concept. It was a challenge unlike any before, and I was curious to test the extent of my knowledge.

“I could use a nice blowjob. Which one of you girls gives a good head?” Immediately, all of them jumped to argue whose technique was better. There was no illusion in any of the girls; I paid to fuck them, so they wanted to please me and prove their worth to me and maybe earn some tips later. All except Anya, who remained silent.

I let go of my seat and allowed my body to float up. The girl right in front of me just dove between my legs and started slurping on my cock. I counted a minute, then another girl took over, then another, like that in a circle, each showing off their skill and unique technique. Each girl sucks cock differently, but when you’ve got six of them together competing to see who is better, you really notice how different they are and compare their strategies to please a man with their tongues.

“That’s enough,” I said after several rounds. “I can’t choose which is best because you are all amazing.” That was a good thing to say, and I watched six hookers puff up in pride at being complimented on their oral prowess. I thought this would seem utterly bizarre somewhere in some other universe, but in a place like this, it was normalised.

Anya looked at me with her big eyes as I pulled on her bikini strings and pulled them away, crumpled them in my hand to squeeze water, and then threw them across the room, accidentally hitting the garbage. If I aimed for it, I would have missed it. Anya was about to say something but bit her tongue as I pulled her into my lap and, after wiggling a little, stuck my cock into her pussy and played with her breasts.

One of the girls started saying something; the other laughed. Soon enough, all six of them were busy debating some topic while I leisurely fucked their Ukrainian colleague. I don’t know how much time has passed. I closed my eyes and enjoyed the feel of my cock inside Anya’s pussy. She was safe; all of them were. Heinrich assured me that all the girls working there had up-to-date health certificates and were tested once a month. There was no chance of picking up anything more than a cold from them.

At one moment, I noticed Anya moving independently, grinding her pelvis and gyrating her hips. Her nipples were painfully extended, and when I looked from the side, her eyes were closed. Some girls on the other side were whispering and snickering. Obviously, Anya was too far gone in her own arousal, seeking her own release. I kneaded her fat tits in response, focusing on my own pleasure and the feel of her hot pussy on my cock, milking it.

I could feel Anya’s orgasm from a mile away. Her pussy squeezed and pumped, rippling across my shaft. It was all I could stand, getting lost in my own fantasies, and I let go and released. My cock twitched and blasted, filling her pussy with a generous dose of hot white semen.

Anya moaned quietly and trembled in my arms, impaled on my cock, riding her own orgasm for a minute, and then she slumped. My cock was still semi-hard inside her, and I continued to pump, keeping the blood flow on, knowing from experience that if I kept it on for another ten minutes, I would be hard as steel, ready to fuck again. Thanks to god and science for all the extra testosterone. I made a mental note to thank Kris, my personal trainer, for keeping me fit and my libido in top shape.

The girls watched from the other side. I could tell some were interested. It was quite a sight, watching Anya cum in front of them. She slumped with her back against my chest after her orgasm, and I used all my skills to give her a massage, kneading her neck and shoulders, arms, and breasts until she almost purred. I could see she gave up the idea of not getting fucked all night.

Some twenty minutes later, I was ready to go again. My cock was hard like a steel pipe, but I wanted something else. Anya yelped a little, feeling her pussy suddenly empty again, and before she managed to say something, I was pulling her hand towards the bedroom again.

“Anyone wants to help?” I asked, and all the girls got up and followed. I was going to fuck Anya’s asshole, and the girls would lick her pussy and suck on her tits while vibing her with Hitachi Magic Wand at the same time till I get her to squirt again.

Chapter 41 - Checkmate

My phone bleeped, and I checked the message. The party was starting downstairs, and I got the best view of the house. All the girls were smart enough to take their bikinis off before getting into the bath, except Anya, of course, whose bikini was still wet and cold. She was still dizzy when I pulled her up from the bed, but she quickly turned a lovely shade of red when she realised I would parade her in front of everyone completely naked, unlike the other girls who wore their swimwear.

It must have felt humiliating to be the only fully naked girl in the club. Even the strippers on the stage started with at least some clothes. In a sense, she would be the biggest slut in the place, and the eyes of all the men would be focused on her, imagining fucking her and stuffing her face with their cocks.

Anya pleaded for something and pointed at a trash can with her finger. I only assumed she wanted to put on her wet swimsuit again. I was having none of it. She should have thought about it earlier.

One of the scantily clad waitresses led us to our VIP table with an ice bucket, champagne, and various snacks on a silver serving plate. All eyes were on us. Every guy stared at a man with seven hottest girls in the place, and one of them was completely naked.

Only six empty seats were there, and I made Anya sit in my lap. The lights went down as the volume increased, the strippers walked out on the podium, and the show started. After each dance, the crowd would go wild and clap. Those with small denomination notes would throw them at the girls on stage.

It was great fun, and all my girls enjoyed themselves, looking at the dancers and praising their moves. The strippers were professional, with athletic bodies and sinuous curves. They knew how to arouse and entice with their acrobatic moves. A waitress came over to change our bottle and bring some homemade crackers and black caviar, compliments of the chef.

I saw this sparked Anya’s interest, so I used a small piece to scoop some and put it into her mouth. Anya closed her eyes and chewed with pleasure. I finally found her kryptonite. I wasn’t a great fan of caviar or any food with strong smells except cheese. Different people and different cultures have their own habits. Hers was an interesting and expensive one.

A small piece dropped off and fell on her nipple. I bowed my head and put it into my mouth, then sucked on it. Immediately, Anya’s nipples popped up like pencil erasers. I took a bit more caviar and added it to another. Goodbye, dance routine; we started to attract quite a few onlookers. The girls were dancing on the stage while I was sucking on some nice boobies. It was easy to figure out which was more enjoyable for the onlookers, especially when the young woman closed her eyes and started gyrating.

Anya had very sensitive nipples, and after experiencing multiple orgasms, her entire body was oversensitive to any kind of sexual play. The song ended, and then another one began. I continued sucking on Anya’s breasts and rubbing her clitoris with my hand. The entire situation with the sex club and the onlookers turned her on even more. It was humiliating, but somehow, it pushed her further. Once Anya accepted that she was just a sexual object for men’s pleasure, she let go of any false morality, seeking salvation for her soul in sexuality. I was surprised to see how the mind worked sometimes. I wished I could talk to her, but there was no point in even trying.

Another round of applause and another group of dancers appeared. I noticed Anya started gyrating her hips again, slowly rubbing her pussy against my leg. Instantly, my cock jumped up. The decadence of what she was doing turned me on even more.

I repositioned her slightly and twisted until my cock was pressing against her pussy entrance, feeling her wet and hot cavity gently rubbing against the tip of my member. As the music changed and the strobe lights flashed, Anya dared to move a bit more until, at one moment, she slipped and impaled herself on the entire length of my cock and squeezed.

Goodbye to the strip show or planned entertainment. One-third of the guys were looking the other way as Anya gyrated, rubbing my cock with her pussy muscles while I kneaded her breasts and pulled on her nipples. This went on for a while until I felt my orgasm building again. Anya had three small orgasms before I erupted once more. My cock twitched inside her hot, trembling orifice and released my semen, coating the walls of her pussy with my essence for the third time that day. Thanks to Tara’s relentless training and Amy’s insatiable sex drive, I knew I could go at least three more times, but I was saving myself for later.

Everyone applauded, and the lights came on. Anya stood up, and my cock slipped out, followed by droplets of sperm rolling down her thighs. It caught the attention of many, and I received a pat on the back.

I saw a man in his early fifties at the adjoining VIP table. He was tall with a muscular build and a slight beer belly. I could tell he took care of himself and exercised but also enjoyed the good life. I could understand that. It’s easy to get used to the finer things in life. I raised my champagne glass to him and nodded. He filled his glass and did the same. Another glass of champagne arrived, and I motioned for the man to join us.

“Cheers to your good taste,” the man said, introducing himself as Gunner. We shook hands, and I handed him a champagne flute.

“To better opportunities.”

“I’ll drink to that,” Gunner said, clinking his glass against mine.

“Do I detect an American accent?” Gunner laughed. His accent was unmistakable.

“And you’re English, I presume.”

“Yep, born and raised, a Londoner.”

“To happy coincidences,” the man raised his glass, and I was happy to drink to that. Some people familiar with higher mathematics and chaos theory would say there are no coincidences. If a man could control all of the system’s parameters, everything would be predictable.

The show ended, and the men and the girls milled about, swimming or sunbathing under powerful lamps, trying to pair up and close a deal.

“It is busy tonight, and you’re hogging all the action,” Gunner said, and I laughed.

“You know what they say. Good fortune is what happens when opportunity meets with planning.”

“That’s Thomas Edison.”

“You are right.” I liked Gunner. He was well-spoken, well-mannered, and clearly well-educated. “Let me guess, Berkeley?” the man laughed.

“Only for the undergrad, then Wharton. How about you? Cambridge?”

“Guilty as charged,” I said and refilled his glass. We were making friends fast. “How did you know?”

“It is the smugness. All Cambridge graduates I met were almost as bad as those from Wharton.”

“It takes one to know one.”

“I’ll drink to that.” The drinks were coming, and the girls giggled, watching us spar. Two men, exceptionally well educated, were cracking nuts and enjoying our time. Our conversation veered to travel and personal interests, and we found that we had much in common. It turns out the whorehouses are perfect for making affluent friends, so we talked and laughed.

After some time, a bell rang, and the DJ announced that the food was ready to be served, listing all sorts of delicacies.

“I am a bit peckish; how about you?” Gunner nodded, offering me to join him for dinner.

“I have a better idea. Why don’t you release your companions and join me in the VIP room upstairs? I’ve got the chef making something special. As you can see, I have plenty to go around.” Gunner appraised my girls, and they were a significant upgrade; he nodded and tipped his girls to go away.

“How did you manage to get a VIP room? When I asked, they told me it was impossible. All of them were taken.”

“Simple, I took them all and all the best ladies.” Gunner looked at me with raised eyebrows and big saucer eyes. “Come, let’s have some food and drinks in private, then my ladies could entertain us.” He followed.

Gunner looked around and smiled. It was the best VIP room in the place. Within moments, the waiters arrived carrying trays and plates, setting up a banquet with the chef’s compliments. While people downstairs got pork and chicken, we got lamb, beef, duck, fresh cream soups, and expensive wines. The chef was an epicure who outdid himself.

Gunner sat on one side and ate, with me on another. We raised our glasses to celebrate our newfound friendship and dug in. I especially enjoyed watching Anya eat. She was starved and slurping her soup like it was the last plate in the world, eying the rest like it would disappear at any moment.

We spent our time in pleasant chit-chat, talking about travel, life, cars, and motorcycles. When he heard about my Ducati, he wanted one, and I was jealous when he told me about his brand-new electric Hummer. Gunner has visited Dubai multiple times and had a room at the Burj Al Arab. One thing he didn’t do was have sex in the sand, swearing he would try it the next time.

The meal ended, and the waiters took the plates, pouring a glass of scotch each before leaving us alone. We sipped the aged beverage, enjoying a moment of silence. The girls ate too much and were sleeping it off for a bit, except for Anya, who still munched on her plate. She didn’t let the waiters take it away.

“So, Jim. Tell me what this is all about. I know when I am being buttered.” I laughed. Gunner was exceptionally smart and observant, not that I worked hard to hide it so much.

“I want to talk to you about business, Gunner, or should we drop the pretence and call you Owen Fisher, born and raised in Walnut Creek, California, recruited at twenty-five, and climbing all the way to the CEO title, working at the New York office.” The man laughed. I pulled out a yellow manila folder and handed it to him, then took a sip and watched him go through it.

“This is a shakedown,” he said, looking at all the information inside.

“No, Owen. This is an opportunity.” My private investigator did an incredible job, combing Owen’s life with a fine-tooth comb, finding all the discrepancies, and connecting the dots. There was enough information there to bankrupt the man and put him in jail for at least fifteen years. Going to prison at fifty would be a life sentence, or at least living the rest of his days bummed instead of chilling his bum on the beach like nature intended.

“What are you talking about? If this gets out, I would be screwed.”

“You’re looking at it wrong. I got all of this from a private investigator. If I could get it, someone else could, too. I’m not here to extort you but present an opportunity.”

“What if I refuse?”

“I guess then you’ll have a problem.” I looked into his eyes and smiled. Owen stared at me for almost a minute, then burst out in laughter.

“You have some balls, Jim. I’ll give you that.”

“Remember those Godfather movies. I am here to give you an offer so good, you can’t refuse it.” Owen started laughing so hard that he almost fell from the chair. The situation was so funny that I had to join in. He got me, and I got him; we were in it together. I reached out for the scotch bottle and filled our glasses. We took a few sips, staring at each other, then burst into laughter again. I don’t even know what was funny, but the situation was ridiculous. Two men in white bathrobes, sitting sprawled on sofas next to a bunch of hookers blackmailing each other. If Dante were alive, he’d call it a divine comedy and probably write a book about it.

“Alright, then, let’s have it. What’s the deal?”

“I know you’re currently getting two per cent of the contract value as a bribe, paid into your offshore account. Unfortunately, whoever set it up for you is an amateur, and I was able to trace it. If I could do it, so can the feds. Money laundering will get you a prison sentence, if nothing else. The deal I am offering is five per cent, and when you get the cash, it will be untraceable.”

Owen instantly stopped smiling. We were not threatening anymore but talking business. He was the money guy and knew the ins and outs of the corporate world, and the offer I made was better than any he ever had on the table. He would stand to make millions on top of the millions he already made. I handed him another manila folder containing the details of the proposal with complete financial projections and a printout of all the numbers, as well as the maths and the formulas in appendices that were used to get there.

I watched Anya go catatonic and fall asleep with her head on the table. She ate so much food that she passed out. It was funny, and I wanted to laugh. Owen was lost in the papers, and all thoughts of sex and fun vanished. This was business, and I was right. The offer was too good for him to pass on. He sipped his scotch, flipped through the papers, looked at the numbers, and flipped back. Finally, he closed the folder and poured some more scotch.

“I can’t just make this happen. The board won’t go for it. There is too much risk.” He was right. No sane board member would vote for that. The risk was unpalatable, and I knew he would say that.

“What if the board had no choice?” He looked at me, and I took the final manila folder and passed it on to him. It was the thickest one, over a hundred pages. It contained a complete risk assessment document with proposed mitigations and associated numbers.

“You’ve been lied to, Owen. Your supplier has you by the balls because they are bribing you. They made sure there was a paper trail, leading to third parties involved. If this blows up, it will be your ass, and they will just get a slap on the wrist.” I could see the recognition dawn in his eyes, and his face looked darker with every page he read.

“This can’t be true.”

“Your contract allows for independent audits. You never did one because of the bribes, but I guarantee it: Six months from now, your company will be at least two billion dollars out of pocket, and you will be out of a job.” He believed me now. I watched him flip through the pages in rising panic, then put it all down and look into my eyes.

“What can I do?”

“This is where the opportunity comes in. Unlike with your old partners, it is just you and me here. We are in it together. I need you, and you need me. I have a plan.” He got me at last. This wasn’t a shakedown but a real opportunity that would save his ass and make him rich. It could be the final push for him before he retired. The money he would make could ensure that.

“I need some coffee,” he said, and I called the waitress. Ten minutes later, she brought us a pot with cups and disappeared. We sipped the sweet nectar of sobriety for over an hour before we shook hands and agreed to work together. Of course, I could use all this material I found to squeeze Owen and force him to dance the way I liked, but I preferred a friend to an enemy. There was enough money for everyone, and there was no need for greed.

“You played a perfect game,” Owen said, shaking my hand again. I gave him the key to another VIP room and smiled.

“Go, take your girls and have some fun. You dodged a bullet and made money in the process. That deserves a celebration.”

“Which ones will you give me?” He pointed at the six girls on the bed.

“They are all for you, partner. All of this is for you. I’ll just keep this one. She kind of grew on me.” I pointed at Anya, who regained consciousness and stared at us with her big eyes, watching me point my finger at her. She flinched, thinking I would make her fuck my new friend, but Owen just shook her hand and walked out, calling the six to follow.

This weekend trip cost me a bomb and put a severe dent in my already strained savings, but I achieved what I set out to do, and I was in business. I poured myself another cup of coffee cup, took it to the hot bath, and submerged myself inside, switching on the bubbles. I could feel the stress coming out of my muscles. This was the hardest game I played, with everything at stake. Inside my head, I thanked Dan, Grr, and everyone who helped me shape myself into a man who could pull this off. There was no way for the old Jim to come off even a little believable. Owen would see through him, and the deal would never happen.

Anya watched me from the other side of the room. For a moment, I forgot about her, celebrating the win for myself and alone. This was the culmination of endless planning, and it went perfectly. It liberated me and gave a new meaning to my life. The rest would be just going through the motions and pushing it to the end.

I saw Anya get up and walk towards me, then enter the bath. She wrapped her arms around my neck and her legs around my waist, and our eyes locked. No words were necessary; she understood everything inside my eyes, and then we kissed for the very first time.

Chapter 42 - Power of one

The club closed at six, and they kicked everyone out except me. I had a long night, and they let me sleep it off. After all, I spent enough cash to buy me some preferential treatment. I woke up sometime after nine, feeling starved with Anya lying on top of me, looking literally and metaphorically fucked.

When she joined me in the tub last night, we had sex in the bubbling water one more time, then I took her to bed and ate her pussy again before fucking her two more times, cumming inside her pussy and asshole. It must have been close to four in the morning when we finally collapsed, sweaty and sexually drained. I gave it my best, everything I had, and took it all out on the young Ukrainian woman.

She stirred and jumped a little, sensing my move. The night had ended, and it was a bright new day outside. The fantasy was over, and she needed to go home. I could see the sadness on her face. I cupped it with my hand, and her eyes fluttered before she closed them. We were from two different worlds, and she knew that. I could have used the translator app to communicate, but there was nothing to say.

Anya watched me jump into the shower and lather my skin. Ten minutes later, I was out, feeling refreshed after cold water. She went in next, and I made a phone call while putting on clothes. Five minutes later, one of the assistants brought up a small sports bag containing all of Anya’s clothes, including her wallet and documents. She had twenty Euros in it and a folded hundred Grivnas note, some Ukrainian money, which she probably kept there for luck.

I checked her passport, which was brand new, and she had only one stamp when she entered Poland. The sound of feet tapping on marble came from behind me, and I turned to see Anya wrapped in a towel and drying her hair with another. Her eyes widened when she recognised her bag, but she focused on her passport, and I read it out.

“Anna Tkachenko, nineteen years old.” I could see her eyes water, and then she almost jumped when I closed her passport and put it into my pocket. I gave her a stern look, and she calmed down; then, I looked through her bag again and threw it at her. She got the message and started putting on her clothes.

When Anya turned to me, I had a small stack of cash in my hand. I handed it over to her, and she counted, mumbling “Dyakuyu,” and almost curtsied. I could see from the look in her eyes how much it meant to her. I reached into my pocket and pulled out a stack double that size, then counted the same amount of notes on the table and another. Anya watched me put them together and wave them before her, studying her reaction. She couldn’t take her eyes off the money. I mimicked one and two with my fingers, looking directly into her eyes and willing her to understand.

Anya quickly nodded in agreement and watched me pocket the cash. I offered her an arm, and she took it before we left the room together. She was an intelligent girl. I paid her for the night, and without words, I made a deal with her for the next two days. Judging by her body language, this was the most money she had ever made.

The cleaners were all over the place, preparing it for another night. Heinrich was long gone, but the administrator stayed. She thanked me for the visit and said a taxi awaited me outside.

“Take me to the centre, please.” The driver nodded, put the car into drive, and we were off, sitting at the back. Anya sought out my hand and entwined her fingers with mine. Her palms were sweaty. I could tell she was nervous. She probably had never done anything like this before. Last night, I had plenty of time to read through all the information Heinrich emailed me. There wasn’t much, but what I gathered was that Anya flew right in from Warsaw, and that was only two days ago, and her passport was little more than a week old.

Anya wore simple distressed blue jeans and old sports shoes, a white T-shirt with a pink blouse on top, covered by a cheap denim jacket. It looked at least a year old, maybe more, and regularly washed. Something told me those were her best clothes, and the keys in her bag had a small metal plate attached with a logo and the name of a cheap hostel. I’ve seen those and the lockers they had. It would be impossible to keep anything bigger than hand luggage inside. The security was virtually nonexistent, which would explain why she carried her documents everywhere, including what I assumed was her Ukrainian identity card, written in Cyrillic, which I couldn’t read.

The taxi driver dropped us at a mall in the centre; I paid for the ride and tipped him well. Anya watched me with her big eyes as I took her hand and pulled her inside. We started with the shoes, and I got her a brand-new pair. I could see her eyes water when I paid. The salesperson offered us a box with her old shoes, but I told her to throw them away.

Anya was a little surprised, but I shrugged and pulled her hand. Next was a fancy lingerie store; buying panties was easy, but it was hard to find a bra her size. Her massive mammaries refused to be contained. She actually giggled when none of the bras fit. We went from one store to another until I found one that carried the size for voluptuous women and bought her a matching purple lace bra and panties. They looked amazing on her and fit her great.

Everything got much easier after that. I bought Anya a lovely new pair of Armani jeans and a T-shirt, a beautiful multicoloured sweater made with Kashmir wool, a Versace leather jacket, and a Burberry handbag. I topped it all with nice Bulgari sunglasses before I took her to a makeup section and got her a Mac cosmetics set, asking the salesperson to apply it first. Finally, I let Anya go to the salon and get her nails done.

“Ta, ta, ta, don’t cry now. You’ll ruin it all.” I took a paper tissue and dabbed her eyes. When Anya saw herself in a mirror, all dressed up like that, she burst into tears, and her chin shook uncontrollably. Her eyes looked at me like she saw God. I pulled her in and planted a big fat kiss on her perfectly made-up lips, which tasted of peach.

“Come, let’s have breakfast.” Anya clung to my hand like a limpet as I led her out of the mall onto a main street. We walked around briefly, and she only held my arm tighter. When we stopped, she whispered, “Thank you,” and we kissed again. Dressed like this, Anya was turning heads. She looked like an exclusive fashion accessory to an older, wealthy man. I saw it, and she saw it. Anyone bothering to look saw it as well.

We sat in a small café down the street, and I ordered scrambled eggs with a German sausage and sourdough bread. Anya opted for scones and honey with a healthy serving of coffee and milk. It was kind of funny watching the two of us sitting in silence, glancing into each other’s eyes with smiles, bursting to communicate, unable to cross the language barrier. It was like a game where we let the actions speak instead of words.

While Anya was in the toilet, I called the concierge to make some arrangements, then called my lawyer in the US and asked him to find someone to sort things out for me in the UK. I just put the phone down when I saw Anya walk out. She looked like a million bucks, walking like a princess, turning the heads of everyone she passed. Instead of her chair, she sat in my lap. I’ve never seen anyone happier than Anya for being alive.

The waiter came over, responding to my hand signals. I paid for the food and bought Anya a pretzel. She giggled like a kid and stuffed it into my mouth, so I took a bite, and she nibbled as we walked. Anya trusted me now and followed wherever I walked. We had so much sex last night, and I made a point of getting rid of the six girls, choosing Anya instead of them. At the end of our marathon fucking, Anya collapsed. I doubt anyone ever fucked her so thoroughly in her life. Towards the final moments, she was only able to squeal as I jackhammered my cock into her asshole. I destroyed her body, taking every ounce of my pleasure with no regard for how she felt. I paid for her body and took what I wanted.

There was nothing more a man could want from a woman sexually, and I was sure Anya understood that. I left no doubt in her mind that she wasn’t the first or the last one to go through this, but after the night was over and I was supposed to leave, I took her with me and offered to pay her the same for two more days. Instead of climbing on top of her again, I bought her clothes and took her on a date. I made it easy to understand that I was playing a long game, and Anya was interested, becoming complicit when she saw herself in the mirror. She looked like a princess.

Anya would point at something and smile, then I would point at something else, and she would giggle. We were developing our own language. I felt good, and she felt great. After some time, we reached a large clearing with a train station on the other end. I led her across the road, and we were there.

She watched with curiosity as I bought train tickets. It was her first German train ride, and she was excited to see new things everywhere. As long as she held on to me tight, Anya felt safe. Since last night, I have built enough trust for her to follow me without fear.

The train stopped, and we exited. I led Anya through a maze of corridors until she realised we were at the airport. She got a little nervous, and I could tell by how tight she held onto me and the sweat of her palms. I pulled her relentlessly forward at a leisurely pace until we reached the security control and pushed her through the scanners. On the other side, she quickly attached to my arm, looking at me with some fear in her wide-open blue eyes. I smiled and kissed her, stroking her hair. That seemed to calm her down for a minute.

We strolled down the corridors until we hit the duty-free shops. I tried several perfumes on her until I found the one I liked, paid for it, and gave it to her with a small pack of Toblerone. It was the right move, and the chocolate helped. By the time we reached Starbucks and ordered two coffees, Anya was calm and curious again.

I led her to the gate, and we sat there. She started to ask some questions, but I put my finger on her lips, and then we kissed. This shut her up for some time, so we sipped our coffee and stared at each other. Then, I winked with a smile, and she burst into laughter. It was all a game, and she felt happy and safe with me. I didn’t do anything to harm her in any way. No words could explain that. People say actions speak louder than words, so I wanted to try that instead.

The airline staff called for boarding and invited the first-class passengers. There were only Anya and me, and two businessmen. I took her hand, and we walked towards the plane. They would check for a visa, but our tickets were connecting flights to Warsaw with a stopover, so they said nothing and let us through.

I gave Anya the window seat while I took the aisle. I could feel her heartbeat like a drum. She was scared but excited. A strange man who paid to have sex with her the entire night put her on a plane, taking her somewhere. It was like a modern reenactment of one of the Arabian tales. The stewardess brought us some drinks, and we waited for the rest of the passengers to board. In no time, the doors closed, and the plane rolled to the runway.

Anya squeezed my hand tight as the plane took off. Her eyes were glued to the window. She didn’t want to miss a moment, soaking in the beginning of her grand adventure. I theorised that a girl forced into prostitution was broken enough and hit the bottom hard. It was clearly her first day as a prostitute, and she found it hard to reconcile dozens of men climbing on top of her and using her as a sex object with everything she believed. Anya was clearly desperate, trying to survive and probably save someone. She had no scars or stretch marks on her body, so I assumed it was not a child but most likely a sibling or a parent.

The money I gave her meant survival for whoever, and the two times that was all that much better. Besides, how much worse could it get? I already had sex with her seven ways to Sunday. Logic would dictate that it is morally better to have sex with one man a hundred times than with a hundred men one time each. I couldn’t guess her mental processes, but I kept throwing curveballs at Anya to keep her on her toes and unbalanced so she couldn’t settle into one way of thinking until I got her to where I wanted. Grr would be proud of me. It was a manipulation of the first order.

I was sure some people would be disgusted with me and call me a monster, but I was long past such criticism. It wouldn’t affect me anymore. Does the end justify the means? It did in my world. Dan was right in the end. The hooker game changes you from the inside. I wasn’t as jaded as Grr, but my time in Dubai somehow redefined me. All that I learned, guided by Grr, pushed me to another level. The man who returned to the UK wasn’t the same as the one who left, or maybe I was always that person, and finally, I got into my own. Who would have guessed that my true nature was ruthless?

The plane landed and rolled to the gate. The jetway extended, and we stepped into the hallway. Anya followed me in step, squeezing my arm so hard that her fingers turned white. Her palms were sweaty, and she stayed close to me. Clearly, Anya was petrified. She squealed a little when she recognised little British flags everywhere.

“England?” She mumbled, looking at me with those beautiful big blue eyes.

“Yes. Home.” No power on earth or heaven could stop her tears as they rolled from the sides, ruining her makeup forever. She hugged me so tight and trembled that I almost shook with her from the vibration. Anya knew she couldn’t be there. The UK requires visas for Ukrainian citizens, so she braced herself for the worst.

“Hey, look at me.” I pulled her chin and stared into her eyes. “You are mine.” I showed her the translation on my phone. Her eyes went from the text to my eyes and back. Those three simple words were loaded. Anya placed her hand on her heart, then pointed at me, and I nodded. “Yes. You are mine.” That’s when she lost her strength and fell to her knees, wrapping her arms around my legs and bawling.

“Are you okay?” One airport staff came, noticing the commotion, and offered help.

“No, we need your help. I am a British citizen. My lawyer is outside with all my documents. This is my girlfriend, Anna Tkachenko. Here is her passport. She is a refugee, and I am her sponsor.” The kind lady’s eyes grew big, and she called on her radio. Within minutes, a whole bunch of staff gathered. Anya was in shock and wouldn’t get up, so I lifted her in my arms and carried her surrounded by the airport staff, security, and a person rolling a wheelchair.

Getting into the country is not easy, especially as I didn’t register for sponsorship in advance. All the staff showed incredible kindness to a distressed girl, offering her water. She just held on to me and cried. They led us to an office, and ten minutes later, a translator appeared, a woman in her late thirties. She spoke to Anya, and the poor girl cried, holding onto me and telling the translator everything.

Meanwhile, my lawyer got through and presented them with my national insurance number, tax records, and all sorts of other documents. Anya was clearly endangered and refused to leave my side even for a minute. They held us there for over four hours with a range of people going in and out, making me sign all sorts of documents, place a bond into a bank account, and all kinds of procedures until they produced a bunch of papers in English and Ukrainian and made Anya read through it and sign, then we were done.

“Welcome to the United Kingdom,” a kind policewoman said, holding Anya’s hand in support. She burst into tears again, and I hugged her before she took my hand again. It was an emotional moment. The translator spent some time with me, explaining what exactly happened.

“She was forced into prostitution by her ex-boyfriend who threatened her family.” It was sick and escalating. Anya would have to send home the money, most of which her ex-boyfriend would keep. She told the translator everything, her name, address, who’s who, and where.

“It is clearly unsafe for the family to remain in Ukraine.” The senior policeman listening to the conversation added.

“So what happens next?”

“We already started the case and would liaise with Interpol and the Ukrainian embassy.”

“Why don’t we just bring her family over? I’ll pay for the transport if you can liaise with their police.” This got the man thinking and promised to consider it an option. There was a procedure they had to follow.

Lamin waited with the car outside. By that time, Anya managed to calm down a little, just enough to get into another shock. She was welcomed by a uniformed driver who welcomed her to the top-of-the-range Maybach limousine. Her eyes were everywhere. Still, Anya was unwilling to let go of my hand. The city grew bigger with tall skyscrapers and offices as we approached Westminster, driving slowly so Anya could absorb everything.

“Come on,” I called when the car finally stopped. Anya took my hand and looked around, getting her first impressions of London. I took her to the building entrance, and a short elevator ride later, I showed her my home. It was a small, cosy one-bedroom apartment, spotless and meticulously organised, thanks to Tara.

I took my clothes off and hung them, throwing the underwear into an empty laundry basket before walking into the shower to wash away hours of travel. Anya watched me for a bit, then caught her reflection in a tall mirror and preened. This was much better than she imagined, and she spent a few minutes exploring the place, checking the empty fridge, and putting her nose everywhere.

By the time she was done exploring, I was already on the bed, lying on my back naked. Anya smiled at me, took her clothes off, showered, and washed her hair. There was no doubt another woman lived in this place, given the amount of hair products neatly packed in the shower.

My eyes popped open, feeling a soft body lay next to me. Anya hugged me from the side, kissed my cheek, then wrapped herself around me, and we fell asleep. Neither of us slept enough last night, and after the border ordeal, we only wanted to take a nap.

The loud noise of closing doors, followed by giggles, made me jump. Anya was in a panic, trying to cover herself up. Four girls barged into the bedroom, carrying a pile of paper bags. They dropped their shoes and jumped on the bed, laughing and squealing, pointing at the poor, confused girl and me.

While stuck at immigration, I texted the girls, explaining the situation and asking them to go shopping. Anya had nothing except the clothes and an old Samsung phone with a broken screen. The girls took it upon themselves to recreate Anya’s life from scratch. I gave them her exact measurements, and they went on a small shopping spree to buy her some clothes.

It took Anya a few moments to realise that the girls weren’t shocked or offended by her nakedness. Amy pulled out a box with a pair of Jimmy Choo high heel shoes. They looked exquisite. She passed the box to Anya and had her look at them. The poor girl didn’t realise what was happening while I leaned against the headboard, watching the show.

“This is for you,” Amy said, gesticulating heavily.

“What? For me?” Anya couldn’t believe what she was hearing, and then suddenly, it clicked. The shoes were her size, and the girls pulled out exquisite bras that wouldn’t fit any of them.

“Here come the waterworks,” I said, and like on cue, Anya burst into tears, covering her eyes with a quilt. I could only imagine the humiliation and pain she went through in her life to be forced into prostitution by a man holding her family hostage.

The girls hugged the poor crying girl and joined her with tears and sniffles, and then, five minutes later, everyone was laughing. I loved watching Anya’s blue eyes. They were so expressive. The girls dragged the naked girl onto the centre of the bed and passed on bags and boxes to her, so she unpacked them and found another gift inside. It was like all the Christmases came together at once. Some boxes contained shoes, others socks, bras, or panties. It wasn’t enough for a complete wardrobe, but Anya could go cycling her clothes for a month.

It felt to me like some sort of a grown-up Barbie doll thing. The girls dressed Anya up, brought her to the mirror, undressed her, and put something else on. She just accepted it, with big eyes and a smile, feeling like a princess, pampered in a castle.

Eventually, the girls exhausted themselves and fell flat on their backs over the bed. Anya came up to me and hugged me so tight I thought I would need an osteopath to fix my neck.

“Thank you. Oh, thank you,” Anya went on, kissing me repeatedly like someone who had just had her life saved.

“Is anyone hungry?” I asked, and all the girls squealed in happiness. “Let’s get dressed and show Anya some nice places.” Everyone was now up, taking all the clothes and pulling Anya away into Amy’s place, where the girls would freshen up and change their clothes.

I thought about everything that had happened and smiled, considering buying a bus if I continued this way. The Maybach was registered to transport five people, not seven. We were approaching a crowd better suited for a people carrier. I laughed. To be surrounded by gorgeous women, all wanting to please me and asking for sex, was a nice problem to have. I took a deep breath and closed my eyes, reminiscing about how my life had changed.

***

There was little to do other than wait. I went to the office and came back home. Life went back to its usual routine, with one little change. The American girls finally decided to go home. They had too many things to do for their studies, and they couldn’t afford being away for much longer, resulting in a very emotional moment.

For the last two days of their stay, Rylee and Callie spent the night sleeping in my bed, hugging me and kissing me with a lot of sex. The two were insatiable, begging me to bring them over again. We spent our last weekend practically in bed, fucking until everything hurt. I filled the girls with so much sperm that I imagined they would be dripping it for a week after. If there was one thing I had in abundance, it was sex.

Tara and Amy got a little depressed when the Americans left. They had built such a deep bond that it felt like they were losing sisters. Luckily, Anya was there, and the two focused all their efforts on teaching her English. With nothing else to do, her progress was staggering. Even after a week, we could talk about some basics. Anya’s pronunciation was frighteningly bad, but I could understand what she said, and she understood when I spoke slower. We could communicate a little.

Every day, I would go to the office, click and clack on my computer, and waste my time waiting for some news from Owen. Nothing much came. He planned a meeting with the board of directors and promised to keep me informed. Meanwhile, I focused on spending plenty of time with my Indian delivery partner friends, architects, software developers, and managers, organising meetings and sharing knowledge with them. It helped pass the time.

Lamin would pick me up with the car and Amy inside every day after work. After the first time she tried, Amy decided the danger of being caught turned her on, so more often than not, she would ride completely naked at the back. Panties became a thing of the past, and Amy never wore them. A young, soon-to-be mother was living the dream, entertaining the hundreds of thousands of her followers with the news of her pregnancy. It turns out there was a massive market for cute pregnant blondes with DDLG fetish, and judging by the comments, her fans couldn’t wait for her belly to grow big.

Rylee and Callie collaborated with Amy and Paige in Dubai, blasting cross-promotions like crazy and exchanging pictures and videos. Paige got everyone hooked on TikTok and YouTube. All the girls planned a massive collaboration when they met the next time. The American girls were already pestering me to take them to Dubai to meet Neneh, Dixie, and Paige, all three of whom were walking around the place wearing abayas and niqabs like local women, except that underneath, they were naked.

It looked like my life was finally coming to some level of stability, with all my women finding themselves within the group. Even Anya, the newest member of my tribe, seems to have integrated herself with the rest. She cried all night in my arms, telling me her mother called and they were safe. Anya kept kissing me and thanking me until her lips were chafed.

Her mom told her that some men in a military SUV came and dragged her ex-boyfriend right out of his house, and they never saw him again. The next day, a lawyer visited her mother to give her an envelope with keys and a bunch of papers for a three-bedroom apartment in Bila Cerkva, a quiet little town outside Kyiv, giving her five thousand dollars to organise the move.

“Nobody knows what happened to him,” Anya said in her growing English vocabulary, talking about her ex-boyfriend. Whoever she asked didn’t know where he was, what happened to him, or whether he would resurface again to get revenge.

“You will never see him again,” I said, looking into her eyes and winking. She shuddered, then buried her head into my chest and cried. There were plenty of rich and connected Ukrainian oligarchs in London, and some of them were members of The Chamber. I happened to know one, and we got to talking. He knew a guy who knew another guy who ran a business supplying the Ukrainian military.

The men that came to collect the asshole were from the military office. They drafted the guy and fast-tracked him to the front after tattooing his body with swastikas and the insignia of the Azov battalion before unloading him inside a minefield right at the front line and sending him to attack the Russians with a water pistol superglued to his hand, blowing bubbles. Nobody heard of him since. Anya didn’t need the details. She’s been through enough, but she got the message. The man was never coming back to haunt her again.

Since that day, Anya has looked at me like I am a god. She even joined Amy on her trips to my office to pick me up, at first wearing frilly clothes, then copying Amy and welcoming me butt naked. If I thought having an executive Maybach meeting me in front of the office with one naked teenager inside, having two of them was just making a ridiculous statement. Even I had to admit it was incredible. One time, I opened the car doors in front of my Indian colleagues, and they almost choked, having a quick glimpse of what was inside. From that day, all of them found any excuse to come to my office, promising friendship and loyalty, anything I wanted if I helped them achieve even a fraction of my success.

Our living arrangements were like unspoken rules. I had my private space, and the three girls shared the other apartment. It worked better for us. Everyone had their own space, and we spent quality time together instead of all our time together. This was the mistake I made in the past, projecting a needy image of a man willing to give anything for attention. The quality of the time we spend with each other over the quantity wins every time.

After our trip from the office, Amy and Anya would go to their place, and I would spend some time in mine. Tara would often join me for a shower and an hour of vigorous sex, then leave me to rest before we all went for dinner, a walk, or a play. It was time better spent than just sitting on a couch counting as present with my mind somewhere else, miles away.

I was home one such day when a knock came. The girls didn’t bother knocking anymore, so I went to the doors, and to my surprise, Cassie was there, looking like a cute black cat caught in the rain.

“Come in, come in. I was happy to see her. Would you like something to drink?”

“May I have some water, please?” Something was very wrong. I had never seen Cassie so insecure. Usually, she would barge in with her head held high, like the queen of Sheba, and demand sex. I didn’t want to push her or seem overly concerned. Cassie clearly came here with an intent, so I let her gather her thoughts and tell me in her own time. Sometimes, people are too curious or keen to help, resulting in the opposite of what they intended. I learned over time that sometimes the best strategy is to listen, so I took my mug of coffee, sat on a sofa, and remained silent.

“Jim, I…” Cassie started, and her words failed. I got up slowly and squatted beside the bed, face to face with Cassie, looking into her eyes.

“You know I love you?” I pitched my tone just right. Cassie’s pupils dilated, connecting with mine. She nodded, mouthing the words.

“Yes, but…” I pulled her in for a kiss, and her muscles tensed.

“Sometimes, you have to take a leap of faith.”

“I can’t.” That was it—the wall. Grr was right in the end. My way was good but ineffective. Sometimes, you have to destroy it so you can build it again. I summoned all my strength, knowledge, and experience. There was no other way. I could walk away or turn into a monster.

I reached into a drawer and pulled out a brand new Colt Python .357 Magnum six-shot revolver. Cassie’s eyes went big like saucers as she watched me put in one hollow point bullet and close the chamber. I spun it and placed the barrel on her forehead.

Something incredible happened. All the pain, stress, and tension in Cassie’s muscles disappeared. She closed her eyes, and her face looked serene. For the first time in my life, I saw her like that. Cassie looked like a marble statue of some untouchable goddess, so free and innocent. She took a deep breath and exhaled.

I pulled the trigger, and the pistol clicked. It took Cassie a minute to get back to her senses. She looked at me, and our eyes met. Her deep blue eyes looked even deeper. Cassie looked at me like she saw me for the first time. She watched me spin the gun again and point it at my head, then I took a deep breath and pulled the trigger.

“No!” She screamed, jumping at me, grabbing my hand with hers and pushing the barrel. The gun went off with a loud bang. “No, Jim, no! Don’t do this, please. Don’t leave me. You can’t. Oh, god! Please, Jim. I am pregnant.”

Cassie was hysterical, flapping her hands and touching me to make sure I was alive. She kissed my head and lips, kissed my eyes. Her tears were free-flowing, and she hugged me like never before. “There we are,” I thought to myself. Grr always maintained that fear is more effective.

Please, Jim, don’t do that. I love you! I love you so much.“ Cassie hyperventilated, breathing like a dog in rapid breaths. ”I love you. I love you.“ It went in circles. Grr was right. Some walls can’t be moved. They could only be broken. I spoke about Cassie for hours, and Grr helped me understand the root cause of her problem. Cassie was trapped inside, terrified of love. It took a leap of faith to break through her own boundaries, but she couldn’t do that. She built this massive, impenetrable wall between the world and her heart until she was trapped inside.

I had seen Cassie cry before, but never like that. She seemed inconsolable. I hugged her, and she kissed me, telling me all the sweet things. I broke her out, her inner child and the only thing left was to build her again. I pushed her on her back, letting her lay on the bed as I gazed into her eyes. She didn’t know it yet, but Cassie was mine.

”You are pregnant?“ She nodded and smiled.

”Imagine yourself with me, walking on the beach, holding hands with our daughter.“ Cassie’s pupils dilated as she listened to the pitch of my voice, its sound penetrating the deepest places, filling her head with dreams of a beautiful life. I talked, and she listened. It was the best story I could tell anyone. The night came and went, and we were still locked in our embrace, imagining our future, life and children.

I took Cassie on the most incredible journey and back. It took me the entire night to attack every single vector of her mind, making her feel like we lived in a fairytale in another universe.

”I want you to imagine our love as a dandelion flower, so yellow and beautiful, basking in the sunshine. Now imagine all the clouds gone and the picture getting brighter and brighter. Can you feel that love growing stronger and stronger, almost painful to observe, making it hard to breathe?“ Cassie nodded, entranced, imagining gorgeous images of a flower exploding and turning into a dandelion field reflecting the sunshine.

”I love you, Jim,“ she said and closed her eyes. Her mind was too far gone, and she passed out. She hugged me tight, pulling me closer, wrapping her hands and legs around me, entangling them. This was all I had in me, and I also closed my eyes. I did what I could and threw all my eggs in one basket.

I was never in any real danger. The bullet was fake, and there was no hole in the wall. It was a blank. Grr told me I had to shake her core, and the pistol did the job. The only thing left was to wait and pray about what I did to prevent the reset. It was the hardest one so far, and I didn’t want to attempt another again. My brain was a mess; I was exhausted. A loud buzzing sound made me want to vomit. I concentrated, focusing on the oscillation variance, and the sound changed and distorted, and then I was gone.

Chapter 43 - Cleaning out the closet

I was in the canteen, sharing food with the software engineers, when my phone bleeped. It was a message from an unknown number, simply saying, “All clear,“ and I smiled. This meant that Owen had met with the board, and they had decided to accept my plan, provided that everything I said proved true.

Krishna, the program manager, looked at me, wondering why I had gotten up from the table like this. I smiled, excusing myself.

“May I join you?“ he asked, offering to accompany me to my office, and I waved him over. He showed me some projections he had come up with and wanted me to validate them. It was the right time to implement my plan, but first things first. I had to tie up the loose ends and deal with the problems.

I checked my calendar for meeting invites. Diarmaid was riding Dick’s back again to make some progress in extracting critical knowledge from me. I pulled the email from the spam box and chose the meeting room, proposing a new time. Only minutes later, I got the confirmation back from Dick that he had accepted.

This was enough work for the day, and I packed my bag and walked outside. Sooner or later, managers always get what they want. It was just how corporations work. As much as I resisted the change, fighting Diarmaid would never get me anywhere. I had my own problems to deal with and a plan to realise.

I took a long walk through town, looking at the buildings and all the places I had watched all my life. Everything seemed so tired and aged, or maybe it was the melancholy. I had built a new life, and now I had to live in it.

Lamin found me on a bench in a park, throwing pieces of bread at the pigeons. I was lost in my thoughts, looking at my life and the road I had taken to get where I was. Most people wouldn’t understand that, in the end, we all look back at who we were. Lamin sat next to me in silence. He could recognise the heavy burden getting off my chest. Since I had chosen this road, I systematically erased my past, chipping away at who I was day after day until only a few old anchors were left, but now I was going to cut them, and the ship would sail away into the unknown and a new future.

I was looking forward to it, and I was petrified. What if I messed up something like I did before? I laughed. That kind of defeatist thinking sounded so out of character for me now that my mind organically rejected it. It was at this very moment that I abandoned my old self. I stood up and patted my faithful African friend’s back.

“Come on, buddy. Let’s get this show on the road.“ Lamin laughed. It was time to make things happen. He drove me home, and the girls gathered around me. Cassie was there, and I smiled, pulling her towards me and checking her eyes. I might have gone a little overboard with breaking the wall. It was obliterated. She felt happy and safe, looking forward to becoming a mother. Who knew that I would give her a purpose by taking things away from her. Amy and Cassie immediately bonded over their pregnancies. Gone was the haughty seductress, replaced by an ecstatic girlfriend. So much so that she even looked younger.

Cassie was strong and fiercely independent, doing things as she wanted, but the wall grew larger deep inside. It was the pregnancy that made her unbalanced. She wanted the child so much, but she was scared and came to me hoping I could magically make her brave or at least believe she was. In the end, it turned out that I was, in fact, the Wizard of Oz, and she was my lioness. She made the greatest sacrifice, and I took all of it and gave her a heart back.

For some reason, Cassie liked me from the first day. Maybe it was my openness, or perhaps because I was the only man she knew who was messed up more than her. Perhaps I was her type, or maybe it was the stars or the gods. It didn’t matter, and nobody cared. I stopped obsessing with whys and focused on what really mattered.

When she got pregnant, Cassie was petrified. Plenty of women out there are single mothers, but that wasn’t it. She cared for me, and the pregnancy forced the issue. I was the only man Cassie had sex with since our first time. I didn’t choose her, but she chose me for that privilege. Cassie had no illusion about how beautiful she was, and everyone in the world, including myself, wanted her for that. The idea that I would want her for something more was weirdly unpalatable, and she couldn’t bring herself to ever trust another man again. It was a roadblock ruining her life. Not all men are the same.

Of course, I was an asshole like the others, but I was an honest one. I never lied to Cassie, and it paid massive dividends. It was like in the Bible. “Then you will know the truth, and the truth will set you free— John 8:32.”

I haven’t thought about God for a long time and missed his countenance. The words of the most beautiful woman, the Arabic beauty, echoed in my ears, “Those who seek must ask for guidance.“ I sought and found my answers. I followed the light and found my path, just like Cassie did. It turned out we all had our cross to bear and had to walk alone across that bridge. I just shocked Cassie out of her gilded cage and made her jump and admit what everyone knew, and the birds in the trees sang. I found this the most frustrating. I could see she loved me in her eyes, but no matter what I did, Cassie wasn’t ready to admit it to herself. She avoided me so she wouldn’t get hurt by her love. She couldn’t believe I would want her for anything more than her looks.

It almost made me laugh at the same time as it drove me insane. I wanted everything from Cassie, especially the children. Those beautiful genes she carried were like a gift from the divine. God made her to procreate and bring forth the most beautiful, healthy children to bring a smile to the world as it changed. Cassie was a beacon of hope for all of us who loved to look at genetic perfection and wonder how the world would look if we all were this way. Cassie was a prize worth having, and I intended to keep her barefoot and pregnant until she asked me to stop. Just looking at her smile and gazing into her eyes when she accepted that I wanted her as a mother, Cassie blossomed. She was destined to be one, and I was the lucky man whose seed she carried.

The week went in quiet preparation. I ordered a dozen hardshell suitcases online, which arrived two days later. The girls packed their stuff during the day, and I would come after work. We would go out just to walk, explore, enjoy a meal, and have fun with the city.

Wherever we went, people turned their heads. You do not always see a well-dressed man surrounded by four gorgeous women looking at him with love in their eyes. Not even once did the girls even hint at jealousy. They cared for each other as much as they cared for me. Maybe I was their man, but we never defined the nature of our relationship. Whatever it was, everyone knew it; they just never said it out loud or verbalised it. We were a family.

The weekend ended, and Monday rolled around. I wasn’t looking forward to work that day. I got in early with a takeaway Starbucks cup, logged onto the computer, and started a program I wrote. It went through all my personal files, deleted them, connected them to my shared profile and backups, and purged them. I got rid of anything that could even remotely be construed as not work-related, erasing any trace of me doing anything other than the strictest definition of my job. I already deleted all my past emails, keeping only those related to work.

Five minutes before ten, I sat on one side of a conference table with paper and pen, watching the large dark Microsoft Surface we used for corporate video conferences and presentations. It was blank, just like I felt at that moment.

Richard walked in, closing the door behind him, looking at me with a stern face. He was pissed off, all right. It took us months to finally meet, and I caused him a world of trouble. I smiled at him, offering my hand. He ignored it and sat down on the other side.

“I am sorry, Dick, for taking so long to meet. I was busy.“ His annoyance jumped up another notch.

“Please address me as Richard, and your apology is not accepted. Let’s keep this professional.“ I could see he was seething with rage. He flipped his notebook and laid out his demands while I took them down as bullet points on my pads.

“I am sorry, but I can’t just transfer that knowledge.“

“Why not?“ His words were terse, and he tapped his feet.

“We don’t have an adequate cadre. See, all our developers are trained to use commodity hardware, you know, Microsoft Windows, Linux, and personal computers. We don’t have anyone here who knows how to work with mainframes. Most of them retired, and the rest, the company made redundant because they didn’t know how to use Linux.“

“You can teach them and make it a part of your knowledge transfer.“ I chuckled, and it annoyed Dick to no end.

“What’s so funny?“

“Ah, nothing. Don’t worry about it. It is irrelevant now.“ That got Dick even more pissed off, and he insisted I tell him what it was, even giving me permission to speak freely regardless of company ethics.

“This is why I made a mistake and applied for the CTO job in the first place. I know the exact difference between a personal computer and a mainframe. It’s not something you could just knowledge transfer, starting with the difference between EBCDIC and ASCII. Most developers don’t even know what that is. This is why I thought you would be a particularly poor CTO candidate. You barely know how to turn on the computer.“

“You fucking twat!“ The man lost it. “I got the job because I earned it. I worked here for years, putting in the time. I deserved the promotion.“

“And I have a master’s degree from Cambridge in software engineering and computer science, while you got your master’s in liberal arts. You are a pencil pusher and a brown-nosing political animal used to bending over.“ Dick got almost purple in his face. He asked for it and got it right back. The way I always spoke plainly in the office was legendary. Everyone knew I didn’t do the fluffy and fuzzy. I was always precise, honest, and direct. That was one of the reasons I was respected. Once people got used to my style, they stopped asking me nonsense they didn’t want to hear the truth about.

“You sent me in front of the commission, and I got a fucking reprimand. You messed with my livelihood and my career.“

“That’s because you always looked at me with those hungry eyes like you do now. You just want to dominate me for sex because I am a vulnerable woman.“ Richard exploded in laughter, slapping his hand on the desk like he heard the best joke in the world.

“Everyone knows you were playing a game.“

“What would you know about my identity? It took me years of struggle and psychotherapy to be brave enough to accept myself. Go look at my psychiatrist’s records and see how many times I wanted to kill myself. Then, you come and treat me like a piece of meat because you want to fuck me.“ That got him enraged. I saw little hairs on his arms raised.

“You fucking faggot! You motherfucker, I will kill you for saying this shit.“

“See, this right now. You are scaring me. Look into a mirror. Look at your eyes. You are horny, and you want to rape me.“ The man stood up. There was nothing but disgust in his eyes. He looked at me like I was a piece of shit he wished to stomp. His hands turned into fists, and I could only imagine how much he wanted to punch me.

Please don’t hit me, Dick. I give up. I will have sex with you and never tell anyone, I promise. I will suck your dick right now, just please calm down. You are scaring me. Oh god! I am so scared.“ I lifted my hands to cover my face.

“You are a piece of shit, Jim, a fucking faggot tranny. You disgust me. You are a filthy ass fucking nobody. Look at yourself; I want to spit in your face. You make me sick.“ I slid from the chair and went on my knees, raising my hands towards Dick, speaking with a pleading voice.

“Please, Dick. Don’t be this way. I promise I will do anything; just don’t fire me. I am so scared. Don’t beat me again. Here, let me suck your dick, and you can cum in my ass like you did that one time at the office party.“ Dick’s face was precious to watch. The grimace would be worth all the money for the Hollywood producers.

“Get the fuck away from me, you fucking pervert piece of shit, or I’ll fuck you up. I will punch your face.“ I kept crawling closer and watched the purple of his face turn white, then green.

“Please, Dick. Don’t hurt me again.“

“That’s it, you piece of shit. I am done. You are fired. Get your fucking personal belongings and leave the office. We are done. I don’t want to see your face again.“ Dick stormed out of the meeting room, and I got up to my feet and went to my office. I sat down at the computer and sent a lengthy email to human resources, which included the diversity officer and ESG representative. I closed my personal computer, put it into a bag, and walked out of the office, handing my access card to the security guy in the lobby and walked out.

Lamin waited outside with a car for me and opened my door. I looked into his eyes, and he smiled. I got in and looked at the back mirror.

“Where to, sir?“ My suit already needed dry cleaning.

“Let’s clean out the trash.“ I muted Tina’s texts and avoided her messages. Her emails went straight into a special folder I never opened. The bitch was going nuts, struggling without cash for almost three months, and she was angry, desperate, and vindictive. Just like predicted, she relented in the end, finally realising that I wasn’t falling for her bullshit anymore and that I meant every word I said.

After such a long silence, I texted Tina for the first time. She immediately called me, and I answered, but then she started spewing vile profanities. I just disconnected and sent her messages straight to the voicemail again, and I got five messages before she started texting me again with her apologies.

“There we go. Good little slut.“ I mumbled as I read what she wrote.

“I’ll be at your place in exactly two hours. Please have the boys ready, and I will bring the cash.“ Lamin parked at the bank and went with me inside. I took him into the vault and pulled out my treasure. He helped me fill my suitcase and escorted me out. We sat in the car and drove away.

At the appointed time, I knocked at Tina’s door with a notary, a witness, and a lawyer. Her eyes widened when she saw everyone, but she bit her lip and invited them in.

“Where are the boys?”

“The kids are upstairs. Did you bring me what you promised?” This is where the lawyer interjected.

“This is the agreement. Please read and sign.” I opened the suitcase, and Tina’s eyes went wide, seeing all the gold coins. “And this is the appraisal and certificate that the sum of the coins exceeds a million pounds. You can take them to this company, and they will pay you the amount printed at the bottom.

Nina couldn’t hear anything. She took one coin in her hand and rubbed it with her fingers. Deep down inside, Nina never believed I could pull off something like that. After all, she was convinced that she destroyed me and took more than half of what I owned.

“What does this say?” She addressed the lawyer, pointing at a ten-page document.

“That you relinquish full custody and complete parental rights to your ex-husband. Please read it before you sign.”

“I should have my lawyer look at this first.”

“You are absolutely right, miss. We can return at another time when you have had enough time to study it.” Nina’s face fell. She was hooked by all that shiny gold in front of her eyes. One thing is to talk about money in numbers or even cash, but gold made it that much more real and tangible.

“No, that is okay. I will read it and ask if I need to understand something.” Tina spent the next twenty minutes reading, asking basic questions like any layman looking at a legal document. That’s precisely the reason why I hired expensive lawyers.

Ultimately, she took a pen, dated, and signed four copies while the lawyer ensured she initiated all the pages. I countersigned, and so did the witness, then the notary recorded and bound all the copies separately, putting seals and signing them, keeping one copy for the official record keeping.

I got one copy of the agreement, and Tina got another. The final one ended up in my lawyer’s suitcase. It was done, and I pushed the suitcase at Tina, and she grabbed it like Gollum in the Lord of the Rings films. The lawyer and the others said their goodbyes and left. It was done. The boys were legally mine.

“I hope you never find happiness. I hate you from the bottom of my heart. Now take your kids and fuck off. I never want to see you again,” she snorted like a swine before screaming at the kids. I heard the footsteps, and the boys got down, running down.

This couldn’t have ended without a final stab. Tina had the boys wearing pink dresses and girl shoes, and she had their ears pierced. She laughed in my face, seeing my eyes water. It was one of the most painful moments of my life. I bit my tongue and steeled my face. My boys needed me. This was the end.

Tina’s shrill laughter followed us out, and I couldn’t keep it inside anymore. I turned to her and stared her down. I saw her afraid for the first time in my life, and I pitched it right.

“Remember my words, you fucking whore. I swear to you with my life. You will live to regret what you have done. It will haunt you for the rest of your life.” I could see her pupils dilate. There was no comeback. Tina was genuinely scared. I spat on the floor to get rid of the bile in my mouth and marched my kids out.

She followed in silence with a scowl on her face. Then her eyes got big, and her mouth opened. A top-of-the-range Maybach stopped in front of the house, and a suited driver walked out and held the door open.

The kids ran inside, and I walked in after them, never looking back at the monster at the doors, who was watching us drive away. As soon as we turned the corner, the boys hugged me, and I broke out in tears.

“Come in my lovelies. I love you so much.” I kept kissing my sons and hugging them hard. I could feel my heart break, and my hands trembled. I kept kissing and hugging them, telling them how much I loved them. I’ve never loved anyone more than those two poor boys crying in my arms.

“Please, Lamin, stop.” I couldn’t take it anymore. I saw a sports shop on the way and took the boys inside. The salespeople stared at me and Lamin, acting as a bodyguards, not allowing them to come even close. I had them give me sports shoes and shorts of their size for the boys.

“Give me this shit,” I told the boys, crumpled their dresses, and tore them into shreds before throwing them in the bin.

“Come here,” the boys approached me, and I pulled out their earrings and threw them at the wall. I was boiling inside and wanted to punch someone, so angry I could take a cricket bat and walk to Tina’s home to beat her into a bloody pulp.

I pulled the boys’ hands and threw money at the salespeople, disgusted with the place where their dresses lay even in trash cans. I felt like dousing it all with gasoline and setting it ablaze. It took all the training and power to keep myself from blowing a gasket.

“Where are we going, daddy?” Liam asked. His little voice brought tears to my eyes.

“We are going on a long trip, just us, and I will take you to see sharks and elephants. We will fly on a big plane and on a big boat, and you will make new friends, and we will always be together.” The boys hugged me tight and cried, and I cried with them. Nothing else in the world mattered more than that.

Lamin drove in silence, watching the road, transporting the most precious cargo for me, my greatest love. I lost track of time, embracing my children. This was the happiest I had been since I could remember. It was the last anchor tying me to this place, and I cut all the ties. I was a free man.

The girls squealed and sang as I brought in the boys. They rolled out food, cake, and a whole mountain of boy toys, age-appropriate.

“They are your aunties,” I said when the boys looked at the girls with gaping mouths and big eyes. “This is Amy and Tara,” I went around. The girls were already in full-blown mommy mode. They squatted to the boys’ level, shook their hands, and hugged them. I was so happy to cry if I had any tears left.

Within minutes, the boys sat at the table, and we had our first family dinner together. It was laughter and joy all around, and I felt complete for the first time. There was nothing more I wanted, but there were plenty of loose ends to tie. This only motivated me more.

Over the next week, my former company tried to contact me several times. I ignored all their attempts, focusing on my children. I took them to a private doctor the very next day, who examined them head to toe, and they weren’t abused.

“I can’t speak for the mental abuse. You would need a specialist to have a look at them. My lawyer bent over backwards to certify the documents with the court, issue a letter, and then contact social services. I was haemorrhaging cash in legal services, the best money I ever spent. He met us at the passport office one day, where the kids were issued all the necessary travel documents.

The girls ran the boys ragged. They dragged them all over town, getting them dressed in the best boy clothes and buying them any toys they wanted, provided it was from the boys’ section. It didn’t take the girls long to figure out that Tina messed with the boys’ heads, so they all joined together to fix what was broken and steer the boys towards understanding the difference between men and women.

Another week passed, and I found myself in a familiar environment again. Ironically, I was in the same room where I got fired, except this time there was Diarmaid, the human resources representative, and Jim, the director of legal compliance. All of them looked grim, staring at the court summons and my lawyers on the other side, probably wanting to understand how much this was going to cost them.

“Five million pounds.” My lawyer opened with a high number for the out-of-court settlement. I saw everyone on the other side take a deep breath. Nobody expected something like that.

“That is impossible. The court would never go this high for wrongful termination.” The company’s general counsel jumped in. My lawyer smiled, and I played a soundtrack on my phone. This is the problem with technology these days. The teleconferencing system’s screen was off, but not the camera or the microphone. Unknown to Dick, there was a Zoom call going on in the background with me recording it from my personal computer in my office and my lawyer with witnesses watching it on mute from their office.

I could see the blood drain from everyone’s face. This wasn’t going to be a wrongful dismissal charge but something much bigger involving systemic discrimination against the most vulnerable of society’s minorities, with added sexual harassment on top of it. I could barely stop myself from chuckling.

“We are prepared to offer Jim his job back and start disciplinary procedures against Richard.”

“I am sorry, but my client doesn’t feel this is a safe working environment for transgender people. Here is an affidavit by his long-term psychiatrist relating to his deteriorating mental state after the firing.” My lawyer pulled a piece of paper and slid it to Diarmaid across the table.

“We can only offer him two hundred and fifty thousand pounds. This is as much as I am authorised before taking it to the board,” Diarmaid butted in, wishing all of it to go away.

“Unfortunately, this won’t be enough. It is equivalent to his yearly salary, which he couldn’t get elsewhere. According to the terms of his employment contract, he can’t work for anyone else for two years after the termination of the employment.” Everyone knew that if this went to court, the recording would play, and the news would explode. It would be worse than the whole Bud Light debacle.

Diarmaid was desperate to keep this disaster under wraps, or it could affect his upcoming bid for the CEO job. I could see the other Jim’s tiny smile. He was the old CEO’s favourite and passionately despised Diarmaid. Anything that could sabotage the man even a little, Jim would see as a positive. I was sure he would support paying me what I asked just to get rid of Diarmaid for the management race, and Diarmaid knew that.

“Give us a realistic offer, and we will consider it.” My lawyer was losing patience with the amateur games. “The courts would give Jim at least five years‘ worth of severance and fine you, so you’ll be at least two million out of pocket, not to mention all the reputational damage and resulting share price decline. The right number is five million pounds. We can sign it today, and all of it goes away.” This is what I was paying the big bucks for. My lawyers were sharks, and they were smelling blood.

“I wasn’t bluffing. I can only authorise the quarter-million-pound spending before it gets into a board review, and then all bets are off.” Diarmaid’s panic was palpable.

“Then my client walks away with a loss. Your contract prevents him from getting another employment, and you’re offering something he would get anyway if you didn’t fire him like that.” I could see Diarmaid’s eyes sparkle.

“We could waive the non-compete agreement.”

“I’m sorry, that won’t do it. I read that contract, which is bad for my client. You could go after him a different way.” Diarmaid looked at Jim from legal, and he nodded. He knew exactly how bad the contracts were. The human resources nodded as well. It was a scam. The employment agreement was written in such a way as to screw the employee in any way they wanted. Diarmaid wouldn’t let go of it. He was a shark as well, and he sensed he could push it.

“We could nullify the contract like it never happened, no harm, no foul, and he walks out with a quarter-million today.” My lawyer looked at me, and I nodded. I could see the victory in Diarmaid’s eyes. He was still the best, the hotshot manager, the rising star who will be the CEO someday.

“We would need a non-litigation agreement,” the general counsel said.

“Only if it is reciprocal. My client will agree not to sue you in the future if you agree not to sue him as well.” We had a deal. My lawyer already had all the documents drafted and printed out. The only thing missing was the sums.

I took a brief walk through my old offices, shook hands with my former colleagues, and got the last cup of coffee from the place before returning to the meeting room. On the way, I noticed Dick’s office was empty, and his name was taken off the door. Something told me that the company would soon be hiring for a new CTO.

It took about an hour for all the documents to be signed and certified. Then we watched Diarmaid connect to his laptop, log into the payment system, make a few entries, and add references. A few seconds later, my phone bleeped. I checked it and a quarter million pounds were there. The company would take care of the taxation and other issues.

With all that done, we said our goodbyes, and I walked down the well-known corridors for the last time. I was out and gone, and according to our agreement, I never had any employment contract there. The original was null and voided by the agreement of both parties, and Diarmaid won again. Lamin looked at the back as I entered the car.

“Where to, sir?”

“Get me the fuck away from this place.” He laughed, pressed on the pedal, and we were gone. Two weeks ago, he graduated. I bought him a new wardrobe, fitting my new Chief Operating Officer.

Chapter 44 - Surf and Turf

I sat on the outdoor sofa, drinking coffee and watching Liam and Callum play in the sand. They were building a castle, and Amy fretted over them, ensuring they had enough sunblock to cover every inch of their bodies. In the distance, Dubai arose from the fine sand particles, looking like a fog from where we lived. I could see Burj Khalifa, the tallest building in the world, dominating the place.

“Daddy, daddy, come, come,“ the two happy kids urged me to come and see what they had built there. The sun was scorching, but I lifted myself up, walked over, and knelt in the sand. They were playing with some toy cars parked in front of a castle.

“This is you, and this is Neneh,“ they said, pointing at the toy soldiers. For some reason, the kids were fascinated by the African princess, perhaps because she would sit every night with them and read from the book of the thousand and one Arabian tales.

Liam and Callum were ecstatic about going on their first plane. Cassie sat with me, Anya sat with Tara, and the two boys sat with Amy. She told them stories and played cartoons on the in-flight entertainment system. We were a big family, all right, about to be bigger.

Iqbal waited for us, but it was with a people carrier this time. We had to take another two taxis just to transport all our luggage. Only my wardrobe counted eight large suitcases, while the girls counted twelve, not counting the hand luggage. There was no doubt in anyone who saw us collecting it at the conveyor belt. We came here to stay.

The three girls waited for us at the entrance, wearing their abayas. That didn’t stop them from squalling and jumping around, hugging everyone.

“This is Neneh, your aunt, Paige, another aunt, and Dixie.“ This is where I stopped and stared. The former homeless skeleton girl looked like a supermodel. Her two friends made it their personal mission to make her stunning. She even had nice breasts, thanks to a surgical procedure and first-class silicone.

Dixie laughed as my mouth fell to the floor. She ran into my arms and squeezed me hard.

“You are so soft,“ I said, unable to contain my amazement. She gave me a big fat kiss on the lips and quickly whispered in my ear, “You can test drive my new body tonight.“ I didn’t know if I should laugh or cry, but I was sure I would take her up on that offer.

It was fun watching the London girls meet the Dubai ones. At first, there was some awkwardness, which vanished a minute later when Neneh suggested we should all go and have some food in a restaurant. She booked us a private room in her favourite place, the Madinat Jumeirah, followed by a boat ride on the canals and ending with a little shopping spree in their open-air mall.

The girls started running around the place, discovering exquisitely furnished rooms with ensuite showers and wardrobes. Everyone wanted to look pretty, wearing their best clothes. They had been talking about Dubai, begging me to take them there since I sent them the first pictures. I also took a shower and put on some fresh clothes. I could hear the girls squealing and calling each other, having a look at something or trying something else. Our villa was superb, a perfect marriage of simplicity and opulence.

I told no one that I provisionally owned the place. Ahmad, the house owner, was happy to sell it to me with a deferred payment. I wired a hundred thousand dollars from my settlement as a down payment, promising to pay off the balance later. If you want to win big, you have to gamble big or not belong in the game. It was my favourite quote from Tai Pan, a novel by James Clavell. I hadn’t even started my company yet, and I was already twenty-seven million bucks in the hole. It made me laugh. In some other life, I would be petrified.

I called out to everyone, and the girls descended, dressed to impress, looking like angels. Iqbal waited for us outside with a large people carrier, which turned into a school adventure trip as soon as we crossed the bridge. The London girls were losing their minds, pulling each other to see different sights, pointing at them, promising to explore them someday. I smiled, thinking about how much energy everyone had after a six-hour flight.

Neneh led us to the restaurant, which had fine views of the canals and friendly staff bending over backwards to make everyone feel welcome and comfortable. It was a surf and turf order, and the large table contained a banquet, anything from camel meat to lobster and fish. The girls dug in like it was their last meal, taking hundreds of pictures and recording videos of the excessive splendour on the table.

A long time ago, I wondered what a man must do to afford that. From my new vantage, having gone through a personal transformation struggle, I know it doesn’t work this way. You don’t just go to people and tell them, “Do what I do, and you’ll get rich and have beautiful women; just buy an expensive car to compensate for your flaccid micro penis, and the world will change for you; the doors will open.“ There are too many monkeys like that all over the internet pretending to have great advice. Don’t do as I do; just do what I say.

The first question one should have is if someone is so rich and powerful, why would he want to share his secrets with others? I know that I wouldn’t, and neither would anyone sane unless selling them is part of how you made them. Give me a million so I can teach you how to make ten. That’s easy math; just find nine more fools.

I learned over time that money is an abstract concept. When you work for it, there is never enough of it, but as you grow, learn, and expand your views, the world adapts to your new perception and situation. In my wildest dreams, I could never imagine hanging out with a group of women like that, let alone having them as part of my family. They say everything is possible if you can imagine it, but how does one imagine a life he is afraid to live? How does one dream if the only thing he sees is four walls with no way out? Most of the working-class people are that type, the cogs in a well-oiled machine, sitting at home, watching the ads on the internet from someone claiming he is rich and will teach you his secrets. Of course, it is nonsense.

My worldview changed in a year, and I learned how to dream new dreams. I didn’t try to influence the world to bend it my way. That is impossible. Instead, I learned how to bend myself, open my mind, learn from authentic sources of knowledge, and incorporate it with mine. With every step, the world I lived in expanded, and I could find a new kind of people, a new kind of world views and perceptions, and connect with it on a higher level. The profound realisation I had was that personal perception shapes one’s financial situation, and it is not limited to just money. Still, everything I touched and everyone I met resonated with me on a different level.

Even Owen, my new FKK club friend, would have never taken me seriously, let alone do any business with me, if I didn’t exhibit the traits he could resonate with. It was a concept I was aware of in my previous life that I so casually discarded, thinking I knew enough and was the smartest. There is a difference between wisdom and intelligence. I was an intelligent idiot savant, and everyone knew how to use that. Others knew how to profit from a cretin that thought he knew everything. That was the wisdom I could not perceive, locked in my little world, living my benign, dull, ordinary, and utterly unimpressive life.

I smiled, looking at my girls, laughing, eating, feeding my sons, and playing with them. I was a guy living in a twenty-seven million dollar mansion in one of the world’s most impressive developments. I surrounded myself with the most beautiful women and lived a life most people couldn’t imagine. I laughed. This was not money but power. I made that.

People often talk about money and power and how they go together as if they are interchangeable, as if money gives you power. I thought about it long ago, and I realised it was the same conundrum as the chicken and the egg. Which comes first? I concluded in the end that money is imaginary. It is a skewed reflection of someone’s power. While cash will give one option and influence, this is how poor people think. They assume that by getting rich, they will be powerful as well. That is a mistake that all those “get rich quick“ scheme peddlers on the internet failed to understand. It is how poor people see the world. The high class, low class, and no class. You can’t see the top of the hill looking up.

I looked around at the waiters and the other guests at the restaurant. Some threw us glances, while others openly stared. They had never seen a man at the head of the table surrounded by the most extraordinary collection of beauties since Hugh Hefner, and they thought this was money, but they were wrong like everyone else. It was power.

That’s what I sought out and learned from the others. I took what they had to teach and put it together like a jigsaw puzzle, changing how I see the world and waking up the real me inside. I evolved from a larval version of myself, cocooned and scared, into a butterfly everyone wanted to look at and admire. Most people seek money, but I sought power, and it started with Dan and learning how to become a man.

After that first night with Lexi, when I felt it for the first time, I was awed, impressed, and addicted to that brief moment. It wasn’t the sexual ecstasy or anything so pedestrian. For the briefest, fleeting moment, I felt what it was like to be a man. That was enough for me, and I wanted more. My eyes were opened to the possibility. I didn’t want to live out the rest of my life without feeling that spark again, so I did what I had to and sought to awaken the man inside. Here I was, in Dubai, surrounded by a bevvy of beauties, living the life that resulted from it, and that spark was now permanent.

The dinner ended, and Amy took the boys on a boat ride through the canals. Some girls joined them, while others opted for a stroll through the open-air mall. I took my own path, not interested in trinkets, getting lost in the corridors, trying to find my way to the date shop, hoping to get sufficiently lost to stumble upon the most beautiful woman I’ve seen again, the magical Arabian princess.

I lost track of time, and who knows, maybe a couple of hours later, the girls found me sitting in a small Arabian cafe, sipping my coffee, munching on chocolate-covered dates. Liam and Callum ran up to me for a hug, and I gave them a selection of dates to try. It was their first time trying one.

The girls eventually managed to drag me away after each getting a drink to take with them. Iqbal found us and took us home. I was thinking about how impractical all of it was. The girls would need cars to be mobile and independent. There was no way for Iqbal to handle all of that.

It was dark outside, and we ended up sitting in a circle on the floor of a well-lit living room, surrounding a pile of gift-wrapped packages. The girls from London didn’t come to Dubai empty-handed but brought with them all sorts of presents. The Dubai girls ripped into them, squealed, and thanked their friends. It was like Christmas with only the tree missing.

***

We spent the rest of the week discovering Dubai. The local girls already knew all the best places to visit and were happy to be our guides. The boys were ecstatic and had a great time, but I couldn’t escape the feeling at the back of my mind that something was a little off. I could see them get confused sometimes, and it frightened me. Tina had already managed to do much damage, and I didn’t know if it was reversible. It was something I intended to look into as soon as possible.

Out of everything the city had to offer, the girls liked the desert the most—driving cars on the sand dunes or surfing down the slopes, falling and rolling down, giggling like little children. My boys loved it the most, and my worries subsided. Nothing is more stupid than surfing down the dunes and then climbing back through the hot sands to do it again.

No woman with half a brain would repeat it more than two or three times, but the boys couldn’t stop themselves, going up and down, rolling down the sands and laughing. There it was, right in front of my eyes. Forget all those so-called professionals and the rest of the woke retards. The boys will be boys, and nothing could convince me otherwise. Even if the reverse was true, I didn’t want them to end up mutilated for the sake of scoring some brownie points with the perverts in power.

Almost every day, we went to the Jumeirah beach and walked at night, ending up in a rooftop bar for a drink and a light snack. Neneh would usually excuse herself from that, taking the boys home to tell them the stories of Aladdin and the Jin. I thanked her once. She was a significant positive influence on the kids.

There were no gay men or transgender individuals where Neneh lived, and I knew why. Their education system was incompatible with that. Some people are born with no arms and learn to live with that. Some women are born with male genitalia, and they learn to accept that they are men. Those who don’t are eventually bred out. It was nature’s way of telling them, “end of the line.“ That’s why they fussed when Neneh tried to kiss another girl. It was unacceptable in her inflexible society, and eventually, they won when she got married.

It was a lifestyle and culture rooted in traditional values, something the West couldn’t even begin to comprehend. Western countries view themselves as progressive, to their own detriment. I refused to play that game, and I pulled the plug. I moved all my remaining assets abroad, and I was done. I would miss London, but I could come as a visitor anytime to walk the familiar streets and notice how backwards the place got while the rest of the world prospered. The Western neo-Marxist ideology was pulling them backwards. Luckily, I didn’t have to worry about any of that anymore. Like so many smart ones, I dodged a bullet.

The girls and I mostly stayed home for the weekend, and they cooked. The boys were the best critics, telling the truth without worrying about hurting anyone’s feelings. As soon as the boys said it was terrible, everyone laughed. We all knew the food wasn’t that great, but we didn’t want to say it out loud to discourage further attempts.

“Let’s all take a cooking class. I’ll find a chef, and we can all learn how to make the best meals.“ The girls cheered. I’ve been meaning to do this for a while but haven’t gotten around to it yet.

“Can we learn too?” Liam asked, excited like everyone else.

“No, we are men. I’ll take you on a boat and teach you how to fish, then the girls can prepare it for us.” The boys jumped up and hugged me. Though not strictly true, I had to always watch out for causing confusion and further damage.

Monday rolled in, and so did my brand-new electric Hummer. It took me a while to source the right supplier and negotiate delivery times. The waiting list was long, like a snake’s tail, but I managed to negotiate a deal with the guy next in the queue to wait a little longer so I could get my car earlier.

It was a ridiculous idea to have an electric vehicle in Dubai, where petrol costs next to nothing, but I loved the car. It came with a portable generator and a spare petrol tank. The girls squealed, watching the truck unload the vehicle in front of our garage. It had zero miles on the clock, and I signed a receipt, threw the keys to Tara, and she let everyone in. The boys were ecstatic. The car was white and looked exactly like the toys I bought.

Neneh made me a cup of coffee and stored it in a thermal flask. I took Anya, Paige, and Dixie with me, and then we were off. The girls were excited. I was going to take them to my office. The security issued them their access cards, and we were off, up in the elevator, then straight through the corridors.

The place looked busy with all the computers and monitors that arrived. Ten Indian guys were about, most of them sitting in front of the computers and a few standing in front of the whiteboard. They saw me and smiled. I shook their hands, glad to see them again. Krishna came up to me, and I patted his shoulder.

“I’m happy to see you again, buddy. Everything okay on this end?” He smiled, handing me a tablet with the daily report. He’s been emailing them to me for a while.

“We are at sixty per cent capacity onshore and about thirty per cent offshore.” Everyone was ready, busy reviewing a set of architectural documents I gave them, analysing Terraform and Ansible scripts, sorting out the blue, green, and dev environments in AWS and Azure, and using DigitalOcean for spikes.

“How’s your accommodation?”

“Excellent, sir. Everyone is happy.” I rented a block of flats in Sharjah and signed them up for the bus service there and back. Everyone was excited to work on the new technologies.

About a week after I left the company, half of the Indian engineers rolled off from the project, some on holiday, others for changes in the assignment, and I scooped them up on a long-term contract. They were not coming back to London anytime soon, if ever. All of them were excited about working in Dubai as it was closer to their families, and they could just find a cheap flight and be there in a few hours for the week or a weekend. Our IT setup was all about cloud services, and they could technically work sitting on a tree branch in the forest.

“This will be your office,” I took the girls to a nicely furnished room with modern, cosy furniture. The three were keen on doing something productive and having some sort of self-actualisation experience. I thought it was good for them. I already had a deal with Amy to rejoin the university online. Anya and Dixie wanted the same. They were not qualified for much at the moment, but they had my trust, and that’s what counted the most in my book.

Amy would only work part-time to get a taste of the corporate experience, still focused on her social network followers and being a cute and sexy daddy’s little girl for me.

“I’ve got the technology and management covered, but I need a public relations and a marketing department.” The girls knew little about it but knew how to attract attention and milk it. If they researched and studied, they would figure out what kind of website we needed, how it should look, and what it should say. Good artists copy; the great ones steal. What’s good for Pablo Picasso was good for me, even though I took it in a less figurative sense.

I went to my office and let the girls sort themselves out the way they thought best. Within minutes of sitting down, all of the engineers found their way inside, knocked on the glass door, and sat on the chair opposite, thanking me for a great opportunity and telling me how much they enjoyed working with me.

It was an investment I nurtured for a long time, and now it was paying dividends. They knew that if I wanted, I could poach them from their consultancy and employ them directly, giving them more professional development options.

The girls burst into my room just before lunch, bombarding me with their ideas. Some were spot on, and others were out there. I lifted my arms in surrender.

“What do I know about marketing? Do your best and make me proud.” It was the worst thing I could have said, and they attacked me with their lips, squealing like children.

“No, stop, please. Be professional,” I pleaded, watching the engineers on the other side snicker. Luckily, it was lunchtime already, so I dragged the girls downstairs. I was glad to see them excited and motivated, presented with a serious challenge. Some people need this to feel valued.

It took us a week for everything to come into its place, the home, the work, and our free time. The girls turned this exclusive villa into a home, converting one of the rooms into a nursery, and the boys got the room all for themselves, filled with boys‘ toys. During the day, the girls would come out in the sun, swim in the pool or the sea, and sunbathe. Our villa was at the very tip of the palm leaf, so only two other villas could have reasonable access, and both were unsold and empty.

The girls seemed to find their niche in just a couple of weeks. Neneh became the house manager. She was the one presiding over what went where and how things worked. Cassie became a real mommy girl. She would read and research everything about pregnancies, conspire with Amy, and love to cuddle. It made me laugh. Cassie barely found out she was pregnant and already acted like she was about to deliver.

One day, Cassie approached me after dinner, curled herself in my lap, and licked my cheek as always. I never asked her why she did that because I had to admit I found it cute.

“I would like to talk to you about something,“ Cassie started. I sat up, and she wrapped her arms around my neck. “Remember Shay?“ Cassie began. Who could forget the gorgeous blonde bombshell? I’ve been meaning to ask her about that. Cassie went into a lengthy story about the two of them being best friends, how they did everything together, and how they missed each other.

“Would you mind if she lived with us? I promise she will never be a problem.“ I couldn’t figure out why Cassie would think I would be against Shay.

“Book her a ticket today and bring her over.“

“But there is one more thing.” Cassie stared into my eyes. “She also wants to get pregnant.“ I almost laughed. That girl was a real copycat. Where Cassie went, Shay followed.

“I guess we’ll have to make her a baby then.“ I shrugged, watching Cassie’s pupils dilate. Then her eyes filled with tears, and she hugged me tight and buried her face into my neck. I stopped trying to figure her out and accepted it was impossible. Maybe someday in the far, far future, Cassie would tell me the story of her life. Until that time, all she needed was love, something all of us were able to provide in abundance.

The following weekend, I drove Cassie to the airport. I could have sent Iqbal, but this was an adventure. Cassie was in love with my Hummer. She would take every opportunity to drive it anywhere she liked. We stood by the barrier, right outside the security zone, when we heard a squeal. A gorgeous blonde ran up to us, pulling two massive hardshell suitcases. Shay didn’t come to visit us; she came to stay.

The two best friends embraced while I pulled Shay’s luggage, keen to return as quickly as possible before they turned too many heads. Dubai was a discrete city where public display of affection was discouraged, and the way the two women went at each other bordered on getting arrested. I certainly didn’t want that.

We barely managed to close the car doors when Shay attacked me with her lips full force, making it hard to breathe or get a single word in to answer her squeals.

“Thank you, oh, thank you, Jim. Thank you so much.“ There was nothing to thank me for. I liked Shay a lot, and the fact that she wanted to have my child made me like her much more. Shay was a gorgeous girl but damaged, perhaps in the same way as Cassie or even more. At least Cassie had her own unique style, but Shay was always content with mimicking her friend.

I didn’t mind, knowing that somewhere down the road, in her own way, Shay would open herself up to me when she was ready for that. This way or another, we are all damaged. I was just happy she chose me to be her child’s father. It made me think. The world was extra hard on gorgeous women.

Cassie, Neneh, and Tara were to blame. Without clear direction on my side, they caught and spread the baby fever, birthing in real life the manifestation of their fantasies. All the other girls jumped on the bandwagon and took the frenzy to a ridiculous level.

I created a world for myself with plenty of security and little judgment. The girls took it to the next level without possessive jealousy or pointing fingers, effectively creating a commune with me in the middle.

I should have stopped that, put my foot down and laid the law, but in all honesty, I got caught up in this, adapting my plan, adding one layer after another. All of it fits into my vision of the future, with minor alterations here and there.

“I am ovulating,“ Shay whispered, biting my ear with her teeth and moaning while I pumped away. After her arrival and all the commotion died down, I pulled Shay’s hand, saying, “Come with me, I want to show you something.“ I took her to the bedroom and pulled her down. There is no time like the present to make a strong statement. I could see Shay still needed encouragement beyond just words of a promise. It was the key to her psyche. Someone hurt Shay in a bad way, making her unable to trust men.

With deep, merciless strokes, I jackhammered my cock into her, pissing hot sperm like from a hose, filling Shay’s insides, painting her ovaries, while she moaned loudly, biting my shoulder. Actions speak louder than words. I showed her that some men keep their promises. One doesn’t have to be a psychologist to determine what happened and why Shy mimicked Cassie.

It was time to meet with Dan again, and much had changed. We’ve been talking online, bouncing off emails, and coming up with a plan so crazy that it might just work. Sometimes, I felt like Don Quixote, riding a horse and chasing the windmills of modern times, but it was all worth it in the end. There was no expense I’d spare for the sake of my children, even the seemingly crazy one.

Dan was a product of his time, just like everyone else. He had an ability, an innate talent to teach something that nobody could, and I seized the opportunity, telling him we should go into business. Not together, of course. I had no interest in helping other men, but I wanted to finance something Dan would be good at.

I’ve been perturbed about my boys since the divorce. At first, it was hard to even process that their own mother would be able to do something against them. It turns out that not all people are made the same. Somehow, my ex projected her misguided hate for me onto them, knowing it would hurt me more than anything else. The crazy bitch was ready to sacrifice her own babies to get at me, and for what? Ego is a dangerous poison.

It took some time and a lot of phone calls, messages, and meetings online before I managed to cross all the t’s and dot all the i’s. The one part that was missing was the final meeting with Dan. After completing our monthly scheduled training, I gave him my boys.

Through a bunch of intermediaries, I invested in a place in Thailand with a pool, villa, elephant rides, jet skis, beaches, and a whole other range of boy’s activities. Together with Dan and a group of instructors, child psychologists, and whatnot, we came up with a plan.

Dan would take my boys for a month to something looking like a Boy Scout summer camp. It cost me a bomb, but it was worth it. Dan would take my kids and some of his other clients, take them with his instructors and all the medical personnel, and in one month, he would un-brainwash their heads. Boys will be boys without confusing their gender. The toxic situation in the West made them doubt themselves.

I had zero confidence in Western experts affirming the lunacy of arbitrary gender. They even called it gender-affirming care, pumping the kids with puberty blockers, cutting off body parts, bolting another, then training everyone else to pretend we don’t see they were mutilated, applauding them for their bravery like taking the knee, virtue signalling some shit nobody believed, and everyone pretended afraid of a social judgment. I was done with that shit, and so were my children.

If my sons were gay, I wouldn’t mind. We are who we are inside, but to teach them at the impressionable age that they could be girls and it would all be fine was crossing the line. I felt for the people with profound mental issues feeling trapped in the skin that practically itched, but to actively promote it as a lifestyle choice, change your sex like you change your shoes, broke my will to live. I rejected the place that rejected my life, and I left. I was done with the shit on the stick shoved down my throat, and a red-hot poker showed up in my asshole, telling me to take my medicine and keep quiet.

I always got worked up when it came to my children. I wanted what was best for them, to love and protect them, and there was no power in the world to tell me I wasn’t allowed. I made a plan to fix all of that. I had a plan to give them a better future. Anything short of one hundred per cent from my side, and I would have failed in my eyes as a parent. Ultimately, it came to life, and I didn’t care about mine when it came to the health and happiness of my children. And I wasn’t alone there.

Dan told me a story about situations similar to those in other families. His former clients got married and had their own children, only to be caught up in a toxic system, radicalising wives and confusing children. That’s how he got a bunch of other boys to join the camp, and their fathers were happy to pay any amount. It cost a bomb and was experimental, but I only laughed, as I was sure did the other fathers. Kingdom for a horse; world for your children.

***

“We would need you to move fast.” I watched the directors looking at me. I could see they were worried. Lamin did an incredible job working with the Dubai and offshore team from the New York office, supporting him with everything he needed. I had a burst capacity of two hundred and fifty people identified by my Indian delivery partner. We have already grown the team to fifty dedicated handpicked professionals, with all the senior engineers working directly with me in Dubai.

From my side, Lamin liaised with Owen and the team of my new client and discussed a range of operational issues. My lawyers talked to their lawyers and drafted the documents. They even visited our Lexington Avenue offices and video conferenced with me and my offshore team, noticing dozens of faces. We did not appear as a small enterprise unable to deliver on what we had promised. I even put the girls into the frame so we appeared as a diverse business, not just a geeky boy’s club.

The directors were nervous and wanted a meeting in person, so I jumped on a plane with Cassie and Faye, dressed in the best-tailored professional attire, looking exquisite. I introduced them to the board as my personal secretaries who travelled with me, took notes, and did anything I asked.

It is strange how the mind works sometimes. The board spent about an hour going through the same questions we went through at least ten times before, secretly throwing glances at the two incredible female specimens. All of them felt comfortable about what I had proposed in the end. I could understand that. They ran the company, but they were responsible for the shareholders. It was a massive publicly traded household name, and any reputational damage would make the heads roll somewhere. They desperately wanted to avoid that.

Nobody signs away billions of dollars to a company nobody had heard of unless they were desperate. Luckily, I had them by the balls, and Owen, their CEO, kept the tight ship, shutting down any descent before it surfaced. He personally stood to make enough cash in his back pocket to comfortably retire and live out his life as a rich man on a private Caribbean island somewhere.

It took us the rest of the week to iron out all the agreements, with hundreds of documents to sign and endorse: the NDAs, the SLAs, security, privacy, data sovereignty, and thousands more. Meanwhile, the IT teams signed off on the integration architecture. They exchanged data contracts, protocol specs, crypto keys, and a full load of everything else.

The hard part was getting all the insurance. It was going to be a massive system migration, and it took an incredible amount of documentation and third-party experts to assess our designs and readiness. On top of that, we were paying through our noses in premiums for that. If we broke any of our agreements or promises and the internal arbitration failed, the insurance company would cover our customers‘ losses, but all of it was still risky as hell.

“Nobody has ever done anything like this,” Owen said, drinking his scotch and smoking his cigar. He was a member of a private gentlemen’s club in New York and invited me for a nightcap.

“Why didn’t you do the audit?” I expected them to send a team of specialists to their suppliers. Owen laughed and patted my back with a cat-ate-the-canary smile.

“You know why, Jim. Of course, you do. Self-interest. I will make five per cent of the sale and get rid of the risk on the other end. Like you said. We’re in this thing together. Now tell me about those two babes.” It was my turn to laugh. Owen wasn’t a fool.

“Cassie and Shay are my girlfriends. Cassie is pregnant, and Shy trying.” The man whistled, shaking his head in disbelief.

“I don’t know how you do it.”

“Getting girls like that wouldn’t be so hard for a man with your charm and resources, but finding them is difficult. I’ll tell you what. Once all this is done, I’ll introduce you to someone.” Owen filled up our glasses and raised his.

“I’ll drink to that.”

We still had to do all the due diligence and perform the audit for the record’s sake, collect all the data and source code, and organise a proper handover. Going big bang approach on something as big as this was extremely risky. We planned to gradually redirect traffic and run the two systems in parallel for three months until we could decommission the old one, so someone had to go to the supplier and plan it all out. There was nobody I trusted to do that job but myself. It would be three months of hard work before it was done.

Cassie and Shay stayed in New York for a week, then flew back to London. I had a particular assignment for them. They moved into my apartment, telling me Amy’s three-bedroom was too big for them. They had the keys to Maybach to drive it around and go from place to place. Now they were salaried employees of my company. I opened a subsidiary in London, and the two would manage it.

I planned to stay for a month in New York and help Lamin set up the office. After all the documents were signed and ratified. I looked at our accounts and smiled. The company paid us the first tranche of five hundred and fifty million dollars, five hundred of which I rerouted to Dubai, leaving fifty in New York. This would be enough to run the office.

The contract was two and a half billion dollars paid in five instalments, then just over two hundred million monthly for operational costs. They were still making massive savings compared to the old supplier, and it was peanuts compared to what they made on top of it, which was over fifty billion in yearly turnover. It was unthinkable money, making our two billion in a year seem like a joke. The company was minted, and we became their key supplier. It was a perfect marriage of convenience. Owen was looking to make over a hundred million tax-free money, which was handed to him in bribes from the initial deal alone. Of course, he did his best, and I was right. It was the opportunity of a lifetime.

The following week, ten Indians arrived with their business visas, ready to integrate. Our client preferred in-person meetings, so I created a great collaboration space right there in our offices on Lexington Avenue. The first thing the guys did was extend the corporate DMZ so we could access their systems, and they could access ours. The team that arrived included the integration architects, specialists in configuring Cisco systems, and experts in edge computing. We were making magic.

Finally, in my third week, everything started working just fine. The customer teams and mine managed to completely integrate, and we could start the migration process. I went home that Friday feeling happy, exhausted and starved, but I couldn’t return to my hotel just yet. I flagged the cab down, and it took me to the airport, where I found Starbucks, sat down and waited.

About an hour later, I saw them and waved. Morgan and Bailey noticed me and squealed, running towards me like professional sprinters. They almost knocked me on my back, kissing and hugging me all over. The girls looked well. I kissed one, then another, to the dismay of all the conservative onlookers. I thought to myself, “fuck them.“

“What’s with all this?“ I asked them, pointing at the two large suitcases they rolled behind them. “I thought you were staying just for the weekend,“ I said, smiling. They squealed, hugging and kissing me again. The two started talking over each other. I couldn’t understand a thing they said. Hold on, calm down. Let’s talk about it over dinner. I didn’t have any food today. I am starved.“ More squealing and hugging ensued. I was just teasing the girls. They missed me terribly, as much as I missed them. They texted me and the girls all the time, but somehow, the stars didn’t align in the way we could have met before.

The taxi took us straight to the hotel and waited while I gave the suitcases to the bellboy and asked him to take them upstairs. Then I jumped back into the car, sitting between two ladies who wouldn’t stop kissing and fondling me until we arrived. I booked us a table at a fancy steakhouse, feeling so hungry I could eat a moose. They ushered us in and gave us aperitifs, then I turned to the girls, and we talked.

“It is terrible,“ Morgan complained. She got some work in films, mainly on B-roles and one time as a supporting actress. Sometimes, the dreams should stay where they were so you can keep dreaming about them and stay naive.

It was ironic that Morgan sacrificed everything to become a Hollywood actress who made enough money to pay her own bills, just to realise she wasn’t well-suited. When all the excitement and pomp wore off, she looked at what she was doing, and it was just another job. Like most things in life, the one per cent made all the money, while the rest kept spinning the plates, doing what they could to keep their heads above the water.

My girls didn’t help much, either. Morgan was a part of my close-knit inner circle, and she saw all the private photos the girls posted to each other, all the glitz, the glamour, and the carefree lifestyle. It was enough for Morgan to ask herself what she was doing with her life. She burst into tears as we waited for our steaks, hugging me tight, letting it all out. We all need to decompress sometimes, and Morgan had a sensitive soul inside. One thing I noticed after learning the hooker game was to pay attention to subtle emotional cues, a slight incongruence in body language.

“How about you? What’s your problem?” I turned to Bailey, and she burst into tears as well. I chuckled. Now that I made both girls cry, the world was good again, and we could eat. With all those women and two boys constantly up to some mischief, I got used to someone crying at any time of the day. In fact, for those weeks in New York alone, I started to feel a little disoriented without anyone sobbing anywhere. I missed all those female hormones.

When our food arrived, a confused waiter watched the girls dry their tears and sit on their chairs. It took them only a few bites before the waterworks stopped, and the world was a happy place again. The steaks were excellent. If there is one thing I loved in America, it was a perfectly done bison steak. I could eat it for dinner, lunch, and breakfast.

“We want to go dancing,” The girls whined after finishing their meals, including two servings of the desserts.

“I am exhausted today, but I can take you tomorrow.” I’ve never been to a dance club in New York.

“I hope you’re not too tired,” Bailey whispered into my ear, biting it a little. My cock hardened instantly, demanding release. It’s been the longest time without sex since I could remember.

“I want you to cum inside me,” Morgan added from the other side. Two naughty minxes had all of this planned. I had to clear my throat twice to raise my hand and speak.

“Check, please.” I could see a suppressed smile on the waiter’s face. The look on mine must have been entertaining. The eyes of the restaurant guests were glued to us as we walked out. A man wearing a business suit with two gorgeous ladies dressed to impress hanging on his arms never failed to amuse the onlookers.

We walked on the street for a while, attracting curious stares. The girls have never been to the Big Apple and wanted to get their first impressions straight. It was a lovely evening, warm with a clear sky. I enjoyed the walk and taking a breath of fresh air. No matter how nice my office was, I felt a little suffocated. I was grateful that the girls came when I called them. Perhaps we could save each other again.

We got into the hotel room with the girls laughing and giggling. Bailey, always the comedian, was making us laugh. The girls tugged at the strings of their dresses, and they peeled off and fell like red autumn leaves. I swallowed; I could smell them. The girls came to me and started tugging on my tie. I was shedding clothes as they pulled me to the showers, and I smiled.

Chapter 45 - The changeover

My plane landed in London in no time. I was getting used to intercontinental travel. I spent a week with Morgan and Bailey in New York, working in the office and exploring the city in our spare time. The hard part of the job was already done, and I hired both of them to be my eyes and ears and run the marketing department, liaising with the girls in Dubai.

One would wonder why we needed one, but it was all part of a much bigger strategy. The girls had already created our online presence, brochures, business cards, logos, and letterheads. If anyone looked at us now, they would think we were one of those institutional conglomerates with perfectly designed, insanely boring corporate identities. The girls in New York wanted to extend that principle and created an equally clean and unexciting online presence.

They would closely work with Lamin and support him as my trusted representatives. Lamin would take them to meetings and delegate tasks that took too much effort for him to handle alone. Unlike Lamin, the girls were uneducated, but they were intelligent, hard-working, and motivated. They wanted to help and devised a plan to ask if I would give them a real job. The whole acting and modelling thing wasn’t panning out the way they imagined, so they saw my invitation as an opportunity to change their lives.

Trust over experience, commitment over competence. It is said that good decisions come from making mistakes. Most corporations I’ve had a chance to interact with were incredibly risk-averse. They spent millions on error prevention and next to nothing on recovery. I liked to think the other way around and plan for the mistakes to be made, but limit them and have procedures to quickly recover from them. This results in a nimble, progressive style of management with people empowered to make their own decisions instead of pushing them up the management chain until the committee of the frightened incompetents decides it was too much risk for their appetite. The solution for corporate inertia was employee empowerment at every level of a structure limited by a perceived impact of damage before bumping it up a level.

It took me an hour to clear immigration and pick up the luggage. This was the part I hated the most about air travel, which depends on mass transit procedures, queuing, prodding, and herding us like cattle.

Cassie and Shay waited for me outside, instantly dispelling my irritation like sunshine does the mist of the night. I was starved and parched, refusing to stuff my stomach with heavily processed aeroplane food plied with cheap wine to help me replace one nasty aftertaste with another.

“You have to see this place,” the girls said, having found another fancy restaurant doing fusion cuisine for a taste palette used to cornflakes and hamburgers. I didn’t expect much, but I was pleasantly surprised. Instead of the usual gauche design and waiters pretending to speak French, serving pretentious middle-aged men wearing bow ties and women with raspy voices, the place looked cosy and friendly like a pub, and the menu had both spaghetti and steak, but they never touched.

It turned out the place was owned by a gay couple, both of them American, one from the Midwest and the other Italian, and both were chefs. Instead of doing the obvious thing, mixing nuts with berries, they chose to offer a bigger menu, keeping the food separate, catering to a broader customer base without resorting to cuisine nouvelle.

I had to give it to the girls; the food was excellent, the wine list extraordinary, and the entire ambience exquisite, although more for the company than the venue. Cassie and Shay kept gurgling like doves, happy and excited about their new life.

“You know what day it is?” Shay asked me, squeezing my hand. I kept a detailed calendar of things that mattered. Of course, I knew those were Shay’s fertile days. When she failed to fall pregnant on the first try, Shay took it as a kind of personal challenge, not wishing her child to be too far apart from Cassie’s. One would call it lunacy, but I found it cute. What goes insane these days? Is a sane person inside the asylum the sane one, or is it the other way around? Insanity is hereditary; you get it from your kids. This clearly applied to Shay, making her a little coo-coo but also very nice.

***

It felt strange to be back in the lobby of my old company. I was sitting on a plush sofa next to three serious-looking gentlemen from a management consultancy hired by my client. Ten minutes later, the office manager issued us temporary electronic passes and led us to the conference room.

“What are you doing here?” she asked me, recognising me immediately. Donna and I were never on good terms. She always thought I was strange, and I could see it in her eyes now. She was interested in me, but because of my prior clumsiness, I missed all her little flirting cues.

“I am the specialist forensic auditor hired for this job.” Her eyes popped, and her jaw slacked. Donna knew perfectly well what would happen. I almost chuckled, willing to bet she would take a day off or at least a long lunch break today just to get out of dodge. I would do the same if I were in her place.

“You know your way around. I booked you into 5-D,” she said and disappeared, probably to get an early start on her escape plan.

Five minutes later, five people joined us, and they stared at me like seeing a ghost. I introduced my three auditor colleagues to my former ones—the account manager, program administrator, technical sales manager, and two junior techies. They sent the B-team, where the B stood for “bullshit.” They were the warm and fuzzy feel-good sales guys whose only job was to say “yes” and ply the other side with alcohol and hookers. They didn’t expect to see me there.

A knock came on the door, and one of the canteen staff arrived with tea, coffee, and biscuits. I poured myself a cup and took one bite, waiting for the waitress to leave the office so we could start with the process.

All eyes were on me as I pulled out a thick yellow manila folder and took out a bunch of printed documents.

“To save us time, I prepared this questionnaire for you to answer.” All the technical questions exposed the systemic failure of their system. Without me on their payroll, they had no way to patch the live system. I knew the entire line of work was frozen as they didn’t even have a single mainframe specialist working on their side. Sooner or later, the whole system was doomed to fail, and at the moment, they had no capability to fix it.

Since I was the only one who knew how their internal algorithm worked, it would take them months, if not years, to reverse-engineer it. Of course, that would be impossible with a failed system. Without me, the company was looking at a widespread service outage.

When I explained this to the board of directors and my new clients, I could see the sheer panic rise in their eyes. Their former supplier could have easily taken them out of business. Sure, the lawyers would get involved, and somewhere, someone would determine the damages. By then, it would be too late for the board of directors and everyone else. A part of my pitch to them was complete transparency, including knowledge transfer. From a business continuity perspective, if my business were to fail, my clients could easily take over and run that part for themselves.

My former colleagues were shocked, looking at the paper. Mentally, I patted myself on my back. There was absolutely no way they could answer any of those questions without lying and passing this audit. If they failed, a range of contractual clauses would be invoked, which wouldn’t only cost them a client but also have numerous financial repercussions. Owen let me read the contract, and I laughed.

Owen was an intelligent man and a shrewd businessman. He was looking to recoup the money he spent on me through an arbitration leading towards the lawsuit. This way, we would make a pile of cash without costing his company anything. In a sense, my old company would be footing the bill for everything I did against them. I had to admit I developed a bit of an acquired taste for schadenfreude.

I watched the techies on the other side go through my document with frozen faces, but their eyes gave them up. They knew exactly how deep in the shit they were. There was absolutely no chance for any of them to bullshit their way out of that. They walked in smug and confident, and it made me want to laugh to see it all crumble away.

“Those are complicated questions. It would take us some time to prepare our answers.” This is where one of the guys on my side jumped in.

“That’s okay. Our forensic expert and the rest of us are happy to stay and work with you jointly to find the answers. Please remember that you are contractually obliged to provide them within seventy-two hours.” The guys on my side knew perfectly well how the game was played. They were briefed about the issues and were sent there to bring it all down. I knew Owen was out of reach for a planned holiday, skiing in the mountains without cell reception or internet access. He timed it perfectly so he couldn’t be contacted. I wanted to scream from laughter, watching their faces. A picture of a deer in the headlights came to my mind.

I finished the IT stuff and let the management consultants rip the B-team apart. I carefully instructed them who was likely to be there and informed them of all the holes and weaknesses. It wasn’t a meeting but bloodshed. Owen felt personally threatened, so he sent the consultants for a pound of flesh.

We broke up for lunch, and the account manager escorted us to the canteen. I was halfway finished with my meal when Janine approached me. She was Diarmaid’s personal secretary.

“Excuse me, Jim, but Diarmaid wants to see you in his office as soon as you finish.” I wiped my face with a napkin and pushed my plate away.

“Is he mad?” Janine shuddered, looked at me with her big brown eyes, then looked down.

“He is furious.”

We walked in silence. Janine made me sit in my chair for ten minutes, a standard play with Diarmaid. He was a creature of grand gestures that were ultimately meaningless like he would always come to the meeting five minutes late and make everyone start over. Diarmaid was a sadist of the worst kind. I once met his kids at the office party, and they looked petrified, especially the boy, Tom. I was willing to bet one would kill another. Everyone knew Diarmaid had a short fuse but was also a political animal. Whoever stood in his way ended up screwed. He was the kind of man who rarely lost his temper but held a grudge forever, and now I would meet him face to face.

“What the fuck do you think you’re doing?” Diarmaid started without even offering me a seat. I smiled, walked over, pulled my chair, and sat in it, staring into his eyes, and the man winced. It’s been long since anyone could win a staring contest with me.

“You should have paid me five million,” I said and chuckled. It was hard to control my amusement as I watched Diarmaid’s face turn purple.

“I should have fired you a long time ago.” I tapped my fingers. He was wasting my time.

“Is there a purpose to this conversation, or did you call me to vent? I don’t work for you anymore and don’t have to listen to your tantrums.” It was the wrong thing to say. Diarmaid caught himself at the last minute, just about as he was to throw an expletive. He probably remembered what happened to Dick and controlled his temper.

“This is a conflict of interest. I could take you to court for corporate espionage.” I couldn’t help laughing. He watched me with big eyes, unused to someone belittling him this way.

“I bet that giving me the CTO role looks very good now.”

“Fuck you, Jim. I will see you in court. I promise you that.” This got me annoyed. It was time to finish the charade. I sat up straight and took a deep breath. Our eyes connected, and I pitched my voice just perfectly.

“You will do nothing, fucktard. All this is your fault, and after I leave the office, you’ll do what you do best—scramble like a little pig to protect your ass from turning into bacon, then probably pin it on Dick and have him take the fall. Do you want to know why? Because you are a cockroach.” I could see Diarmaid’s hand tremble. His face was so red, I thought his head would blow like in the film Scanners.

“You were the one who insisted we void our contract. You were the idiot who signed the non-litigation agreement. Your fingerprints are all over this shit, you pompous cretin.” Diarmaid’s hands were almost white, how hard he was squeezing the seats of his chair. He was angry and wanted to lash out, but something in my eyes and the tone of voice kept him frozen.

“You will do nothing but allow us to conduct this audit, and you will lose your customer. This situation will cost you billions now. There will be no court. I am smarter than you, and you underestimated me. You are the idiot who didn’t want to give me the CTO position because I don’t know how to play the game. I am better at it than you, moron. I just have a distaste for it, and remember, I am a multimillionaire now with almost unlimited resources to go after you personally. I know you took bribes, and I can prove it, so be a good little boy and do what you’re told and stay the fuck away from me.” I showed him the finger, stood up, and slammed the door behind me.

Janine looked up at me with big eyes and a pale face. I smiled at her and winked. She almost giggled. Janine got the message that I wasn’t really angry or upset. She hated her boss more than anyone else, but it was her job, and she tried to tolerate it. I heard the intercom buzz, and Diarmaid screamed her name. She got up to enter his office with worry on her face. I caught her hand and stopped her for a moment.

“If you need a job, come work for me right here in London, and I’ll get you a better salary.” I slipped my business card into her pocket and smiled. She mouthed “thank you” and ran inside.

Everything happened just as I predicted. I was assigned a team of engineers, all from the same delivery partner. None of the original guys were left on the project to minimise the exposure to any conflict of interest. According to contracts, the delivery partner could work for competitors as long as the same people didn’t work on the competing projects, so all of them got replaced.

I didn’t need them but kept them busy anyway, copying files and transferring from one source control system to another. Over a thousand little libraries had to be migrated and documented, and terabytes of data had to be moved. After the terms of service of the original contract, their client, now mine, owned the entirety of the data and the source code. It would take a month to transfer it all, but my Dubai engineers working with ones onshore could take care of that. I employed everyone with a deep knowledge of the systems, and they were busy building a hybrid cloud infrastructure.

Just as expected, I never spoke to Diarmaid again. He kept away from me, and there was no talk about lawsuits or any such bullshit. Dick, who was placed on administrative leave, got blamed for everything as my direct line manager and fired. I would feel sorry for the man, but you can’t make an omelette without cracking a few eggs. This was the cost of corporate politics. When you rise up to the C-suite, you must expect it. I was the CEO of my company now, and I didn’t enjoy the job, but it was necessary. Someone had to do it.

We had a massive party after my return to Dubai. Tara and Dixie took the Hummer to pick me up, wishing to see me as soon as possible. I was away for six weeks, and they missed me. They stood at the arrivals security gate, tapping their feet and waving. As soon as they noticed me, the girls wanted to rush the barriers. It was all I could do to stop them from getting arrested. They hugged me hard, disregarding the onlookers, so I quickly moved them away to a more private place.

“I need coffee,” I croaked, and Dixie produced a Starbucks cup out of nowhere. It turns out my needs were predictable, even as I remained a mystery to everyone, including myself. The girls offered me to drive, knowing how much I liked my Hummer, but I was exhausted and preferred to frolic with Dixie while Tara took the steering wheel. Dixie cuddled with me while I watched the city pass by. It was good to be home.

Loud squeals greeted me as soon as I opened the doors. “Daddy, daddy,” Liam and Callum screamed, running towards me to hug me. I kissed my boys, missing them terribly despite our almost daily Zoom calls.

“I missed you so much, my lovelies,” I said, hugging them tight like I was never going to leave them again. The girls stared at me with teary eyes, and I opened my arms, calling to them. “I love all of you too, my darlings,” we ended in a group hug lasting at least ten minutes until everyone had a chance to kiss me and get a good squeeze.

“Come, come, we prepared a meal.” It was delicious. Those cooking lessons paid off with dividends. I ate like a pig and ate some more. The girls laughed with pride. There was just something deeply cultural in all of them, responding to feeding their man.

“We’ve got some news for you,” Neneh began after the girls took away plates and served desserts.

“Mmm-hmm,” my mouth was too stuffed with tiramisu to speak, and all of them giggled.

“I’m pregnant,” Neneh announced.

“And so am I,” Paige added. I almost choked, trying to say something. Instead, I stood up and opened my arms to hug them.

“I love you so much, my darlings.” I kept kissing them all over. Liam and Callum felt left out, so they ran up to us to extend their hugs. I squatted down to their level and spoke to them.

“Do you know what it means?” Both of them nodded.

“We are going to get more brothers or sisters,” Callum proudly exclaimed. I hugged them tight.

“That’s right, my lovelies. You will have a huge family.” Dan did a fantastic job with the kids. I got separate reports from him and Tara every day. After a month of doing the drills and talks with child development experts and psychologists, all that pile of woke bullshit that Tina spoofed them was gone. I strictly forbade anyone to play with any child television program made in the twenty-first century. Disney was off the menu, and so was Netflix. The kids were not allowed smartphones or access to the internet. The only sanctioned company was Hanna-Barbera before it got sucked into the Warner Bros conglomerate. My kids knew how to read, and that’s what I promoted. They were allowed television only thirty minutes per day.

Neneh was the strictest of teachers, having had firsthand experience with what happens when you go against nature. She read every book before giving it to the children and sat in every class as we homeschooled them. Neneh even went so far as to vet their friends, took the boys to the mosque, and made them pray every day. She took Arabic classes and had the boys learn how to speak and read the Quran. Neneh wasn’t going to let the boys even think about anything effeminate.

She met and interviewed a group of mothers and their families and chose three best friends for the boys of the same age. I don’t know how she managed to find a former Taliban fundamentalist family that migrated for work to Dubai, and I didn’t care. I just knew there were no transgender Taliban out there. I was hoping that by providing the boys with the contrast between ultra-conservative and progressive conservative values, I could lead them to a healthy place.

Dan told me I didn’t have to do that and that the boys were fine, but I wanted to set a precedent and build a proper learning environment for all my other children. I swore to myself I would never drop the ball again. It was strange and possibly contradictory to be a proponent of conservatism while living the life we lived. I didn’t want my kids to be brainwashed one way or another. I wanted them to be open-minded and know the difference between right and wrong.

There was absolutely no way I would accept my boys being told they could be girls or taught the joys of gay sex. The progressive liberal left could collectively get on their knees and suck my dick, then turn to each other and fuck themselves. I didn’t want any of that shit in front of my kids, even if it meant I had to move to Africa somewhere. It wasn’t going to happen. Not on my watch, ever.

If someday my kids grow up and figure out they are gay or something else, god bless them. I wouldn’t love them any less, but I wasn’t going to allow a group of perverts in the government to use my children for their political experiments. In a way, I felt sorry for the entire LGBT community. Most of them just wanted to live, love and have the same rights as the others, but someone somewhere saw an opportunity to subvert that and turn it into a weapon against my children. This crossed the line.

All my girls knew about my stance, and they supported it. Most of them suffered some sort of violence or neglect from their broken, dysfunctional families if you could even call it that. We were a family and a tribe, close-knit, tightly integrated, loving, and caring for each other, and none of us wanted to do anything to break that. Instead of being jealous and having arguments, the women found friendship and love in each other.

Of course, it was a little hypocritical because all of my women were bisexual, but they were adults, able to make up their own minds, and they were careful to never show that side in front of the children. In every family, the kids should be sacred.

Our strange living arrangement became a beacon of hope and a blueprint for success. The girls loved me as much as they loved each other, and they got what they had missed and desired their entire lives—a family of people who wouldn’t judge them, who would lift them up instead of drag them down. We all wanted that. I never knew what it was to have a dad. All of us were from broken homes, and together, we made something incredible.

It was unintuitive to think that having multiple women would bring out the balance, but that’s what happened. The girls were never alone and never without someone they could trust. There was never one person washing the dishes and never one person raising the children. It was a community living of a different kind. I might have been the head of my tribe, but we were all equal.

“I have a surprise for you,” I told my boys and my girls. “Tomorrow, we’re going to Abu Dhabi to take a boat ride through the mangrove forest.” Everyone squealed. The girls were trying to get me to take them to this world’s wonder, a desert converted into a forest with rivers and lakes of immaculate water. Who on earth even heard of that? Dubai has the tallest building on the planet, but it paled compared to the mangrove forest. While the West was destroying itself with political misadventures, the other countries cared for what they had and nurtured the land.

I used every opportunity to spend as much quality time with my family as possible. Amy started showing quite nicely and needed a lot of attention. The girls helped her make amazing pictures and videos and posted them to her followers. She had over two million of them by then, and companies were begging her to do some product placement. Naturally, Amy ignored them. She wasn’t in this for money but attention, ever as much of an exhibitionist as ever. Most of my girls got to sunbathe in the nude on the roof of the house, where Neneh had contractors create a little lounge with a bar and shade.

Most of my attention during the workday was focused on getting the services up, and after four weeks of testing, we went live. The initial Terraform and Ansible code I wrote was extended and improved by Indian engineers. We could press a button now, come into the office the next day, and have an entirely new scalable environment built for us, together with access points through a private VPN. All we had to do on our side was install the TLS certificates on our office servers; voila, we were connected. It worked like magic, and we stress-tested it to bits. Thanks to my distributed algorithm, the damn thing scaled like crazy.

This was the key to my proposal. I wrote a unique algorithm that separated and parallelised the workload over multiple commodity hardware running Kubernetes instances. The result was staggering. I hoped we would be within standard mainframe tolerance levels, but after tweaking the algorithm, I got it to work at three times the speed. Not only did we satisfy the non-functional requirements, we blew them out of the water. There was ample space for growth, and we could onboard other businesses.

I even installed our own software that randomly messes up the connectivity or reboots the servers. It was based on Chaos Monkey and Simian suite, so when we do the testing, we can see what happens when things turn to shit. The techies from the client side were rubbing their hands and licking their lips. The board was ecstatic with the reports, and Owen patted himself on the back.

The next tranche of money landed in the five hundred million for migration and two hundred for the operation. I pushed it all into Dubai. We were flushed with cash, which made me move to the next step of my plan. It would require a lot of flying around, and I was done with the commercial flights.

I took a lease contract for a large executive Airbus ACJ 350 XWB, the top of the line in corporate flying at a measly three hundred and fifty million apiece. The salespeople were salivating. When they told me I had to wait for a year, I hung up on them. The manager called me back in twenty minutes, apologising. It turns out they found one that was brand new, ready to fly, had all its certificates, and was good to go.

The plane landed at Dubai Airport, and I had to inspect it. It had a boardroom, a lounge for sitting and drinking tea, a bar and a restaurant, a sitting room, and even a full-blown bedroom. All of it was exquisitely decorated with the most modern materials, leather and silver, mixed with white and brown mahogany. The girls couldn’t stop screaming and running around it like insane. All of them insisted I take them on my travels. Every single one of them wanted to join the mile-high club, flying in style.

When I saw the brochure, I loved how it looked. All the executive planes I saw on film or the internet looked similar, with some sort of a plain cabin with few plush seats. Not this one. The aircraft was built like a modern five-star hotel room. It was the highest form of decadence. After seeing the girls’ reaction, I knew there was no way for me to fly a commercial. Even the carpets and lights were of incredible design. Every single thing on the plane was put there to awe and impress. It was the ultimate “fuck you” to the boys in their Lambos and Ferraris, the ultimate perversion of opulence, a veritable finger in your face. I wondered for a moment what kind of pervert would even dare buy one, and then it dawned on me. I was the one.

The plane was the ACJ 350-1000, slightly bigger than the nine-hundred series, just over two hundred feet long. It was the less desirable model for the price difference. The company had a dispute with an existing customer who paid the deposit and then tried to pull back from the sale and order the cheaper one. I also wanted the cheaper one, but when the sales director told me I could get this one the same day, I made up my mind, pressed a few buttons and the agreements were signed.

This plane changed things dramatically. I could travel comfortably, work and sleep, and even shower, and I didn’t have to do it alone. The best part of it, I never had to rent a car again. I could just load mine into the cargo hold and use it as I like, and I would never have to go through the baggage and immigration bullshit. The plane would land, and by the time I disembarked, my car with my clothes would be waiting for me.

The company was kind enough to find two incredible pilots with decades of commercial and military flying experience. Finding the flight attendants was an easy task. I went to the recruitment company and asked them to send me the list of the youngest ones who recently completed their training. I chose the two prettiest ones who worked as fashion models in their spare time, a redhead and a brunette, then had a local designer make their uniforms look so sexy that they were borderline obscene. The girls said nothing; they were just happy to fly in this incredible machine. It took me a month to get everything ready, but the plane was finally here, fully staffed, and my girls were going nuts, exploring the place in front of two pairs of jealous stewardesses’ eyes.

It would be a hard six months spent mostly in the air, flying between New York, London, and Dubai, and the plane would make my life easier. I was going to take the New York and London public. My lawyers shook their heads, telling me six months was ambitious, doubting it could be done, but I stubbornly refused to listen.

They helped me hire the right consultancy for the assessment, financial audit, and legal and regulatory compliance while I busied myself sourcing the right investment bank to be my underwriter. I already had a great legal firm representing me, and they recommended the accounting equivalent, a household name that knew its way around public companies.

The only thing that would be left in the end was the SEC filing and the due diligence, as well as working with the underwriter to get the set offer price. My biggest job was to onboard the early investors and sign contracts with other clients to bump up the assessment and raise our starting share price. Luckily, I knew the right people who could help me with that.

While I was busy with the technical stuff, the girls would be flying around all the time doing roadshows and marketing. I hired a specialist marketing consultancy to shadow them, prepare everything the girls needed, guide and teach them exactly what to do, where to go, whom to meet, and what to say.

“Who wants to go for a ride?” The girls started jumping around, squealing like crazy. None of them wanted to miss the opportunity for an incredible adventure. It took the pilot twenty minutes to file the flight plan and get all clear. Then we were pushing off into the air, and the girls cheered.

Liam and Calum were glued to the windows, looking out. They loved flying, and as soon as the plane levelled up, they enjoyed everything the plane had to offer, especially the inflight entertainment. I pulled out my laptop and connected to the internet. We had WiFi in every corner of the aircraft. I never flew in such luxury, and neither did the girls.

The flight attendants brought us some drinks, and the boys approached them, curious to find out who the girls were and if they were also their aunties. I smiled, thinking how one never knew and promised myself that if ever I got more girls, I would recruit them for a specific purpose, like flight attendants to staff my plane. When I started my changeover, I was starved of attention, especially the female kind. Over time, as I grew to know and love my girls, the others became less interesting. To bring someone else into my inner circle would mean exposing them to people I loved and my children.

Over time, the bar raised itself to the point that I wasn’t even interested unless a girl was an incredible genetic specimen—we are talking eights or nines on the M-scale—or if she could be trusted to fulfil a specific role in my tribe; otherwise, she’s not worth the investment.

It was a six-hour flight, and after the initial excitement, the girls calmed down. Tara was the first one to figure out that the plane had a fantastic bedroom inside, and the bed could be used for all sorts of purposes in addition to rest. She approached me and cuddled into my arms, gurgling gently into my ear.

“Master, I want to fuck.” She looked at me with her innocent eyes, fluttering her eyelashes. Tara knew me well and learned a trick or two from Amy along the line. I could never refuse the horny little daddy’s girl when she looked at me like that.

“Ah well, fuck it. Let’s go join that club,” I said, and all the women laughed. Dixie was turning into an outright comedian. She cupped her hands around her lips and nose to mimic the sound of the in-flight announcement system.

“Ladies and gentlemen, we are cruising at an altitude of ten thousand feet. Please expect some turbulence.” Even the stewardesses burst into laughter.

I woke up with a start. After testing every position mid-flight, I closed my eyes and drifted away, enjoying the feel of high-thread-count linen and thick satin covers. They slithered around my body as I breathed, imagining I was in heaven, riding the clouds. We were high above them, going full speed, with the enchanting hum of the engines lulling me to sleep.

“We are about to land,” Tara said. I quickly took a shower and put on my clothes. Minutes later, we were all seated and strapped in, looking through the portholes at the tropical paradise below.

The girls started squealing even before we landed. The cars waited for us next to the runway. When the doors opened, a gust of hot, wet air hit us, so different from Dubai, smelling of an exotic fruit cocktail. It took us some time to get to Belle Mare, all spent in a daze, breathing in with our full lungs, getting drunk on nature’s essence. The hotel staff awaited us outside, almost bowing to the ground, expecting its high-rolling customers.

Within minutes, we checked in and unpacked, changed into our colourful bathing suits, and tested the waters. The white coral sands spreading from one infinity to another cuddled our toes as we walked into the waters. None of us had had such an experience before; it was awe-inspiring, almost spiritual in its nature.

The girls swam and giggled, playing like children in a game of sharks. It was the heaven of heavens, with all the luxury and opulence of Dubai already forgotten. The water was perfect, as were the sun, the view, the scent of the air, and, to top it all, the hotel. It was an opulent, luxurious place, surrounded by the beach and a tropical forest on the other side. Every one of us was taken aback, feeling like we had stumbled upon a garden of Eden.

The hotel wasn’t the newest type, and if I looked closer, its age started to show in places, but none of it detracted from the experience. On the contrary, it added to its charm, feeling lost at the end of the world, surrounded by nature. None of us noticed the passage of time, too consumed with the beauty of life. Belle Mare, they called the area “the beautiful sea,” translated from French. The name didn’t do it justice as we all stood in awe, watching the sunset. One could be born, live his life, and die without seeing a sunset like that. It would be a wasted life. I felt privileged, and the girls cried. By fate or cosmic accident, we had found one place on this planet to feel perfect happiness.

The hotel staff took care of us, bringing out chairs and tables right on the beach, together with grills, and started the fire, intent on feeding us next to gentle waves with torches for light and quiet music fitting the ambience. My mouth watered, smelling grilled lobster while the waiters filled our glasses. I lifted mine, toasting to everyone, and the girls squealed in perfect happiness. It occurred to me, right at that moment—I had sought an adventure and found a new life. One thing was certain, beyond any doubt. We will remember this holiday for the rest of our lives. The only question remained: how do I convince everyone to leave this place?

***

It turned out that purchasing the plane was one of the best investments I ever made. The Dubai girl enlisted one of the Indian software developers to create a private phone app that could be downloaded on our family intranet. I almost died from laughter when Amy tried to teach me how to connect to our family Office365 account and access Microsoft Teams and Sharepoint, which had everything from calendars to recipes.

The app would connect to exposed calendar web services, treating the plane as one of the meeting rooms. The girls could book flights here and there while the app would calculate the most fuel-effective days. If someone went to New York, it would be better to plan with someone who is going to London. Lamin hitched a ride more than once, and now that we had a private plane, we could fly directly to Africa. No more layovers, no more nonsense. It cost us a lot of money, but it was worth every cent. Besides, the New York company paid for all of it, claiming it as a legitimate travel expense for tax purposes.

Days, weeks, and months flew by, and we worked day and night. Three months into the program, we cut ties with the UK, and my old firm became history, with their ancient mainframes decommissioned. My company was making two hundred million easily every month, with expenses totalling only about ten million, including delivery partner consultancy fees, offices, and cloud servers. We were massively profitable. Dubai was, but not New York. I structured the company in such a way that most of the money ended up in Dubai, where I could simply walk into the bank and transfer all the profits tax-free into my personal account.

The major expense in New York was all the lawyers, consultants, and other parasites who were commuting through the company, contracts, and business plans. I signed up three more companies to start next year, each netting about a hundred million a month. We were talking about incredible numbers, thousands upon thousands of transactions per second, but my algorithm proved to have almost linear scalability, which meant we could grow it to vast numbers.

The girls did an incredible job going on roadshows, presenting our pre-IPO packs, and offering shares at discounted prices. I was already down to about seventy per cent ownership of the New York company while retaining one hundred per cent ownership of Dubai. Investment firms, banks, venture capitalists, and other sharks could smell the blood in the water. They bombarded my team with all sorts of unsolicited offers. The demand was so huge and coming from everywhere so fast that the accountants had to revise the share price almost every month.

Hiring Morgan and Bailey was one of the best decisions I made. The two girls were like hungry wolves, unaware of what they were capable of. They focused all their efforts and drive on winning the fight, and within just three months, they became outright ballbusters. Of course, Lamin helped them. He hired a small group of business advisors to support the two girls and teach them what to do in the real world, and they were insatiable. The two had an equal thirst for success as for knowledge.

After three months, everything accelerated. The damn company crossed some threshold, and everyone wanted a piece. I kept selling my shares and putting the money aside, and suddenly, I had a board of directors sent to me by the investment companies. It was all I could do to control the place, running from meeting to meeting, saying “no” to everyone.

The shares split and split, and at the end of the fifth month, I was a minority holder with only about ten per cent of company shares left. The investors traded amongst themselves and speculated. I had to fight off someone from the board almost every day. All of them united against me, calling me incompetent.

“You are a techie, not a management type. We want to hire a real heavy-hitter,” they said. I was the biggest thorn in their side, refusing to run the company as the investors wanted. It was the same old story as with Diarmaid and my old company. The money guys were made of the same cloth, and I didn’t belong to their club, but I was too smart to just use as an idiot. I knew the game they played. The investors saw a great opportunity to make money and swooped in to take it away from me.

“Why do you need a plane? What are those expenses?” They went on and on. It was exhausting. I used to run my company as I saw fit, but suddenly, there were so many rules. We hired so much middle management that everything became a problem. Nobody could make any decision, no matter how small. The parasites infested my brainchild, and they were giving me haemorrhoids.

It wasn’t fun anymore. Even Amy quit after getting into a fight with one of the new know-it-all idiots. She was about to give birth and was highly hormonal. The New York company became a cesspool of politics. Even Lamin came to me a couple of times, begging me to release him from the job so he could become my driver again.

Coming up to the IPO day, the pressure became unbearable. Morgan and Bailey would come to me every day and cry in my arms to release stress. Even sex didn’t help. We were all pissed off, nervous, physically and mentally exhausted. I knew all this would happen, so I insisted we push for the six months. I would probably kill myself if I had to endure it for a whole year.

The board was screaming at me, threatening lawsuits and all sorts of other shit, demanding my resignation, promoting some other guy for the CEO position. I met the smug asshole, and the stench permeated. He was a Teflon-coated and lubricated turd of a man. I had to count my fingers to check they were all there after shaking his hand.

“Now is not the time. Let me get us through the IPO, and I will step down as CEO.” This seemed to placate them. I understood the investors in some way. They invested millions into my company and didn’t care about it. All they wanted was their big payday, the return on investment once we go live.

The day finally came, and we hit the stock market. There was a public announcement, and everyone started trading like crazy. I took all the Dubai money I borrowed and bought stock straight away, then sold it at a higher price, repeating the process over and over again. I wrote a program to do this automatically for me, following a different algorithm and using the same software infrastructure to make an incredible amount of decision-making and trades repeatedly. When the stock started to slow down, I would use cash to buy it at a much higher price. It would push the ticker up, and all other investors would buy, sell, and buy.

My program made whale-like trades, pushing the stock up throughout the day. Up and up we went. I was losing cash, but my math was correct, and the algorithm could make real-time decisions. Predicting the stock market is a pipe dream, but predicting the stock price of only one company you control is actually not that hard, provided that you have enough cash.

Ten minutes before the end of the trading day, the algorithm sold all my positions, and I sold the last ten per cent of the stock I owned at an incredible price. That’s where everything stopped and plateaued. The trading day ended, and I was out of there.

The first thing in the morning when the management walked into the office, they received my resignation letter. According to my terms and conditions of employment that my own lawyers drafted, I could do that without notice. I paid myself a ten million dollar bonus for leading the company through the IPO and fired Lamin as COO, giving him a five million dollar severance.

I fired all the girls that worked for the company, paying each a one million dollar severance as well. My plane lease was transferred to the Dubai office, and I was out of New York. The board called me in a panic, failing to understand why I did that.

“This is what you wanted, isn’t it? You’ve chosen your CEO, now have it.”

“We wanted you to stay as our head of engineering,” they said, and I laughed.

“Sorry, I’m not interested. I wanted to be the CEO of my own company, but you ruined it for me. Find yourself another person.” I said my polite goodbye, and we were done. Some emails followed, asking me why I fired the COO and practically the entire marketing department. I wrote back to explain that now that they had the new CEO, he would want to make his own team, so I saved him the trouble of firing everyone. The marketing department was optional as they were hired to get us across the line.

Undoubtedly, they checked whether I was allowed to do that, just to read it in the bylaws of the company and employment contracts. I could pretty much do what I wanted and not be liable for it. I made sure my lawyers were explicit about it but hid it inside legal jargon and the small print.

The new CEO took up the reins. The share price dipped a bit, but nothing significant. It quickly became painfully evident that the shares were at their maximum, and they would stay there for a while, but there would not be a massive climb that would allow the investors to speculate. They locked their cash and had to hold it for a while or use it as collateral to free up other financial instruments. They didn’t lose much but didn’t gain much either. The trades were too fast on the first day, thanks to the program I wrote. I specifically designed it to make trades unintuitive so a human brain or another algorithm wouldn’t be able to catch up with it and figure out what I was doing.

Of course, the traders had their own computers, but none of them could predict that I was willing to make a loss to recover it in the final trade. I was just propping up my ten per cent before I sold it, resulting in zero on the investment account, but that wasn’t my money anyway. I effectively used the investor’s cash to artificially prop up the share value, so I can sell my ten percent at the best moment.

Chapter 46 - What dreams may be

It took the New York company some time to figure out the new management and replace the Indian software engineers with those locally sourced. Only then did they realise that the New York company was permanently tied to the one in Dubai through contracts.

Their first instinct was to bring all the software in-house before they figured out that the algorithm used was never a part of the deal. I kept it as a personal intellectual property registered to my company in Singapore and exclusively licensed to the Dubai company on a per-transaction basis. I got paid a fraction of a cent for each transaction made using my algorithm, paid monthly, which, based on the current transaction volume, summed to just over twenty million dollars per year.

There was no way around it. This was the key to how the entire system worked. Everything else was just the infrastructure they could manage in the US or elsewhere, but the Dubai company would only sublicense the algorithm with the rest of the service.

The new owners had it legally tested, and it failed upon reading. All this information was inside the contracts and the details within reams upon reams of technical documents nobody ever bothered to read. That’s always the problem with those super-smart money guys. They know everything, and they are above everyone. I was always just a simple IT guy who paid attention to details.

“Those are wonderful. I must have more.” Salvatore smiled, having another date filled with honey and dipped into white chocolate with golden Arabic writing on top. Those were the most expensive dates I could find, custom-ordered from my favourite shop in Dubai.

“I will make sure you do, Count Conti.” The man laughed, taking another sip of coffee and looking at the sea from the terrace we sat on. It was a little-known fact that Salvatore Conti was actually a count connected to European nobility, the oldest of the old money.

“You did well for yourself, my friend,” he said, patting my knee, laughing. “Three and a half billion dollars, if I am correct.” He was a smart man.

“Not as well as you did, my count.” The man was a gambler, but a safe one. He had a nose for money like nobody I’ve ever met before. When we first met, I told him about my plan, and he loved the idea and backed me with ten million dollars. He spoke to his friends in The Society and elsewhere, and they were the leading investors helping me prop up the shares. They made tens of billions speculating on share prices, which I controlled. Even all those multi-billion contracts I signed were with the companies they owned. I knew that all those sales and contracts would evaporate for this reason or another.

The new CEO would have a tough time keeping the customers, and I was willing to bet they would replace him within a year after he cost the company billions in unrealised sales. That’s when the shares would turn to shit, and Owen’s company would buy it out cents on the dollar, cutting their expenses from two hundred million per month to about a quarter of that. Owen would get praised for that, make millions in executive bonuses, and retire somewhere, happy and loaded.

I heard loud giggling and turned to the side. Cassie was waddling towards me, heavily pregnant, followed by Shay, barely moving her belly. Cassie carried a boy, and Shay was laden with twins.

“I see you’ve been busy,” Salvatore joked. “Remember, son. You live only once. Children are the only real wealth a man can have, and I am sure with beauties like that, they will be perfect.” The old leech always had a thing for pretty ladies.

The girls sat down, and Salvatore’s butler appeared with a selection of fruits and juices.

“Would you care for a refreshment?” The butler asked with a perfect English accent. The girls huffed a few times to catch their breath, then thanked the man, taking fresh ruby red orange juice and some fragrant tea. The old count found all of that amusing. He sat there smiling, twirling his moustache.

“Did anyone tell you that you look like the Monopoly guy?” Shay innocently asked, and the man exploded into laughter. Shay never knew how close she came to the truth. The old man Conti loved to play real-life Monopoly, and he won all the time.

Nobody knew how much cash the man had. Nobody dared to ask, but everyone knew he was connected to the high heavens and welcomed into royal circles where no mere commoner was allowed. The word on the street was that Salvatore financially propped up several European monarchs. I was willing to bet this was true and that he did it because it amused him to have a royal title. What’s a royal title without royals around? The man was merely protecting himself from becoming a commoner.

“The view is so beautiful here,” Cassie said, looking at the sea past the terrace.

“It is even better at the apartment,” Salvatore reminded her of the incredible place we stayed at and the pool on the roof we never tried.

“God, yes. It is so beautiful. I could live there,” Shay added, and I joined Salvatore in laughter.

“I bet you could,” he said, finding all of it too amusing. “How was your flight?” The girls started talking about the plane, promising to show it to him. The man could easily afford such an expense, but he rarely flew, and keeping a plane, pilots, and the flight crew was too much of a hassle.

“How did you get here?” The girls told Salvatore that one of the stewardesses drove them. They took a Maybach from London and brought it to Monaco. None of us had any immediate plans to visit London anytime soon. I talked with the manager of the car company and paid off the loan early.

The first thing I did when I made my money was stop any long-term haemorrhaging, pay off all loans, and complete the house sale in Dubai. We were in the clear.

“You must be tired. Let me take you to the apartment.” We followed the old count to the car, and he joined us inside, admiring how roomy and bright it was. The stewardess drove us around right into the centre of Monte Carlo, then into the basement of the apartment block, from where we took the elevator to the top floor.

The place was, as I remembered it, regularly cleaned and maintained, a perfect luxurious living space with an incredible view of the coastline.

“This is as expensive a place as it gets,” Salvatore said. “Probably the most expensive real estate on the planet, going by price per square footage.” He took us from room to room again, showing us everything as if we could forget. Salvatore gave me the keys, the key cards, and a yellow envelope full of papers.

“What about the other thing?” I asked.

“Ah, yes, right.” He pulled another envelope from his coat pocket and handed it to me. I checked the contents inside, and everything was perfect, just like we agreed.

“I’ve gotta be going now. Have fun and enjoy yourself, and don’t forget to visit sometime.” The old man made his way down, through the lobby, and out where his car waited.

“You know what? I could use a nice cup of coffee.” The girls jumped to make it while I sat down, enjoying the view in the distance, the sea and the ships. It looked incredible. The girls joined me on the balcony while the stewardess returned to the plane to fetch the kids. The boys were sleeping when the plane landed, and the girls didn’t want to drag them around until we were home.

“I love this place,” Shay said and sighed. I couldn’t agree more. It somehow resonated. It wasn’t the riches and opulence, but something else like a perfume in the air, the sense of freedom unlike anywhere else. The people born here were blessed. It was a perfect safe haven from the idiocy, a little traditional place inside Europe, cosy and protected by France, not part of the EU, but kind of part of it. I loved places like this, sitting on two chairs, reaping all the benefits without the investment.

I could smell the gentle breeze carrying the salty scent of the sea, and I closed my eyes. The girls were already on cloud nine. There was indeed something special in this place, and not just the price; it enchanted me and made the time pass faster.

The sound of the bell made me jump. Was it already an hour? I looked at my empty cup of coffee. When did I drink it? The girls were semi-catatonic, so I got up and opened the doors. The two stewardesses came in, bringing the kids, and they ran into my arms, squalling, “Daddy.”

Six months have passed since I had enough time to spend with my children. The boys grew like weeds, and they were so big now. Callum had just turned seven, and Liam was almost eight now. Ever since I took them from their mother, both of them blossomed. Dan did a fantastic job bringing them back into the boys‘ camp. Whatever he did was incredibly effective, and I had an idea I wanted to talk to him about, but first things first. I wanted to spend some time with my kids.

The pregnant girls were too tired to waddle to the restaurants. The trip and the pregnancy wore them out. I already made different plans, and twenty minutes later, I heard the bell again. A man in his late thirties came in, carrying two large bags full of groceries.

“This is Gaspard. He used to run a three-star Michelin restaurant in Paris before it went bankrupt during lockdowns. He couldn’t keep the staff, and it all went tits up.”

“C’est la vie,” the man said and laughed, unpacking the groceries in the kitchen. Gaspard was a curious character, an epicure who liked nothing more than to serve a good meal. He used to serve in the French Foreign Legion when he was younger, from which he returned with shot nerves. Cooking and reading were the only two things that could calm him down, so he went to cooking school, and it turned out he was gifted.

Gaspard liked to play classical music while he cooked, so he shooed us away to go somewhere else until he called. The boys were still jet-lagged, so I took them to the bedroom and let them sleep it off, knowing there would be hell to pay later when they started going nuts like gremlins after midnight.

Cassie and Shay barely made it upstairs. The roof of the building was exquisitely decorated, looking like some sort of tropical beach cabana, with a large pool in the middle, wooden sunbeds on its sides, and one covered sitting area with matching rattan sofas and glass tables if someone just wanted to sit outside, enjoy the incredible view, drink coffee, work on a laptop, or just hang out with friends.

There was a self-standing changing room that doubled as a bathroom and a covered area with an outdoor built-in barbecue, fridges, and storage for utensils and plates. Whoever designed the place perfectly married utility with style, resulting in a picturesque rooftop oasis in the middle of Monte Carlo. It was impossible to find a property more central than that.

Cassie and Shay shed off their clothes and flopped into the pool like two pregnant sperm whales, finally able to catch their breath as water buoyancy released their spine muscles. It looked funny from afar, but what would I know about being pregnant? As much as the girls loved the experience, they swore an oath to get their revenge. They were tired and hormonal, flipping from laughter to tears like a bipolar bear inside a washing machine.

I quickly undressed and joined the two in the water. They swam towards me, and we embraced. Then, the two lovely ladies cried. It was hard for them to carry babies, travel the world, and work in the office. We all had scars from the past six months, but it was all over.

The girls were shocked when they received the texts from their bank accounts that a million dollars had been deposited. Nobody expected it, and I didn’t tell anyone. Lamin was jumping to the high heavens from happiness.

“What do I do now, boss?”

“You can do what you like. You are a multimillionaire.” He looked at me, a bit lost and deflated, then perked up and smiled.

“If you don’t mind, I would like to take a couple of months off in Africa to help my family; then, I would like to return and be your bodyguard and driver.” It was a good life, and Lamin missed it. He was smart enough to realise there was nowhere to go but downhill. Lamin was the chief operating officer of a successful multibillion-dollar business, and in six months, he burned out. He had enough stress to last him a lifetime and enough money so he didn’t have to work again. He could return to Africa or stay anywhere, get married, have a family, and do whatever he liked, but he missed being my driver, hanging out with my girls, reading books, and studying.

“I think I want to join an art college.” I patted the man’s back. Over time, he became my good friend.

“You are always welcome, Lamin.” We hugged before he took off to visit his parents.

It was just us now in Monaco and Dubai. London was gone, and so was New York. We pulled out from there and left the place alone. I kissed Cassie, and then I kissed Shay, patting their bellies.

“You know how much I love you?” The girls nodded and snuggled in closer, and like that, we floated for a while until I went for a swim up and down to reactivate my muscles. I did what I could over the past six months, but I slacked a little on exercise. I was committed to doing better and forcing myself back into shape.

As I swam to the front of the pool, I noticed the two stewardesses standing there, watching me and my girls with burning jealousy in their eyes. It wasn’t the malicious kind but the wishful type. My girls befriended them and saw them as extended family members, like Iqbal and his family or anyone else we regularly interacted with. The stewardesses got to see our Dubai house when we invited them for dinner, and they almost choked watching the luxury we lived in.

When they visited Monte Carlo, their heads spun. They landed the most ostentatious plane in the world in the most ostentatious city. Now they were invited for dinner at the most ostentatious apartment they’d ever seen, to have a meal prepared by a Michelin-awarded chef just because I wanted it.

This wasn’t just a perverse display of wealth but a lifestyle far and above any they could even imagine. People hear about supercars lining up Monaco streets, but none of those rich people transported their Maybach inside their own luxury Airbus like one does luggage. It was beyond decadent.

“Don’t you feel hot up there?” I asked, and the stewardesses nodded. “Why don’t you join us for a swim?” Their faces instantly turned several shades of red darker.

“We don’t have swimming suits, sir,” Erin, the brunette one, said. Tess, the redhead with the cutest freckles, just remained silent, staring into my eyes.

“Do you see any of us wearing them?” The girls shook their heads, and I swam away to do my laps, letting them do what they wanted. I didn’t particularly care. On my swim back, I saw the two quickly undress and smiled. They were tall and slim with perfect curves. No wonder they used to work part-time as fashion models. Erin and Tess were exquisite.

I swam to the end of the pool, right up to the glass barrier. It was one of those infinity-type deals that makes you shit yourself if you look down. The pool ended right at the edge of the building, and I would probably pass out from vertigo if it wasn’t for the safety glass. Cassie and Shay, of course, knew that, and they teased me about it.

“I hope our kids don’t inherit this.” They were the sassy ones. It would be hard to measure, but I liked to think that Cassie loved me more than all other girls. She loved to cuddle in my arms and would always kiss me and lick my face. Shay naturally copied everything, like two clones in different super hot bodies. She loved me with all her heart, but I was sure she loved our unborn twins more. Sometimes, I caught her sitting on a sofa, reading fairy tales to the two unborn babies. All my girls were deliriously happy after so many years of having a real family.

Erin and Tess came over to join us at the end of the pool, staring at the wide city vista, the sea and docks with a dozen multimillion yachts moored there. It was a breathtaking view impossible to forget. Shay sighed. She was the most enamoured with the place.

“I wish I could just stay here forever.”

“You could if you wanted. I own it now.” Cassie and Shay almost choked, while Erin and Tess just turned pale.

“You are joking. This place is worth millions,” Shay added. She never spoke about money before.

“Yes, estimated one hundred million euros.” It was a gift from the old man or, rather, a part of the deal I made with him. He backed my business, but if I made him a pile of money, he would do an enormous favour for me, plus give me the apartment. I would have settled for the favour, and the apartment was a gambit.

The old man was looking for a way to offload it anyway. It had been empty in the market for a couple of years already, without anyone rich enough prepared to spend this kind of cash on it when in a less desirable location, they could buy a house for half that money. This apartment block was a landmark building where only the richest of the rich lived, making the property priceless on paper and worthless if you wanted to sell it. Nobody sane would spend that kind of money.

The girls stood frozen, trying to process the fact that I owned this landmark property. It came with two dedicated parking spaces in the basement—one for the Maybach and another for the Hummer if I wanted to have one here. Cassie’s eyes were all over the place, reassessing the property from a completely different vantage point, while Shay shuddered.

“I was just admiring it. I didn’t mean.” Shay’s voice failed. I pulled her in and kissed her head. She was such a sweet weirdo, like most of my babes. All of my girls knew full well that they could sit on a plane and live wherever they liked in whatever property I owned. They might as well choose to live here for a while, then come to Dubai or anywhere else. Erin and Tess just floated quietly, trying to comprehend the immensity of what I had just said. It was so out of their reality that it almost sounded perverted. Cassie looked into my eyes with a smile, shaking her head.

“You are crazy. That’s why I love you the most.” She hugged me tight and licked my cheek. “I guess that’s the big surprise and why you wanted us here.”

“Not really. I wanted to show you something else.” All the girls stared at me like I was about to pull out a wedding ring. I pointed at the harbour, and everyone’s eyes grew big. “Which one do you want?”

There was only one choice. Out of dozens of yachts and luxury motorboats, only one stood out like a black swan. It looked like a beautiful monster, making all the other ships look like toys in the water. It was so huge that it took up an entire side of a dock, and still, about a third of it protruded in front. The ship was vast, with a sleek black outer hull and four white decks, one on top of the other. It had pools and bars on it, and an entire helicopter was secured on the helipad.

“This is Belle,” I pointed at the ship and smiled. Four hundred and forty feet in length, one hundred and thirty-four meters and change. It was an exclusive super yacht costing me three hundred and seventy million dollars, including the helicopter. It was the fifteenth largest in the world by its size, flying the Monaco flag. The ship was built by a bankrupt Italian shipyard, pricing it at five hundred million, but I got a hefty discount. They needed money to survive, and I had plenty. Like the old man Salvatore said, I did very well for myself and made almost four billion dollars over six months, most of it on the day my company went live.

I had no idea what to do with that money, so I decided to buy a few toys I liked and invest the rest. Even if this failed, I would receive at least twenty million per year in intellectual property royalties. I had enough money to last me ten lifetimes. What else was I going to buy? I had a gorgeous villa in Dubai, an iconic Monte Carlo apartment, a luxury plane, and a super yacht, all of which cost me a measly six hundred and fifty million dollars. It represented only seventeen per cent of my entire wealth.

To most people, this amount of money was unthinkable, but then you imagine the real billionaires with ten, fifty, a hundred billion or more. Compared to them, I was an amateur. I never learned about Count Conti’s wealth, but I assumed it eclipsed mine by at least one order of magnitude.

I was never much into riches; they just never interested me. I had an idea of the life I wanted to live, so I got myself a house, a ship, and a plane. The Monaco apartment was a happy coincidence, a fringe benefit of a negotiation ending better than expected. I looked at the girls, and they were flabbergasted. Tess, the redhead, actually passed out, and Erin was propping her up so she wouldn’t drown. I guess it was too much for all of them, but it looked like a big joke, like a video game where I fought the boss to get to the next level.

I helped the girls out of the pool, and they laid on the sun beds to dry. I couldn’t stop myself from looking at four nude beauties basking in the sunshine. The way that the stewardesses looked at me, I knew they would fuck me at the snap of my fingers. That’s why I chose the most beautiful ones, knowing that sooner or later, it was inevitable.

It was the same reason I chose a dozen sailors using the same criteria. Belle, my ship, needed at least a dozen hands to keep it in pristine and tiptop shape. That’s where I pulled Gaspard from. He was the chef I hired for the ship, and he had two female assistants, both gorgeous girls in their early twenties, single and in love with travelling.

Gaspard had no interest in women. Due to the nature of his war injuries, the only real passion he could experience was through food, music, and Baudelaire. It took me forever to source the right captain, a widower in his late fifties still in love with the memory of his childhood sweetheart. The man sailed seven seas on various ships all his life. He laughed when I interviewed him and talked about all the electronic gadgets.

“Those are just toys, Jim. The ocean is like music, like a sonata. You close your eyes and listen to it. You either have it or not.” He had me at that. I didn’t have it, but the man obviously did. He loved his wife dearly, but he adored the sea. He heard its hum and could read the waves. You meet talent like this once in a lifetime. The first mate was a younger guy in his mid-thirties, a Sicilian, married to an exceptionally jealous wife from a wealthy family. They had two kids, and she made it abundantly clear to the man that he would never be able to have any more children if he even looked strangely in the direction of other women.

There was no way on earth any of those three men on the ship would have anything to do with the women working on it, and I made it certain using contracts that any inappropriate sexual advances of the crew to one another would result in immediate termination, and they would be blacklisted.

The rest of the crew were all female. My first criterion was that the girls should look incredible and be perfect genetic specimens. I didn’t particularly want to have sex with them, but I learned with the two stewardesses that eventually it might happen, and with that, everything else—love, kids, and whatever else—so I wanted to cut through this at the start to ensure myself from making a whole new category of potential mistakes. I made it abundantly clear to my recruiter that I wouldn’t hire a single person who wasn’t at least a seven on the M-scale. I didn’t want to explain it to them, so I just said, “Imagine a Victoria’s Secret runway show from the nineties, five-foot-ten, about a hundred and ten pounds, symmetric face, long legs.” They shook their heads, telling me it was impossible.

“It is not impossible, just hard. That’s why I’m paying you a lot of cash. Be creative, or be gone.” It turns out the recruiters needed just a good pep talk. Someone had a bright idea to raid all the modelling agencies, choosing the girls‘ pictures and asking what they had studied.

The waitresses and maids were easy to find, but the chef’s assistants were harder. Gaspard rejected eleven when he interviewed them until he agreed on two. The engineer was the hardest. The recruitment companies had to innovate and troll through Facebook and Instagram to find the two I hired in the end. As a result, I ended up with a crew of three men and a dozen of the most gorgeous sailors anyone could imagine.

I hired the same designer to create some sexy uniforms for them, stocked the ship with four trucks full of everything we might ever need, and sent the captain there to get everything organised. The captain was a humourless bastard who only cared about the well-being of the vessel and tolerated no bullshit or dissent. His word was the law on the open seas, and he was ready to go down with the ship.

When I informed them I was coming, he lined up the crew like a drill sergeant, all hands on deck, and they sailed Belle right into Monaco on her maiden voyage. This caused quite a stir at the docks, and the owners of other ships were asked to moor them elsewhere just to make space for the behemoth vessel.

Belle’s arrival sparked incredible interest. Even in such a rich place, a superyacht of this size seldom visited. People speculated about who might be the owner and stared at the incredibly sleek lines, looking futuristic, like some sort of spaceship. The sailor girls waved to the crowds, and they cheered, adding to the mystery of who might be the owner. Everyone just assumed it was some sheikh from faraway lands. Nobody would guess in a million years that it was just an IT guy.

I rummaged through the storage for a few minutes until I found a brand-new six-pack of Nivea sunblock. I went to Cassie and poured some of the milky cream on top of her belly. There was no point in rubbing it into her back, and she was unable to lay down on her stomach for months.

Using my index finger, I drew a heart in cream on her belly, and Cassie smiled. I loved her very much, and she did me. It was so unintuitive to show the same love to all my women without a trace of jealousy. Somewhere down the line, I made the right move, and it snowballed from there. All my girls were perfectly happy to share me with each other as they were happy to frolic with one another. Sex was just that, great fun. What we had was much more, something that transcended mere physical pleasure. We were a family and had children together.

Of course, arguments happened from time to time. Anyone living with a bunch of pregnant, hormonal women saying otherwise is a lying bastard. Disagreements are unavoidable. Instead of wrapping your language in wool and policing your speech, you better invest in the skills to de-escalate, say sorry when you did something wrong, and apologise. They say that prevention is better than cure. That’s why we wash our hands before dinner. Unfortunately, this turned into a prevalent culture. Don’t say or do something that might victimise the others. We lived in an age where being a victim was an advantage. People were arguing about whose victimhood trumped another.

Cassie sighed and closed her eyes as I massaged her heaving breasts. They grew in size, and as a boob man myself, I loved to play with them.

Invariably, my hands would veer off the beaten path. I am made of stone if I could resist the charms of naked goddesses, ready and willing, opening their legs to give me access. I poured some cream on my hands and delved deeper into the valleys of their flesh, one by one, hearing them moan as I kneaded their breasts and tweaked their nipples.

All four of them reacted differently yet similarly. Each one of them opened her legs wide as my fingers traced their way between them to play with a little pink nub of pleasure. It was a culmination in more than one way, a perfect crescendo in the musical of the day.

One after another, I watched the girls‘ backs arch. Their hands balled into fists as they squealed. It made me think about how this perverse display of wealth had a direct consequence on female limbic systems. I wasn’t seducing them or even trying to impress them. Like some grownup kid, I shared my excitement, and it culminated.

The girls came hard, and then their bodies relaxed, glistening in the sunshine, reflecting the light against their thoroughly lubricated bodies. I smiled, watching their beautiful pink orifices. My cock was hard like a stone yet, but I didn’t want to ruin the moment. The girls were just stunning, and their pussies beckoned. I wanted to stick my tongue into them and eat them till they fainted, but I couldn’t move. I was mesmerised. Out of all the fancy toys and riches, this was what impressed me the most. The four gorgeous naked women shared themselves with me, enriching my life with all that they were.

I let them sleep for some twenty minutes, basking in the sunshine and the warm afterglow of their orgasms before getting a text from Gaspard that the food would be served in fifteen minutes. I stirred the girls awake with endless protests.

“Why do I have to put on clothes again?“ Cassie pouted, and the stewardesses came to her aid. I could imagine how terrible it must have felt, but we all knew it would be worth it in the end. Cassie, of all my girls, was the biggest mommy type. All she could talk about when prompted is how she wanted to nurture her children. She didn’t give birth to our first one yet, and she was chewing my ear off about our fourth one.

“I want you to make me pregnant straight away. You don’t have much time, old man.“ She would mercilessly tease me in bed because I was twice her age. None of the other girls did that, but none of the other girls spent so much time with my sons apart from maybe Neneh. I helped Shay put on her clothes and helped her waddle downstairs. Shay knew she was in trouble carrying twins.

“Look what you did to me,“ she often joked, pointing at her massive belly. Shay frequently cried and needed a lot of love. I didn’t use any of my influence on her, and she still carried the demons she had. “I love you so much, Jim,“ she told me once before hugging me tight and crying the whole night. It looked to me like a catharsis of some sort, but I never asked. Shay was much calmer after that day, but she still cried all the time, laughed like a kid, and cried again.

The two young stewardesses went into the bedroom to wake up the kids, wash their hands and faces, and bring them to the table while I sat down with Cassie and Shay, sipping on a beautiful nonalcoholic cocktail.

“How do you call this?“ I asked, and Gaspard shrugged, explaining that it was something he often prepared for himself. It was sweet, colourful, and fresh.

“Let’s call it Virgin Gaspard Fresh,“ I suggested, thinking if one added some fine rum, it would make a perfect mainstream cocktail. Gaspard liked it and is thinking about adding some coconut shavings next time. “Make us a recipe and put it on a menu on the yacht.“

With all of us sitting around the table, Gaspard started bringing us starters. It all looked so incredible that none of us dared to eat first. The girls took photos and shared them until Gaspard had enough of that and started cutting the food and putting it on our plates.

“You are a treasure, Gaspard,“ I said. The food was excellent, and for the first time, I got enough on my plate, served by the Frenchman. When I mentioned it, Gaspard laughed. His entire idea behind his award-winning restaurant was to serve the most fantastic food, perfectly presented at astronomical prices but with enough to feed the guests. He preferred composting the leftovers to having customers clean the sauce on the plate with slices of bread. It was a winning formula and the reason why his place was so popular.

“Do you miss it sometimes?“

“Bien sûr, monsieur, but I don’t miss the management.” Gaspard only loved to cook, but running the restaurant business, hiring and firing people, or dealing with drunk customers ruined his zen and made him hate the company. This is why he jumped at the opportunity. He would cook for a small group of people who appreciated his cuisine and had enough spare time to read, listen to music, and watch the waves. It wasn’t so much the money as it was the lifestyle. He would never be able to afford one like that.

“Don’t worry about this. I’ll clean up,” I told Gaspard after all the girls fell into a food coma, and he started to pack the food.

“I promised the girls on the ship some leftovers.”

“What do you mean? What do they usually eat?” Gaspard explained that the girls eat what everyone eats. They have their own staff canteen, and they make their own food and eat what they like. I wanted to jump out of my skin.

“Would you mind making a nice meal for the staff every day?” Gaspard smiled, and his eyes got big. “I would love to, but I would need two or three more assistants so I could rotate them. Fifteen people, three times a day, it is a lot of work and not fair to the girls.” I got it; serving the food would require at least two waitresses, cooking, washing the dishes, setting the tables, ordering produce, and managing stocks. This is why Gaspard struggled. He saw only a tiny part of the problem and did the best with what he had.

“I’ll get you the stuff you need. Meanwhile, try to make do with what you have.” I could see this meant a lot to the man. We never met in person, and he didn’t know what to expect. Everyone on the ship received a six-figure salary. I paid better for the deckhands than any other ship owner, mainly because I had such stringent staff requirements, but on the flip side, nobody dared to say a word in protest or even whisper a suggestion. That’s not what I wanted.

I realised that the way the owners usually ran ships was smart and efficient, but I wasn’t trying to cut costs in any way. This entire ship business really cost me an insignificant amount I could easily cover with a fraction of my royalties. A year of the entire ship expenses, including the fuel, cost me less than I made in a month without lifting a finger.

While Gaspard picked up the leftovers, I made a few calls and sent a few text messages. The ship captain was the law on the open water, but Belle wasn’t a cargo vessel or a cruise liner. I needed two more cooks, two more waitresses, two kitchen staff cleaning and washing the dishes, a kitchen manager, and a ship manager in addition to the twelve already there. I found it unacceptable to eat great food and feed my staff with the crumbs of the table. “What the fuck?” I was disappointed. It was nobody’s fault, but I was responsible. To run the ship the way I wanted, I needed at least eight more staff to make it efficient, plus the food bill would climb sky-high, but on the flip side, there would be less expired stuff to throw away.

After pouring some coffee into a cup, I went to sit by the window overlooking the bay and enjoy the tiramisu Gaspard made for me, focusing my thoughts on the little problems. It made me laugh. I knew a perfect job for Lamin when he came back. In addition to being my driver, I’ll make him the chief operations officer of my little family enterprise. After what he had been through, Lamin was more than qualified.

Chapter 47 - Hard Bargain

I almost jumped, feeling the gentle touch of a soft hand on my shoulder. I was so lost in my thoughts that I overlooked Tess, my beautiful redhead stewardess. She was barefoot, wearing only her lingerie and a white towel around her hair.

“Can’t sleep?“ I asked. She nodded her head, her blue eyes meeting mine. I always liked looking at Tess‘ face and counting her freckles, finding them cute on most redheads. She sat on a sofa next to me but didn’t go all the way in, remaining tense and looking uncomfortable.

“Jim, may I talk to you about something personal?“ I nodded, pushing a small plate with tiramisu towards her. She shook her head ever so slightly, biting her lip, gnashing her fingers against each other. I could see a fine sheen of perspiration on her forehead and a little tremble as she moved her hands.

“I like you,“ Tess blurted out. I knew where this was going now and decided to play with that. I was too focused on my business, and I hadn’t learned anything new for a very long time.

“I like you too, Tess.“ I smiled and patted her hand.

“No, I mean, I would like you to, hmmm.“ Tess was trying to find her words.

“Come on, what is it? Blurt it out,“ and she did. Her eyes teared up from stress, and she kept on talking, telling me that she was attracted to me and wanted to be one of my girlfriends. I was about to interrupt her to remind her that I never defined my relationships, but I stopped myself from arguing semantics.

Tess must have kept all this bottled up for quite some time. Once she got going, there was no stopping her, one way or another. She told me about her past life and all the mistakes she made, making a logical leap to save her life. She was projecting, and I let her do it.

This was the best example of what most men do wrong with women. When a girl likes a guy, she will talk and seduce herself. All the man had to do was shut his mouth and nod his head, pretending he was a perfect listener. Instead of pointing out to Tess all the assumptions she made and outright logical mistakes, I listened, looking into her eyes with a smile and encouraging her to talk more. With each minute, she was revealing more of herself, practically making herself available for the picking. All I had to do was to reach for it.

Eventually, Tess ran out of steam and exhausted herself, laying bare in front of my gaze. This was what I waited for, what I like to call the negotiation moment. How I framed this would shape our relationship, and it had to be presented in a way that looked like a problem with a clear carrot on the other end, so she leaps to solve it instead of me setting the rules.

“You know, it’s not that easy. Those are not just some girls I am dating. We are a very loving and tightly-knit family. By bringing another girl in, I could mess up everything.” Tess nodded from the moment I started laying out the problem, and she patiently waited for me to explain before blurting out her answer.

“I know, and we are all good friends. I love them all like they are my sisters. I know you are a family, and that’s what I want with all my heart. I never met my dad, and my mom remarried twice. The last guy tried to rape me.” Hello? My special beacon for broken women was broadcasting as strong as always.

“But you see, what we don’t show in public is that most of my girls are actually bisexual. How do you think they go on without me for a long time?” Tess laughed, getting beet red on her face. She answered me in almost a husky whisper.

“I am bisexual as well, and all your girlfriends are so beautiful.” Ding, ding, ding. I smiled, rubbing her face with my hand, and she pushed against it, fluttering her eyes and exhaling with a shudder.

“You are a beautiful girl, and I like you a lot. You certainly turn me on, like when I gave you a massage, and you closed your eyes and orgasmed. I had to jump back into the pool to cool off.” Tess actually giggled, looking like a ripe tomato in her face. “The problem is, you see, that as far as sex goes, I am spoiled for choice. I am sure that sex with you would be unforgettable, but then, if I took you away, I would have to find another flight attendant, and where does that end?”

Tess hugged me and kissed my cheek, and I pulled her into my lap, pulling down her towel and liberating her hair, burying my nose in it, and inhaling deeply.

“Mmmm, you smell so good, I could eat you.” Tess cleared her throat. It was hard to concentrate, with her legs looking like plucked chicken. I never saw goosebumps pop up quite like that.

“I don’t want to stop being a flight attendant, Jim. I love travelling, and flying in your plane is an impossible dream. I just want to belong and feel safe. I want to have a future.” Her face changed. She touched something dark inside. I avoided digging deep since Cassie.

“I mean, we could try,” I started, and she perked up. “I would love to have you as one of my girls. You are gorgeous, fun, and smart, not to mention cute.” I rubbed my index finger on her nose, and she wrinkled it.

“I hate my freckles.”

“I love them.” She looked at me like a big kid, and I kissed her nose. She sneezed and giggled.

“See, what I am trying to tell you and failing is that I don’t want to have girls for just sex. I don’t want to be another millionaire playboy who changes his women like tissues.” Tess got it and smiled like she won a prize.

“You misunderstood me, Jim. I want the same. I want to have a family and kids as well.” It wasn’t that hard to guess. Almost all of my girls were pregnant to their teeth. One would have to be blind to miss it. “I know the rules,” Tess said with a mischievous smile. Neneh, the tyrant, insisted there was not a single birth control instrument, not a pill or a condom, anywhere near any of my women.

Tara was desperate to get pregnant. It was her greatest wish and a dream all her life, but for some reason, it hasn’t happened yet despite numerous specialists telling her the same. “Everything is normal; you just haven’t caught it yet.” It was making her feel miserable, and having perfectly healthy women using birth control was just rubbing it into Tara’s face.

Over time, this morphed into a family rule. When the boys came, all the women fell in love with them. Liam and Callum were as much theirs as they were mine, and all my girls bent over backwards to give them the best childhood imaginable while steering them with a firm hand towards growing into men.

“So,” I smiled at her, staring into her eyes, moving my index finger down her nose, across her perfectly formed plump red lips. She opened them, caught my finger with her teeth, and licked it a little suggestively. “You would like me…,” and her luxury lace bra peeled off, exposing her grapefruit-sized breasts to my touch. My finger navigated its way between her breasts and across her navel, ending on the top of her uterus, “…to put my baby inside here?”

“Yes,” she hissed and bit my lip, stuck her tongue in mine, and we kissed like crazy. Her hand went to my cock, which was already hard like a flagpole and squeezed it. “I want to be your bitch. I want you to breed me.” Tess was on fire, and she gasped, feeling my finger find its way into her panties and straight inside her pink hole.

Tess squealed a bit when I lifted her up and giggled like a kid when I threw her on a bed. She bounced and rolled, getting on all fours, using her hands to spread her asscheeks apart, giving me an unrestricted view of her pussy and ass.

“Hmm, which hole to choose,” I joked, and her eyes met mine.

“You can choose any or all. I am yours to fuck.”

Sometimes, I felt greedy this way. I didn’t want to choose, but take all of it instead. I came up behind Tess and smacked my lips against her orifice, pushing my tongue inside to have a first taste of what is mine.

Tess squealed, losing her balance and resting her chest against the linen while she gyrated. I lapped her pussy up like a starved dog does a stick of butter. In and out I went, tasting both holes while Tess’ body trembled. Her squeals came and went between panting like a dog and hissing like a cat. Tess growled like a demon from hell, then she screamed, feeling my cock punch through her asshole.

It messed with my mind. The primal way she responded to my cock made me want to fuck her harder, and she pushed her ass towards me each time. Our bodies slapped against each other, echoing like Tess was getting spanked, but it was just me jackhammering my rigid member into her warm, quivering depths.

I flipped Tess on her back without pulling out, and she took my hand and used it to slap her face before laying it against her neck. No translation is needed. I knew what she wanted, so I slapped her a few times, then pushed my fingers into her mouth while choking her with another hand, all the while pumping into her asshole as if I was trying to hurt her, punish her for something bad.

Tess screamed, and her back arched. Her pussy burst into squirts while I slapped her breasts. She growled, hissed and moaned like the dirtiest slut in a gang bang.

“Harder! Fuck me harder! Slap me harder,” Tess commanded, and I obliged. She went insane, giving in to her darkest side. This wasn’t sex anymore but a brutal exchange of force. I set out to destroy her, and she begged me for more. Until I started to gasp for air.

I felt it deep inside, how my cock hardened, and my balls tightened. I wanted to cum so hard, and the train was on the approach. I snorted and squeezed her neck harder. Tess’ face was purple, and so was mine, and I pumped like a maniac connected to a power line.

“Fuck me, Jim! Cum inside my pussy. Breed me; make me your bitch. Impregnate me. Make me into your cum bucket.” The girl was wild, gasping for air and hissing commands.

I was only too happy to oblige, so I pulled my cock out and changed the hole. I stabbed Tess’ pussy with my cock about to explode, marvelling at her warmth and tightness for only a moment before my body tensed, and I hosed her ovaries with high-pressure sperm, my steaming baby-makers.

Tess joined me in my orgasm, squealing like a pig as she came. It turned me on so much that I remained hard, punching her cervix with my cock. In and out, like a sheath and a sword, I jackhammered Tess, feasting on her nipples. Like some demon from stories of hell, I consumed and devoured the sexy redhead, and she came once, twice, three times until I pulled out and stuffed my cock into her asshole again.

Moments later, I was blasting again, lubricating her bowels with my sperm. She screeched like a witch from Wicked, gushing from her pussy, trembling like she had Parkinson’s disease.

I lost track of time; it must have been hours as it was dark outside. I rolled on my back, gasping for breath, and Tess immediately got between my legs, slurping the juices from my cock and cleaning it with her tongue.

Tess didn’t try to make me hard again; she seemed content with just enjoying the feel of my cock in her mouth. She rubbed it all over with the gentleness of her tongue, sucking on it gently, helping me recover.

It felt so nice and gentle, like being touched by a warm feather, and I closed my eyes, drifting off into the la-la land with the music of life permeating my existence. Time melted away, and I just floated inside in endless pleasure. At one point, I felt like I needed to go to the bathroom, but Tess wouldn’t let me leave.

“Pee inside me,“ she whispered. I was too tired to consider the deeply perverted and humiliating idea she had, so I forced myself not to analyse, just go with the flow and lose myself. I let go of my bladder and had this strange feeling of Tess gulping down my warm urine, even sucking it out when the stream slowed. The girl was fucked up; that much was evident. I enjoyed the feeling, no matter how strange. Morning would bring all the questions and the analyses, so I closed my eyes with my cock in Tess’s mouth, and the world melted away.

My eyes popped open, and my body tensed. Before I realised what was happening, I groaned in pleasure. It was bright outside, but my mind could only process the fantastic throbbing of my cock and my balls squeezing my sperm out. One, two, three massive blasts erupted from my cock into something warm and wet, sucking it out like a vacuum cleaner, and I gasped.

As my vision cleared, I saw red hair and a cute face, plump red lips distorted, wrapped around my cock. Then, my eyes met hers, and I recognised Tess. I passed out last night after a marathon of sex, and my cock was inside her mouth. I was trained by the best, Tara, who was a demanding lover. I could easily cum six times a day after a year of constant training. Still, Tess was on another level, seemingly a cute and innocent girl, barely twenty. She fooled me. Once she got going, the woman was relentless. She could fuck, suck, and fuck again like she breathed.

I heard stories about such women, and I thought they were just tales, but I met one, and she was my stewardess, hiding a hardcore nymphomaniac inside. Tess was insatiable. Every time she came, it just pushed her up a little and made her demand rougher treatment. When I pumped her with sperm, it was like giving her fuel. She wanted more and more like a Duracell bunny high on speed and coke plugged into an electrical socket without a transformer.

By the time I got out of my shower, the girls were raring to go, and the boys already had their breakfast. They looked at me with mischievous smiles. It would be impossible to hide what Tess and I were up to till the early hours of the day when I finally had to throw in the towel and tell her to stop, or I’d end up injured. Tess refused to come up for a cuddle, preferring to stay the way she was and fall asleep with my cock in her mouth.

“Who wants to go for a walk and check out the neighbourhood?“ Everyone agreed, so I put on my clothes, and we took the elevator to the ground floor, where I asked the concierge to send the crew up to clean my apartment. I inherited a weekly cleanup service; whether I was there or not, they would come and dust the place, air it, and keep the living space perfect.

I walked around town with four beauties, arm in arm, and my two boys right in front of us. Cassie and Shay leaned on me for support while Erin and Tess helped their balance. One of the good and bad things about being pregnant is that you get to buy new clothes every four weeks as the body goes through the change. I led the girls to a street with a bunch of boutiques and let them go at it with my credit card while I sat down in a cafe with Liam and Callum and sipped my sorely needed cup of coffee while they ate their ice cream. My balls hurt since last night. That little minx Tess put me through paces. It made me wonder how someone so oversexed managed to keep herself isolated.

Our plane schedule was crazy, with flights almost every day. The two pilots I hired begged me to get them a standby replacement, as they sorely needed a long holiday. It got a bit better since my pull back from New York, and I planned a big holiday for everyone after the flight to Dubai. I even paid them extra bonuses for being so understanding and taking it like troopers. I paid well, and they took the pressure, knowing that there was no way to make this money elsewhere.

That was my ultimate secret. I gave my people excellent salaries and made them a part of the bigger picture. There is always an inherent “us and them“ when employing someone, but I worked hard to narrow that divide and made my employees understand that it’s just a gap, not a chasm. That’s why Tess ultimately decided to step over.

I always knew something like this was inevitable, so I prepared for it, even encouraged it like the night before when I pulled the two stewardesses naked into the water, then rubbed their bodies with sunscreen and made them orgasm. Tess was obviously the more impressionable one, and I made her feel she could cross the divide, so she stepped across, and I set the strict frame, which others would use as a precedent and a test case.

The girls came out of the shops wearing brand-new clothes. Behind them, two clerks followed, ambling with bags and packages. It almost made me laugh. The girls made it to the cafe and sat down while I tipped the clerks to deliver everything to the apartment.

“I have to pee,“ Cassie said as soon as she sat down. Tess immediately offered to take her inside. I ordered the cake and fresh juice for everyone. Shay and Erin were telling me about their Monaco shopping experience. Minutes later, Cassie emerged. The two ladies were conspiring something. As soon as they saw me watching them, they stopped talking and made innocent faces. It was like living with children, and I just had to chuckle. There was no doubt in my mind that all four knew the details of what happened last night.

We finished the drinks and moved away to look around town and do some more damage to my bottom line while admiring the city and its people, the views, and how nice everything looked. Monaco was the playground for the richest, with beautiful cars, gorgeous women, and their men wearing expensive clothes. All of them studied us as we walked around. Even in Monaco, you don’t see a man walking arm in arm with four women, some of whom have literally appeared on billboards and in fashion magazines.

Around lunchtime, the boys were tired, and I worked up an appetite, so I stopped two cabs to get us to the docks. The strollers noticed us walking to the long pier and boarding the most luxurious superyacht.

The captain stood at the ready and greeted us professionally. The first mate extended his greetings from a safe distance while Gaspard came running to greet us as friends, bringing two homemade ice creams to the boys and taking them with him to put them to bed. The dozen girls in skimpy sailor outfits were smiling. It was the first time I saw them in real life, and they exceeded my expectations as far as their looks were concerned. All of them were about five-foot-ten, slim with long legs and symmetrical faces. It didn’t take a genius to figure out the core criteria on which they were selected, so they played it up.

It didn’t take much to imagine all of them out of their clothes. Those outfits they wore looked like they were painted on them, with the absolute bare minimum of decency that made the difference between a real uniform and the one you could buy in a sex shop.

“Would you mind if I addressed the crew directly?“ I asked the captain, and he puffed up, graciously allowing me to do that. We had to stick to some level of formality to not erode the captain’s authority. I approached everyone and shook their hands, expressing how pleased I was to see all of them.

Gaspard disappeared back into the kitchen while the crew surrounded my girls. There was some instant electricity between them, and minutes later, they talked to each other like they all went to the same kindergarten.

Everyone had their own jobs, so the captain went up to his office. Two of the cooks ran in to join Gaspard. I followed the first mate while my girls followed the others. We took different paths through the ship. I wanted to start with the engine. The two engineer girls were already there. Their job was to deal with the little things. Nobody could fix the engine. If it failed somewhere, we would have to get towed. The damn thing was so vast and complicated that it could only be maintained in a shipyard by specialist tools and personnel.

I went around deck by deck, and I gasped. When I bought the ship, I got all the papers, pictures, videos, and documents. I sent a specialist crew to examine it bolt by bolt, and it got a clean bill of health. It was brand new, never sailed, and no corners were cut anywhere. The ship was the crown jewel of the oceans. I remembered seeing it in the specs somewhere, and I couldn’t help but stare.

The ship had a large pool inside with spas, steam rooms, showers, massage rooms, and all the bells and whistles one could imagine except a gym, and I thought to myself, this was something I had to fix. I lost track of the rooms and where I was going left and right. There was enough room for at least three times the crew and a dozen luxurious bedrooms with all amenities. There were conference rooms, movie rooms, this room, that room, and more pools and hot spas than I could count.

It took my breath away, especially when we got outside and ended at the back with a massive round, bubbly hot spa, big enough for at least fifty people, surrounded by sitting areas and bars and all sorts of other amenities. It became glaringly apparent that I was wrong to hire only fifteen people. Who would tend those bars? Who would serve the drinks? In the end, who would fly the helicopter in front? It would take a crew of at least fifty people to keep the ship going in shifts around the clock.

The captain said twelve people, and he was right. Twelve was enough to sail it and keep it clean and ordered, but it would take many more to keep it functional and at its peak. I couldn’t expect the staff to work day and night without breaks, so I would have to run multiple shifts and rotate the employees to get enough sleep. I was right when I thought I needed a ship manager, but being there, I realised she would need an assistant as well.

By my quick estimate, the ship could accommodate twenty to thirty overnight guests, depending on how many shared the beds, but if I wanted to organise parties, the ship could comfortably sail with about a hundred guests, which, with a staff of fifty, left only about fifteen people per shift. Of course, you won’t run a bar for breakfast, but you might run breakfast outside. I was getting a headache just going through possible permutations of the place. The ratio of fifty staff to a hundred guests seemed about right to me, basing it purely on the hotels I visited. I knew some five-star hotels have a one-to-one rate, but this wasn’t feasible.

Of course, the ship would only be so full during special events and parties, but what do we do then? Should I hire temporary staff and fire them? I had very specific criteria for all the staff members, and getting them for just a few months a year was a waste, so I either bit the bullet and gave the off-duty staff a fantastic holiday cruise or I never got great service.

My mind swirled, calculating in hyper speed, defining variables, and setting rules. Most problems could be modelled using polynomial equations, and this one was a worthy challenge. If I modelled the variables in a multidimensional matrix, I could use a weighted graph to come to the most optimal solution to the problem. Then, I could apply an algorithm to the result. In essence, this wasn’t much different from the travelling salesman problem aptly described in the first volume of Donald Knuth’s four-part trilogy on the art of computer programming, also referred to as “the bible” by uber-geeks like me.

Shay to the rescue! She came to pull me to the dining room and save me from my brain. I was stuck in my mind, going off on a tangent where every problem was a challenge I just had to solve. That’s how you develop a compulsive obsessive disorder. I had it since the early days when the school psychologist diagnosed me with mild Asperger’s tendencies, which meant “on the spectrum” now using the politically correct newspeak espoused by the British Central Comintern. That, too, changed its name. When I was growing up, we used to call it “the parliament.”

Everyone stood up from the long table as I walked in. I was about to tell them it wasn’t necessary but stopped myself. I liked the gesture as a show of respect. After all, I owned this ship and paid all their salaries. Without me, none of this would be here, and perhaps I did deserve the honour they were showing me.

I sat down at the head of the table with Liam and Callum on my sides and the captain at the other end. Everyone quieted as I tapped the glass and waited for me to make a speech.

“I want to thank you all for welcoming us so graciously and making this dream possible. Each one of you is an important member of this team, and I want you to know that my doors are always open. I want to hear your thoughts, ideas, and suggestions, so don’t be shy to present them. Remember one thing, the captain is your boss, and I am just another passenger, so treat me like that, relax, and enjoy the adventure. Bonne chance! Bon voyage!“ I raised my glass, and others followed. Then, the food arrived, carried by the chef and his two assistants. Immediately, I saw the problem, and so did the girls, and everyone helped.

The food was exquisite, and everyone lauded the chef and the kitchen team. The girls were so grateful for making the food rule yesterday. It was another great perk of the job. Gaspard only asked everyone to tell him if they would skip a meal or if they had different dietary requirements. The girls would eat anything, and I made sure of that when hiring them. I didn’t want any vegan psychopaths on my ship, nor did I want radical feminists or woke terrorists. I made it clear from the beginning that such behaviour would not be tolerated. One excess and they will be quarantined and unloaded without pay at the nearest port.

Early this morning, Gaspard prepared a cheese omelette on lard with bacon and steak, as well as the baked beans he soaked overnight. The girls loved it so much that he promised them to increase the portion sizes for the next day.

For lunch, we had stuffed pintade with honey-roasted vegetables, cream soup, cucumber and beetroot salad with finely sliced cabbage, crepes with crushed walnuts, honey, and cinnamon and a serving of homemade ice cream.

In the end, the captain and the first mate excused themselves. I sat on a sofa in the main living room while all the girls sat around in a circle. Calum and Liam were sitting at my side, playing with some toys Cassie bought for them. It started slow, but soon enough, they bombarded me with thanks, trying to say something useful and making intense eye contact. They were all gorgeous, but they weren’t blind. Despite being pregnant, Cassie and Shay were of different ranks, and the two held on to me like two doves in love.

“We will be departing tomorrow afternoon,“ I said, laying out the plan I sent to the captain yesterday. “I want you to help Gaspard stock up the ship with everything until we get to where we’re going.“ All the girls promised. Some even saluted with a smile. Liam and Callum were getting restless, so we said our goodbyes.

On the way back, a bunch of people stared at us. I even saw a few secretly taking photographs of us. I guessed everyone was interested in who we were. It took us only twenty minutes to get back to our place. I could actually see it from the harbour and smiled. I couldn’t have gotten a better place to live.

Cassie and Shay were exhausted. I made them a bath and let them soak for a while, then I spent an hour massaging them and another thirty minutes giving them a foot massage. When I lay between them, my two lovely angels hugged me from each side, telling me how much they loved me. I loved them just as much. They were the loves of my life. I loved all my girls in my own way. They were all unique and precious to me. I always wanted to have a big family.

Chapter 48 - Something good

I woke up early the following day with the two mommies entangled with me. I loved waking up this way, surrounded by love and my unborn children. Careful not to wake them, I snuck out and stirred my boys, dressed them up and took them for a walk, and bought some fresh bagels so we could make sandwiches together. I loved being a family man, and I couldn’t wait to meet my other children.

We had a rule to count them only once they were born and named, so I made myself not to think about that. I only knew that there were many since most of my women were pregnant and ready to be mommies.

“I have to go on a trip, my lovelies, but I will see you home in less than a week again.” Liam and Callum nodded. They knew how the world worked, and they felt loved and safe with their aunties. Soon enough, they will be too big to call them my lovelies.

The girls were already up, drinking their coffee when I got back, so I made them some breakfast. Liam and Callum love omelettes with bacon and cheese, so I got straight to it to feed my women and children.

“We’ll miss you,” Cassie said, hugging me tight after breakfast. They were taking a plane back to Dubai with Erin while I was taking the ship with Tess. She would help me interview two more stewardesses. Just like the ship, the aeroplane staff should be rotated. I made a provisional agreement with Lufthansa to lend me their pilots when I needed them so I could give mine some rest without grounding the plane for a month at a time. I thought about everything and came to the conclusion that I had to keep mobile. I couldn’t bring everything to a halt for the sake of two people.

The girls packed up, and I kissed them all and hugged my boys. A people carrier came to pick them up, leaving Tess with me to close the place and lock up. We took a stroll downhill after sending the cab with our luggage. I wanted to experience Monte Carlo some more. After all, this place became my home.

I made the Dubai villa my home away from home. Dubai was where my offices were, and all the IT engineers were there. It was my base of operation, but I refused to call it home. The girls loved it, of course, and it was where they wanted to live, but for some reason, just like Cassie and Shay, I felt best in Monte Carlo and decided I would live in Monaco, at least on paper. That’s why my ship was registered there, flying the Monaco flag. I even signed up my boys for French classes, and I started learning the language. It was utterly unnecessary, but it made me feel like I belonged there.

About an hour later, just before lunchtime, Tess and I made it to the docks and worked up an appetite. We boarded the ship, and the sailors conducted all the necessary checks. Then, the captain gave the signal, and the first mate took us out. He even let me blow the horn, which made me feel like a kid again.

Gaspard called for lunch, and the captain excused himself, preferring to have his meal in his cabin, keeping track of everything. I was loving every moment of it, looking out as Belle cut through the waves. It felt like she glided on top of the sea without any strange movements. At that very moment, it really sank in. I owned this great ship.

All the girls joined me at the table where we chatted and ate, then one by one, made their way back to their numerous duties. A lot of them were on a cleaning roster. The captain was a stickler for cleanliness. He would go around with his white glove and berate everyone if he found a single spot of dust anywhere. The man was strict and demanding but also fair. He didn’t show any favouritism to anyone and always impartially resolved any disputes. The captain was a benevolent dictator of this beautiful vessel. His entire demeanour demanded obedience and respect. I was happy with my choice, knowing that my ship was managed by a firm and steady hand like that.

“Where is the main bedroom?“ I asked one of the girls, and she immediately dropped what she was doing, leading me through the corridors and explaining how to get there. I had been there once before, but I had lost my way in the maze of hallways.

The master bedroom looked stunning, with an ocean view on three sides and a luxurious custom-made king-size bed with expensive leather furnishings and soft, lush carpets. The ensuite bathroom was legendary, crafted with glass, white porcelain, and chrome fittings. It included both a shower and a massive self-standing bathtub that could comfortably fit three people, perhaps even four, inside. All of it had a state-of-the-art digital temperature and jet controls. I fell in love with the bedroom at first sight and made it mine.

Nobody had ever slept in the bed or taken a shower or bath there. The entire room had a faint new furniture smell, and the linen was never used. It was pristine and untouched.

“Oh, god!” Tess sighed. I was so awed that I forgot she was there. She must have not seen this room before, and her eyes were like saucers. She had to look into every nook and cranny, inspect everything in disbelief.

“How rich are you?” Tess looked at me in awe. It finally sank in for her as well that this wasn’t some sort of an amusement ride, but I actually owned all this and employed all of those people for my own entertainment. I laughed and rustled her red hair with my hand, pinching her cheek with my knuckles.

Come on. Let’s get dressed into something comfortable,” I said and opened my suitcase. The sailor girls picked it up from the taxi and carried it into my room when I boarded. I put on my black shorts and loose white T-shirt and took my phone. This was all I wanted to wear or carry, intent on going around the ship barefoot and enjoying my time as if it were a holiday.

When I turned around, I saw Tess was naked. She shrugged, holding a bikini in each hand. One was yellow, the other one was white; one was perverse, and the other one was obscene. She must have got them the day before when the girls went shopping. I told her about the boat trip, and she prepared for it.

Tess gave me a wicked smile, looking at my face. I thought, fuck it. We’re not on a public beach, and the staff would have to get used to it sooner or later. I picked the yellow one, and it stood out brightly, barely covering anything on Tess’s body. In fact, she looked more naked than if she wore nothing, and I had to admit, I liked the swimsuit now that she wore it. Tess looked incredibly sexy in it, with lovely yellow strings on the sides. One pull on each, and her bikini would float away.

The only negative aspect of hiring women with a fashion model figure, tall and slim, was that they often lacked large breasts. This did not detract from their natural beauty or make me appreciate them any less. It was just that I found myself drawn to women with fuller breasts. I found tall, slim bodies with long legs and a narrow waist, combined with large breasts, incredibly appealing and sexually attractive.

Both Cassie and Shay were precisely that type: tall, slim, and highly feminine, with gorgeous full breasts that I loved to knead. They always giggled a little when I would pay attention to their sizeable mammaries, especially now that they had gotten even bigger. It was something I couldn’t control or wanted to change. I liked what I liked, but it didn’t stop me from enjoying women with other body types.

“What are you looking at?” Tess asked with some sass.

“I was just wondering how you would look with bigger breasts.“ Her eyes popped open, big like saucers.

“I don’t like mine much. I think they are too small.” I thought Tess’ grapefruit-sized breasts were perfectly shaped, but she was right. From a purely aesthetic perspective, having fuller breasts would make her look much more feminine for her height and body type. I shrugged and waved it away, pulling her hand.

Come on, let’s sit on the back deck.“ That’s where the large round hot spa resided with a circular sitting lounge and a bar. Tess giggled down the stairs, slipping on the carpet once until she climbed onto my back, and I carried her onto the deck.

When I arrived at the enormous circular hot tub, I cautiously climbed in, attempting to maintain my balance until both of us were comfortably settled inside. I discovered the control panel situated outside, set the jet speed and temperature, pressed the large button, and the pool began to bubble. Minutes later, one of the sailor girls came over, acting as a waitress, and asked us what we wanted to drink.

“Please bring us two Gaspard Fresh cocktails.“ She had never heard of it. “Don’t worry, the chef knows what it is.“ The girl left and came back after fifteen minutes with two tall glasses full of colourful liquid and the edges covered in coconut shavings. I took a sip through a straw and smiled, tasting the rum. Gaspard listened to my suggestions and made a perfect new cocktail.

I noticed the girl was still standing above, so I lifted my glass and offered her a sip. “Wanna try?“ The girl squatted down and took a small gulp, then smiled.

“I love it. This is excellent.“

“Go tell the chef that. He’ll be glad to hear it.” The girl thanked me and walked straight back towards the kitchen. I rested my head against the waterproof faux leather headrest and floated in bubbly water. Tess couldn’t stay still in one place and floated from side to side, trying to find the best place for bubbles.

At one moment, I heard Tess curse something, then saw a crumpled-up yellow bikini piece flying through the air, landing on the deck outside. Tess’ face looked finally satisfied as she floated in one place, enjoying the bubbles. Who cared anyway? If Tess wanted to bathe naked, god bless her. I preferred her in her birthday suit anyway. It wasn’t as appetising as unwrapping a present, but there were other things to enjoy when bathing with a naked woman.

The captain took us into Italian waters by Corsica through the Tyrrhenian Sea towards Sicily. The plan was to turn towards Malta and across the Ionian Sea into the Adriatic. As the sailor girls finished their duties, they rolled off the shift and came to sit beside us.

“Why don’t you join us inside?“ I asked the girl who brought us the drinks earlier.

“We are not allowed.“

“Who said that?“ I didn’t make such a rule.

“The captain said that we couldn’t use the guest facilities.” I had to talk with the man and make him relax a bit. This wasn’t an army vessel or a cruiser; there were no passengers to upset. I knew why he did that; it’s what he learned, but I wanted my crew members to enjoy themselves and see this ship as more than just their workplace.

“Come on in. I’ll talk to the captain later.” She hesitated for a few seconds, then giggled, shed off her clothes and jumped into the pool, wearing her underwear. “Hey! What do you think you’re doing? This is a nude spa?” The girl looked at me like she did something terrible but caught my lecherous grin and quickly realised that I was just teasing her.

“But you are wearing clothes,“ she tried to justify her thought process.

“You’re absolutely right,” I said, reaching below water to pull off my shorts and throw them on the pile. We needed a set of white bath robes and towels, I thought and made a mental note, watching the girl reach down and add her underwear to the top of the pile, never for a second losing contact with my eyes. If I wanted to flirt, she was obviously game.

I turned to another girl and asked her to bring everyone a round of cocktails. She ran like the wind and returned a few moments later, carrying a tray with tall glasses. I raised my voice so everyone could hear me, telling the girls to get their drinks and join us inside. All of them jumped at this and shed their clothes like autumn leaves, picked up their glasses and joined us inside the bubbling water.

This looked much better. I was enjoying myself inside a hot spa with five naked women. None of them seemed to have minded the nudity. The bubbles protected everyone’s modesty. I thought about that and all the changes I wanted to implement.

“I will speak with the captain later, but I want you to know that after your shift has ended, you can use all the facilities. Keep in mind that all the pools, baths and sun beds are to be used without clothes.” The girls nodded and smiled. Not a single one of them protested. They were all young and gorgeous in their early twenties, and there was only one man to worry about anyway, the same guy for whom they all had bedroom eyes.

Tess floated slowly towards me and nestled into my lap. The sailor girls chatted with her about this and that while I sipped my cocktail and enjoyed myself. When I finished, I closed my eyes and rested, feeling all the accumulated stress from the last six months released from my system. It would take weeks or even months to fully recover, but the nightmare was over, and I was a free man living the dream of my own design.

With billions of dollars of liquid assets, even the most conservative plans would bring me more money than I could ever spend. I was planning to put a lot of it into a portfolio of tourism and real estate mixed with riskier, more exotic investments.

My thoughts jumped from one theme to another as I relaxed and enjoyed the bubbles. At one point, I caught a word and a sentence that pierced my ears and grabbed my attention. The sailor girls were asking Tess about her life as a stewardess, obliquely nudging her to share my story and how she got to be with the most beautiful women the girls had seen. They asked Tess if she was one of them, and she confirmed, noting it was a recent development.

The girls talked about my life, my kids, and my lifestyle, including what I did, where I lived, and similar topics. Tess must have thought I was asleep, and she shared everything with them. The girls were naturally curious about their eccentric employer. As the girls started to feel more comfortable, the questions they asked became more direct until they learned about all my women and children. Tess also told them the rules she had learned the previous night about keeping her job, being useful and productive, and topping it all with getting pregnant.

Tess made it sound like the girls would receive my love once they gave me a child. Once that happened, they would become my family, and all doors would be open to them. They would lead a charmed life. It wasn’t about the money; it was about the lifestyle. Tess went into detail about my luxurious Monaco apartment. The girls looked at her as if she were telling fairy tales to children. She made the girls understand that, for the right person, there were endless opportunities, emphasising the most important of all—being part of a large family, a tribe where people love and take care of each other.

I yawned and stretched for effect, and the girls instantly changed the subject. The evening came, and I floated to the other side to watch the sunset. All of them joined me in this one magnificent moment. The sun came down and painted the water with red and orange, creating something magical. It made me feel so grateful and small, thankful for my life, not for the money and wealth but for all the love and friendships I made.

This was the true treasure of life, right in front of me, laid in front of my feet if only I bothered to look and understand. The light breeze came from the side, carrying with it the fine droplets of salty water as the powerful ship engines hummed. What could be more to life than this? And, for the first time, I felt true detachment. It was the feeling so intensely liberating. Life was enough, and all the riches and power of the world couldn’t give me the same sunset again. It was a humbling thought that made me feel so small but connected right in the moment.

The ship burst into light like a Christmas tree, setting the almost romantic mood. The only thing missing were the soft piano notes. It was another item to add to the list—the DJ, the pianist, and the rest of the entertainment. The equation had just become a little bigger.

Gaspard gave thirty minutes warning for dinner, so I got out of the water, looking all pruney and wrinkled everywhere except one place. Tess had been absentmindedly playing with my genitals below water, keeping my cock cocked, ready to shoot at a moment’s notice.

The girls giggled as they saw me exiting the cabin with my erect cock bobbing in front of me. They had all spent at least a week on the ship without even a vibrator for release. They were eager and primed for action. “What happens at sea is nobody’s business.“ I thought to myself as I offered my hand to Tess to help her out. The other girls immediately extended their arms, making me chuckle. I didn’t bother going through the pile to get my clothes; we needed someone to operate the laundry service.

Wherever I looked, I saw something missing. How did the captain think the twelve could handle all this? Then, I remembered what they teach at Carnegie Mellon University—views and viewpoints. His job was to take us safely from that place to this and ensure compliance with the rules. He was the lawmaker, judge, and executioner, the final arbiter of what happened on the water and the tyrant of the ocean. I should have seen that and compartmentalised, but I’ve never sailed before and missed everything.

Everyone went their separate ways to shower and change, and just as we were sitting down to dinner, the captain sent his apologies and requested a takeaway. He was now on duty, keeping watch over the water. I had a lucky break with the man despite being warned that he could be difficult. While I didn’t need a friend as my captain, I did require someone knowledgeable and responsible to ensure everyone’s safety and well-being. At that moment, I realised that I made a good choice.

It was late when we finished our food and drinks and went to bed. I noticed the jealous look in some sailor girls‘ eyes, watching Tess hold my hand as I led her upstairs. There was no doubt in anyone’s mind that Tess would get the fucking of her life, and some of the sailor girls were so turned on after our swim that they were practically eye fucking me all the time.

I knew it wasn’t fair, and I created this situation on purpose. It would be easy to say, “Dan made me do it,“ but I would be false. Dan only participated in my decision-making. He gave me the talk and explained the core principles, promising to expound on it the next time we met before he gave me a new set of assignments and things to practice.

Sometimes, I thought about what more there was to learn from him. After all, I surpassed even the most prolific men, except perhaps Hugh Hefner, who became a kind of my idol in all that. I didn’t aspire to be like him or admire his life, but I was in awe of what he created. The man had a clear vision of the life he wanted and made it without apologising to anyone. I wanted to mimic Heff, not because I was hungry for attention or wanted more women, but because he inspired me to keep true to myself. I had more than enough cash to afford such a lifestyle.

My birthday was approaching, and I would be turning forty-three. If I lived to eighty, that would mean just forty years, less than fifteen thousand days, and I intended to make each of them count. My entire plan, the entire enterprise, was designed to serve that singular inspiration.

As much as I learned from Dan, I learned from reading the books Jack recommended. A common theme through all of them was what it means to be a man and how to live one’s life like in “Ted,“ which had an uncanny resemblance to my own life.

“Live in the moment, life without regrets.” That’s what I learned, apart from how to be a man. “Carpe diem, seize the day.” I wanted to live each day in wonder, like it was the last one, because one day it would be, and all this would be gone. I wanted to look back at my past at the very last moment of my life, close my eyes and pass away with a smile to maybe another grand adventure. The purpose of life is to live it, not to be locked in the system that benefits the crooked and the obscene.

I became a wealthy person as well who relied on others to work and slave for me at least eight hours a day to make me even richer. There was no middle ground. You either win or lose, and I shed that past like an old snake skin. Perhaps that’s why most of my sailor girls looked at me in such a way. It wasn’t the large salary I paid them or the shallow thoughts of getting a wealthy man and receiving gifts and material possessions in exchange for all the arm candy and sex. It was much deeper and far more meaningful than that. They wanted to live the life I had and be part of something extraordinary. At the end of it, when I thought about it, all of us wanted the same thing. We say we don’t, but it’s just a lie. At the end of the day, we all want to live a good life, love, and be loved.

If someone offered me a trillion dollars to be the wealthiest man in the world, but I could never have an intimate relationship with another person again, no love, no kisses, no cuddles, no holding hands, and definitely no sex or children, would I take it? All our life plans and personal philosophies come to this, the simplest equation of all. No money in the world and no riches would be enough for someone to agree to this.

There it was, in a nutshell, the entire philosophy of human nature. All of us know what is truly important. Still, we delude ourselves with silly little games, get good jobs, chase promotions, and accumulate material possessions. Get a nice house, get married; it was all a scam. Someone, somewhere, decided this was “the way“ to get to what we truly desired, to confuse us all and keep us docile, then use our hands and brains, our ingenuity and brilliance, to further his own agenda and increase his personal riches.

The idiots around the world couldn’t see this trap. Look at the pissed-off feminists now insisting that a woman with a dick is a woman, and they belittle the lesbians for not wishing to suck another woman’s cock. All of it got so fucked up. Everyone shrugs when you ask them why. “It is a complex issue.“ We have a right to identify how we feel. Gender has nothing to do with biology. Abortion is a valid form of birth control“ Rah-rah-rah, bullshit and crap. Behind their precious feminist movement was a rich man rubbing his hands with a smile.

If men had all the power, why relinquish it? Because the population was growing uncontrollably. The workers were happy, and they were making babies. How do you slow the population growth and grow the business without creating a shortage of the workforce? Simple, send those lazy bitches into factories, keep the wages down, rinse and repeat. Convince everyone that coal is white, inject them with sixteen flu vaccines and make them wear masks, take away their rights to gather lest they start a protest, and police the means of communication, then send cops to their homes to “check their thinking“ when they repost something off the cuff on Twitter. Brainwash a bunch of retarded idiots, give them a platform to spew their vitriol, and don’t forget to kneel for a minute to virtue signal your support for the organisation that stole all the donations.

Don’t forget to hang enough rainbow flags on lamp posts and streets and inside shop windows, stock the primary school library with all the colouring books depicting gay sex and don’t forget to threaten the parents with criminal charges if they don’t put their kids on puberty blockers because they were confused. Hell, I was confused in my forties with all the propaganda and contradictory nonsense. Who knows, maybe I was secretly gay. I’m sure some gender studies professor somewhere who identified as a woman but couldn’t explain what a woman was without saying “an adult human female“ would say that I was overcompensating due to my own internalised conflict, oppressing my inner woman inside. “Here’s a primary school book that you missed, Jim. It will explain why you should have sex with the other men to feel liberated.“

I showed all this a finger. The motherfuckers messed with my children. If my sons were gay or they suffered a mental illness where they believed they were women, I would be a failure of a father to not notice that. What the cunts did instead, they normalised that kind of thinking, brainwashing my wife and confusing my children by exposing them to explicit materials, staffing the schools with propagandists and radical ideologue perverts, encouraging children to identify as minorities and victims.

They reduced the role of a father to the title of a glorified sperm donor with no rights or a say in anything relating to children’s development. Even in Hollywood, when you watch those stupid talk shows, notice how a white actress celebrates when her DNA test reveals that she is fifteen per cent some other race, so she could also play the minority card and claim she was oppressed when riding around town in her brand new Rolls Royce.

The West was exporting division and hate through radical sex and gender ideology, and it infected my children. I will never forgive this as long as I live, and I will hold a grudge until the day I die. I would spend millions supporting the opposition, and I would live in my own sheltered environment to keep my children safe from the perverts in government.

At heart, I was a liberal. If you want to feel like a pony and have sex with a horse, go ahead, but don’t expect me to participate in your sexual fantasy, and don’t you dare teach such things to my children. They are my responsibility, and until they are of legal age to know better, I will be responsible for educating them and teaching them values that I believe are correct for their psychological and physical development. That, and providing for them and keeping them safe, loving them with all my heart, is the job of a dad, and anyone who threatens that is going to get fucked.

We all had different values, and I respected that. The place where I was born and loved became infected with a “woke virus,“ a more deadly strain than corona that took years to manifest but was equally virulent. This only exposed the power of the media companies‘ grip over the populace.

Of course, it was easy to brainwash people into believing all sorts of nonsense. For years, they systematically eroded our values, demeaned manhood, and broke up our families, creating the Prozac generation. When you have kids as old as ten dependent on mood stabilisers just to be able to function and half of a class diagnosed with ADHD, addicted to their phones, sexting each other, performing blowjobs for a dollar in high school toilets just to be popular and gain followers, it means that we, as a society, should slam on the brakes, stop, and rethink the way we are going before it’s too late.

In my mind, it was already too late. I saw enough red flags, and I panicked. It was the love for my kids that gave me strength to fight, evolve, change my life and create a world for them where they would be loved and safe. I knew many wouldn’t agree with me, even openly criticise. It used to matter what others thought of me in some other story, in some other life, but not anymore. I was bitter and angry inside, a mere step from bursting into violence, but I channelled that energy into something productive, and here I was, dining on a super yacht with my gorgeous employees, far from the perverts.

I was creating a world that I wanted to live in, an invite-only, purpose-engineered private society that functioned outside the confines of the so-called real world. I made all the rules, supported by my women, who were fiercely loyal to me, precisely because they saw the big picture and what I was trying to build and wanted to help.

This was the main reason why I bought the ship. A few miles out, we were in the hands of the captain. I made the rules, and he was the law. There was no mainstream network news on the ship, and all the news companies were blocked through the internet. Netflix was blocked as well, including hundreds of other channels containing content that I found inappropriate, like the film “Cuties.” I bought a small Californian company that had the technology, fired everyone and kept the intellectual property, then tasked my developers to make me an ultimate content firewall. We licensed it to some government clients who paid us enough to keep an offshore team busy, making it better.

The sound of Tess’s voice jolted me from my inner monologue. I’ve been spacing out a lot lately due to the side effects of six months of stress. It was all coming out, and I was venting inside, going through all the negative emotions and letting them play out and dissipate. It was a part of my process of releasing stress. The worse I felt, the more closed off I became. I was a classical introvert.

While I mused about life, Tess ran us a nice bath with bubbles and called me in with a smile, curling her finger and waving her tail at me giggling.

“If you want this piece of ass, you better come and get it.” Now, how could I ever refuse an invite like this? She was the first of the second generation of my women, and I could see the difference. Tess spent a year adjacent to the system, taking care of me and my girls, watching them from up close, learning from them, getting sucked into our lifestyle.

“I don’t need the skill anymore,“ I told Dan the last time we met, but he was right; it wasn’t the skill but the identity that mattered. The so-called skill he taught me was just a crutch, a sort of positive enforcement mechanism to bring out the real me.

There are plenty of wealthy shisters around, flaunting their cash, calling themselves the top dogs. If you look at their women, they are all hookers who would dump them in a heartbeat as soon as someone richer came along. Dan was right about those pompous, obnoxious losers. They had a creepy vibe about them. If you saw them in a bar, you would steer clear of them. Dan showed me videos of some of them, and I couldn’t help but cringe. I spent hours watching those creeps just to make sure I had a good understanding of what not to do and as a prime example of how not to behave. Take away all their cash, and they wouldn’t be able to get laid. That was the dipstick to measure the dipshit.

Tess smiled at me as I entered the bath, sighing in pleasure and resting my back against the other side. I could see it in her eyes; Tess didn’t give a fuck about the money I had. She wanted to feel like all my girls felt and be a part of something bigger, enjoying my lifestyle, but more than anything, she liked me. I had my swagger, the way I spoke and acted. All of this, to the last bit, was learned behaviour. No man is born like this; we learn it by being presented with a good example.

This was the core that brought everything together. None of this wealth or lifestyle would be possible without it. If I were just some guy with more money than brains, I couldn’t have the same kind of success. I chose the women in my life, but they chose me as well. I learned to project that inner power and strength in a congruent, well-balanced manner.

Tess took my foot and massaged it a bit, then made a wicked smile and licked it. I jumped; it tickled. She took my other foot and looked me straight in the eyes before sucking my big toe into her mouth and massaging it with her tongue.

“Piss on me,“ she said as the warm water spray bounced against our skin inside a luxurious shower. Tess was a weird creature with some hardcore fantasies. It surprised me at first, but I would be a liar if I said it didn’t arouse me to no end. I didn’t even want to think about the psychology of why this happened.

Tess knelt in front of me, and I let go of the stream all over her face. Her entire body broke out in goosebumps. Tess opened her mouth, trying to swallow all that while furiously rubbing her pussy with her fingers. She was a dirty no-limits slut, and I loved her for that.

Immediately, as I finished, Tess buried her face between my legs, licking my asshole, trying to swallow my balls, moaning like a pervert. Tess liked it hard and rough. I wrapped her fiery hair around my hand and dragged her naked to the bed. It was time to christen it.

“Rape me,“ Tess begged, feeding her imagination. She admitted to me once that it was one of her most explicit fantasies. Of course, only as a play, not in real life, and that assured me she was still sane. Who am I to say what’s good or bad for someone? Invite me to participate, but don’t be angry if I don’t force me to play.

We played this game many times, or at least she did. Tess loved rough sex, and I obliged. What’s good for the goose, and that kind of thing. Tess stuck her sharp nails into my back as I bit her neck and pounded away. Indeed, there is something special about exclusive yachts. I smiled at the thought and jackhammered fast.

Chapter 49 - Home field advantage

“All hands on deck,” the first officer called, and the girls came out to help us moor the ship against a massive stone dock. The captain notified the authorities well in advance, declared our purpose and the length of stay, and received all the necessary clearances.

“Welcome to Croatia,” a uniformed official said. The inspection wasn’t necessary, but the two men asked to come on board anyway to check out the ship and marvel at its magnificence.

The men checked Tess’ and my passports, allowing us off the ship. Four trucks arrived, with four more queuing outside. The captain decided to restock and refuel the ship in Croatia before going to Italy for a refit. I sent all my requested changes to the Italian architect, and he assured me that the crew in the shipyard would be able to complete all the work in less than a week. I wanted to rearrange the rooms, create more space for the crew, and make a state-of-the-art gym inside with my personal trainer Kris’ help. She rose to the challenge and sent multiple emails with photos of the gym in London to the Italian architect.

I waved to the crew, and they waved back at us. The captain and the first officer saluted, and then we were on our way. A car waited for us outside to take us to town. The name of the place was Split. It was the second major city in the country that could easily fit in a corner of London by population alone. It was Dan’s home, and that was the reason why he had such a strong accent.

As soon as the car let us out in the centre, everything became perfectly clear to me, why Dan never left the place. The girls walking about were stunning and dressed to impress. They moved with such unconscious poise, swaying their hips and throwing everyone superior glances. If I had been born in Croatia and could speak the language, I would never have wanted to leave either. There was no doubt in my mind why Dan became a dating expert. If I had been surrounded by such gorgeous women since childhood, I might have chosen a profession like that. Due to a lucky draw or by the will of the almighty, Dan was blessed or cursed by being born in a place of incredible genetic beauty.

In this place, the sevens were sixes and fives on the M-scale were almost non-existent. Apparently, the Croatians liked their women tall and beautiful, with impressively feminine figures, slim, long legs with narrow waists and large natural breasts. They swayed their hips like models on a runway, trotting on high heels like prize horses to be admired but never touched or bridled, roaming free in the wilderness. They made Tess look ordinary. She was a seven, and I knew she noticed.

“This way,” I pointed, following the map on my phone. I led Tess from street to street, made of old weather-worn cobblestones, all looking ancient, polished by the feet of walking on them for centuries. Even the buildings were made using a mixture of materials, stone, brick, and concrete. The place told the story of a city that had been developing through time. Each ruler or conqueror left a different mark as he won and lost the wars. The Illyrians, Greeks, and Romans all came and went. They built their courts, walls and temples, but people remained.

We arrived at a large stone house that had been completely refurbished in a modern style. It was the best gynaecologist’s office, and Dan’s personal friend highly recommended him. Dan booked an appointment for Tess to remove her diaphragm so she could get pregnant. Tess discussed it with me after our first night of debauchery. She wanted to get pregnant like my other ladies and viewed it as a kind of right of passage, a membership of sorts to my inner circle.

It wasn’t true, but I didn’t want to correct her. If Tess wanted to have my child, I was more than happy to make her one. If there is one thing I learned from being a father, it is that I love having children. In my mind, they were the only true wealth anyone could make. I had the means and the setup to support having a lot of children.

In small family units with a husband and wife and two kids, it could be a nightmare if both parents worked. This is how the Western world transitioned from having three children to one and eventually to none over less than a century. Women entered the workforce, but salaries remained stagnant while the money supply was manipulated by those in power, turning it into worthless paper. As a result, one income was not sufficient to support a family, forcing both parents to work and provide for the family. This has exacerbated our current socioeconomic crisis, skyrocketing divorce rates, and the breakdown of traditional family values.

My setup was large and designed to grow and scale. At any point in time, multiple women were available to take care of children, and the ratio starts to get more favourable, the more women and the more kids you have. The younger ones get older and graduate from one stage to another, requiring different skill sets but getting easier to manage, and they can start to learn and participate in the education of others by being a good example.

The math worked, no matter how people felt about it. Of course, there were gaps and difficulties, but considering the trade-offs, it was undoubtedly the best system for keeping the family together and raising children.

Initially, my girls were sceptical, but once the boys arrived, their doubts disappeared, and they saw the benefits of the strict rules and hard work required to make it work. It was a tough job, but with dedication and adherence to the rules, the girls realised the importance of having children and fulfilling their biological purpose. For all our social and technological advances, biologically, we were still monkeys hardwired to fuck and procreate with a built-in drive and overriding biological prerogative.

All those colourful rainbow people, as lovely and nice as they might be, were destined for biological erasure. Nature doesn’t politicise or discriminate; it just tells them it is the end of their genetic line. We could all sit down and debate our sexual orientation and gender preferences, but the final arbiter doesn’t care about what we think we are, only about our biological imperative. Here’s the plan. You’re free to ignore it, but this is where your bloodline ends. A hundred years from now, only the biologically compliant will survive, and no scientific magic or social justice will change that. Sun rises and sets every day. The birds and the bees are just the facts of life. The rest is all just philosophy, weaponised by the radical people in power for their own purposes.

I left Tess with the nurse and walked out. My plan was to meet in a cafe with Dan while the nurse booked a car for Tess to take her to the hotel. It was my last meeting with Dan as a student, but over time, we got to know the measure of each other, and I was sure we would remain friends.

Dan pulled out his laptop and put it on the table. He showed me his radar graph, and my numbers were off the chart. I knew this wasn’t an exact science, but counting on Dan’s experience, it was as close as when a doctor listens to your lungs with a stethoscope or when a musician plays a chord on a guitar. The good ones just feel it. They say that good judgment comes from experience, and Dan wasn’t a spring chicken. He was about my age, or a little older, and he had been teaching people the same things all his life, refining his craft, turning it into an art. Even the shittiest software developer learns something after spending thirty years on the job, and Dan was an artist.

“You did well, Jim,” he said, shaking my hand.

“Does that mean that I graduated and you will finally let me into your secret group of friends?” Dan’s eyebrows rose. He wasn’t nearly as mysterious as people said. I did my research and my maths, and there was a rumour he was organising some secret group of like-minded men. Grr was one of them.

“I want in,” I said, and Dan laughed. If there was something else to learn, I would have all the time in the world. Since I started on this strange and incredible journey, I got to meet many interesting people. I knew for a fact that Dan had a secret side business, and some of the people from his group of clients enjoyed the benefits, no matter how much he denied it.

“Come on, out with it. What is it?”

“That’s not the way to talk to your teacher.” He was messing with me now, and I found it funny. Dan knew perfectly well that I knew all his tricks and conversational gambits, so he taught them to me.

“Tell me, Jim. What is the biggest problem in getting women?” I knew the answer.

Getting a girl in a bar or a club, in a restaurant, at the pool or a beach, even in queues when you wait to pay for your groceries, was easy. After I learned all Dan had to teach me, it was barely a challenge. On the other hand, finding the right ones, the beauties, the sevens, eights and nines, was almost impossible, and the competition was always immense. There is always some guy waiting his turn, not scared to punch you in the face if for no other reason than to prevent you from getting a woman he can’t have.

It all comes down to investment, Dan said, and I knew exactly what he meant. Dressing up and going to a bar or club is low-hanging fruit available to everyone. Women expect little and are spoiled for choice, and there is rarely any long-term value in that endeavour. Average guys pursuing average women for average relationships and average children. Even sex, if that’s the extent of it, would be average and boring with her lying drunk on her back, waiting for you to pleasure her. That’s not what I wanted or what anyone with taste or self-respect aims for. It’s the bottom of the barrel, the dregs of the ocean with cutup fishnets, broken bottles, and rusty toilet seats with coral growing on them.

“Now that you graduated and know the difference, we need to talk about the pipeline,” Dan asked me about my sailors and stewardesses and chuckled when I told him the story of how I got Tess. “This is your pipeline. That’s how you get quality women into your life. You set up the opportunity and set the rules. Those that find it appealing will recruit themselves.” I invested millions into my ship and my plane, and as a result of clever planning and strict hiring procedures, I would never run out of women who want to join my family and my tribe. I built it scalable and had enough “oomph” to handle everyone.

“My secret business is that I build pipelines for affluent clients,” Dan explained, detailing how he does it and showing me how it works. With a decent salary as an IT guy, one could become the owner of an off-the-shelf model agency or something similar. A boss fucking his young secretary is a cliche for a reason. Most successful relationships started in some sort of a pipeline, a school, university, office and like. How often do you see a happy couple married for thirty years, telling you they met in a club or a bar?

Dan had a team that would build such pipelines for him and his clients, involving them in social activities and creating opportunities for women to show their interest. Instead of a man trying to find a quality woman, the pipeline filters them to the exact specifications he likes. All he needed to do was to be friendly and meet them, seeing how they vibe together in some social setting.

This was the seduction on the next level. Dan was creating a product to bring the right quality women, and all one needed to do was allow those girls to seduce themselves, come to him and start the relationship.

It was as easy as that, instead of being a loser plying girls with free champagne in bars in the hope they would come down from their pedestal and give you a chance to demonstrate your qualities. Then, if she decided you passed the bar, she would tell you her terms, like no sex for the first three months, just so she could be sure that you are the right guy while she fucks her old boyfriend. I knew exactly the type; I was married to one. While I waited and paid for dinner, Tina was sleeping with her ex-boyfriend behind my back. I wasn’t interested in shit like that.

“It all comes down to your peer group,” Dan said and explained. A seven inside a bar full of fives is a princess. If we assume there were a hundred people, with about half of them women, of which there was one seven. The ratio of sevens to fives would be fifty to one, which meant that one girl would have more pull than the fifty others. It also meant that all fifty guys would try to get her to bed, making her the most valuable prize in that group.

The same girl in a different setting, such as at a model agency, would likely be paired with the other models. While personal preferences may vary, all of the girls would likely be attractive and well-presented without an obvious standout among them. As a result, she would have less influence or recognition than she would in the first peer group.

If a man came in who knew how to walk and talk and present himself and stand out in some way from the group through status or scarcity, he would be the unique one. If for no other reason than social pressure, some of the girls would feel compelled to flirt with the men, and the exact opposite scenario would happen.

The man would inform the girls of the rules and his expectations, and if the girl agreed to those, she would proceed to the next level. It amused me. That’s essentially what I did with my stewardesses and my sailor girls, based on Dan’s guidance. He was leading me towards the inevitable conclusion that I required a pipeline.

All of this could be seen as manipulative and highly unethical, and there were laws in place to prevent it. Rules for thee, but not for me. Just ask the egomaniacal mythomaniac at number ten. I chuckled. This is how that old guy Weinstein fell, trading movie roles for the girls in exchange for sex, then when it suited the powerful milking the “me too” movement; they dug it all up and crucified the guy for doing pretty much what others in that industry did at the time. To assume he was the only one promising film roles to budding actresses in exchange for a piece of a cream pie would be incredibly naive.

This was the problem with the short attention span combined with the continuous brainwashing narrative. It was easier to believe the fake news infotainment than using your brain after you fried it at work, getting paid a pittance for your services.

“I am interested,” I blurted. The idea was inspired. I didn’t want Dan to manage my pipeline, but I wanted his team to help set it up. We talked about the details, and I drew a diagram of a napkin with a pen I borrowed when ordering my coffee.

“There is one more thing I want to talk with you about,” I said and looked at me like always with a confident smile. “I want to thank you for all the help you gave my boys.” It worked out perfectly, but I was thinking about doing this regularly. “ I wanted to invest in a business that would involve purchasing a hotel or villa with recreational grounds and filling it with kids on a monthly basis. My goal was to provide an alternative for fathers with boys who were feeling pressured to change their gender by offering them a supportive environment with trained psychologists, peer groups, and male role models.

It would work like a Boy Scout troop with the best trainers money could buy. The parents could have their holiday and watch their boys play sports from afar, yet remain close enough to feel comfortable in case something happened. Many wealthy individuals get into philanthropy for the causes they are passionate about. This would be my way of helping the most vulnerable children who were failed by the radical ideological system, like my two sons.

We would use the extra funds to finance trips for those who cannot afford them and allocate a portion of our profits to organisations and lobbying groups that promote science and reason to combat those who claim that gender is an arbitrary, socially constructed concept.

”Sounds interesting. Let me talk with my guys and get back to you on that.“ Dan’s phone bleeped, and he looked around, and waved. I saw two gorgeous blonde girls walk across from the other side of the square, almost in slow motion, attracting everyone’s glances.

”Who’s that?“ I asked. Dan and I had an agreement from the start; no third parties were allowed during our chats. I assumed the deal was null and void since he was no longer my teacher and just my friend.

”Oh, I have to go. I’ve got a plane to catch. These two are a graduation present.“ He winked and shook my hand, turned around and left.

Hey, Dan!” he turned around. “I’ll be expecting an invite into that secret club you have that doesn’t exist.” He laughed and walked away, waving the back of his hand. It made me smile. I made it a condition for getting his “next level” services as he called “the pipeline,” and he knew that.

The two stunning blondes dressed in black tube top dresses approached the table, and I couldn’t believe my eyes. They were identical twins.

“How the hell did he find you?”

“I am sorry?” one of them spoke, unable to understand what I apparently blurted out loud. It was just like Dan to give me a present that would get me to invest in his “next level” project. Something told me I had no choice. Dan was a comedian with a panache for pulling practical jokes.

“I’m Jim,” I stood up and shook their hands. “Come, join me.” I waved the waiter over and ordered another cup of coffee and an ice cream that looked incredibly appetising. The girls ordered two hot chocolates and sat on the other side, measuring me up and down. I knew the type, and I almost laughed. A gift is never just a gift with Dan.

“How do you know Dan?”

“We worked at his model agency,” the twins chirped in unison, speaking with the same terrible accent as Dan. It was clear that this conversation was going nowhere, and the girls were simply waiting for me to lead the conversation as any other man would. Their insecurity about their mastery of the English language was evident, but it was a problem that they would have to deal with alone. That is the problem with uncomfortable silences. Men blink more often than women.

“Mmm,” I loved the taste of the ice cream. I sipped my coffee and stared at the girls. I was fine. My meeting with Dan ended, and I fulfilled my oath to the letter. I gave him a year and got what I wanted. The girls watched me quietly with their big eyes as I was absorbed in eating my dessert. Maybe they thought I would address them after I finished it, but I ignored them and waved the waiter over.

“This is excellent. Can you bring me another?” I really shouldn’t have since I was back on my diet and exercise regime, but the ice cream here was the best I ever tried. It was exquisite. I could see the nervousness in the girls’ eyes, and they started talking in tandem, possibly thinking I would just sit there and eat my ice cream again, ignoring them like I had done for the last ten minutes.

“Dan said that you might have a job for us.” Ah, the context. I knew what to do now. I shrugged and took the ice cream that arrived.

“What kind of job are you looking for? What are you good at?”

“We just finished the flight attendant school, but we could do something else if you wanted.”

“Why would you want to work for me? I’m sure there are plenty of jobs available.”

“Dan said that your minimum salary is a hundred thousand dollars a year.” I almost laughed. It was true. I paid my stewardesses the same as my engineers, not caring about the current market prices. The jobs the stewardesses did for me were equally valuable as anyone else, but I paid my pilots more for their specialist knowledge and experience, just like I paid senior engineers and team leaders more than the junior ones. The hundred thousand was just the baseline. It also gave me the pick of the litter and a right to impose my unusual hiring rules.

“Why do you want to become a flight attendant?”

“We want to travel around the world and experience a different life, and we don’t want to live here.” That was the perfect answer, and I smiled. I saw Tess looking for me on the other side. She was bored after checking into the hotel and went for a stroll to see the place. When Dan and I finished, I texted her the location, and she made her way to the square.

“This is Tess, and these two are Lana and Luna, although I can’t tell which one is which.” The girls giggled when I introduced them. All their movements and mannerisms were precisely the same. They were dressed equally and had the same makeup and hair. For all intents and purposes, the two looked like clones, perfect carbon copies of each other.

I gave my ice cream to Tess, and she dug into it, making quiet noises. I looked at her and asked, “Isn’t it the best?” Tess nodded, trying to quickly stuff all of it down her throat.

“The ice cream is the same everywhere,” one of the twins added. I called the waiter over and ordered another round of drinks and a large cup of mixed flavours for everyone.

“I want a recipe for this. How can I get one?” The waiter laughed, thinking I was joking, and the girls offered to help me with that.

“I’ll tell you what. You make me an ice cream like this, and you are hired.” The girls’ eyes popped wide, and they looked at Tess as if to ask her if I was joking. She giggled and shook her head.

“He is serious. Do this, and Jim will hire you.” That motivated the girls, and they started talking about the food, telling me how their pizza was better than the Italian one. They bombarded me with local knowledge about all the soups, stews, grilled meat, fish, and even hamburgers.

“Okay, if you get hired, I expect you to find me an assistant chef who can make all that.” As great as Gaspard was, he couldn’t possibly cook for fifty people each day, and having another chef with a different, more pedestrian taste palette would nicely augment Gaspard’s skillset. The girls stared, bombarding me with questions, and I raised my hands.

“Tess is a stewardess. You should make good friends. She will be evaluating your skills and doing the most of the training with her colleague.” The girls started talking at full speed, sharing experiences and bonding. They were young and impressionable, only eighteen.

For the last couple of years, the twins had this dream to visit all the great places they heard of in stories and hatched a plan to skip university and get themselves certified as stewardesses. They did all the training and have already gone through all the hoops. The only thing they missed was on-the-job training, for which I would give them a three-month probationary period with half the salary, but Tess would explain everything. I had more important things to do with my life, and I smiled, eating the best ice cream ever and planning my future.

Chapter 50 - New Beginnings

“Surprise!” all the girls shouted as soon as I entered the villa. I was sure that Iqbal knew what was happening, but he said nothing when he picked us up at the airport; he was obviously in on it.

The biggest shock was seeing the Florida girls, Rylee and Callie, who flew commercial just to surprise me. Both of them were pregnant to their teeth, and they ran into my arms with eyes full of tears. I missed them so much, and we talked online all the time. The two wanted to graduate ahead of time and committed all of their efforts to that enterprise.

All the girls gathered in Dubai to witness the birth of my new child. Amy was the first to get pregnant, but the rest of them weren’t too far behind. I planned to stay there for four to six weeks, and there was a chance someone else would give birth at that time.

The pilots finally got their well-deserved break. I granted them a month to allow the plane to be cleaned, refitted, and refurbished. Although it still appeared perfect and was meticulously maintained, some of the carpets and furniture inside had started to show some wear. I decided to replace them with new ones. I also planned to make a few changes to the plane by removing certain parts that were unused and transforming them into a more suitable design for my own purposes. The second conference room proved to be a waste of space, so I opted to convert it into a lounge area with leather sofas and entertainment systems. Additionally, I planned to remodel another room that was practically unused to the playroom for kids to keep them entertained.

Since the plane was grounded, I asked the stewardesses if they wanted to go home. All four of them preferred to stay in Dubai. God knows we had enough spare rooms in the villa, so they could stay as long as our living arrangement wasn’t too strange for them. The stewardesses readily agreed, so I had Iqbal bring us home with a van instead of cramming inside the Hummer.

That night, I fell asleep in the master bedroom with six pregnant girls on top of me, cuddling with Amy, Rylee, and Callie. We spent the evening talking about how we met and the journey we all had to go through to get here. It was sweet, loving, and special, and I felt blessed. We were all starting a new chapter of our lives where the sky was the limit. I had to take care of just a few more things before we embarked on this new adventure.

I ran out of plans for the first time since my divorce. I didn’t want anything else or desired more than I had. They said I should invest my money smarter to maximise my profits and get the best return on investment. I didn’t care much for it. Only a favourable set of circumstances mixed with opportunity and my moral ambiguity allowed me to get far, capitalise, win big, and gamble. I was done with all that, believing that the key to a good life was to know when to call it a day.

Deep in my bones, I felt the turning of the tide. Something great was about to happen. I could sense the electrifying expectation in the air. All the girls went to bed early that night. We were waiting for a new life to come out into this world. All the future mothers were expecting that moment. All of us were prepared and waiting for the day. I could almost taste the emotional undercurrent like fine, pointy, rain-dropping pins against my bare skin.

The next day began with screams and giggles as Liam and Callum ran around, searching for their father and waking up everyone. I remember being the same way at their age, full of energy and waking up with the sunrise. My mother had a tough time dealing with me, and my father was nowhere to be seen or any male figure. It was just the two of us, my mother and me.

The boys jumped on the bed, ending up in a hugging and kissing centipede. All the girls loved the boys immeasurably. The two were like their biological children. There was no difference.

“Okay, okay, I’m up. Please go terrorise Neneh while I take a shower.” The kids ran out like bullets. The house wasn’t childproof, but the women taught the kids not to run on the stairs. Apart from minor scrapes and bruises, the boys were perfect, and the girls did a fantastic job taking care of them.

By the time I got downstairs, the girls had already made breakfast. Their cooking skills have improved immensely since their training. I saw that the girls enjoyed it, so I paid a lot of different chefs to come in and teach them how to prepare various dishes once a month over a weekend. They learned from Thai, Chinese, Italian, French, and Lebanese chefs—all the best ones I could find. They cooked and tried new things, filling the fridges with leftovers for the rest of the week.

“Who wants to go for a stroll in town?” I asked at the dining table, and all the girls eagerly raised their hands, wanting to join me. On the other hand, the boys wanted me to take them to see the kind lady who gives them dates.

“I should buy a bus,” I joked while driving my electric Hummer, followed by Iqbal in a packed van. With the kids in tow, transportation would be a nightmare. I had already thought about that, and a bus was out of the question. It required a different category license and wouldn’t be allowed on all sorts of roads. On top of that, even the best-looking ones appeared cheap. That’s why I put in an order for ten custom eight-seater electric Hummers.

I was tempted to buy a few sports cars like most other nouveau riche millionaires so I could measure my dick against theirs and rev it to impress the ladies with silicone lip fillers. I was never interested in fame and wealth, but grand designs require sacrifice. None of this was an accident.

We strolled through Madinat Jumeirah, going from store to store, until I stumbled against a closing one right in the middle. A nice Syrian woman was going out of business. She lived in one of the places decimated during the bombing campaign, where she lost her husband and sons, ending up alone with a young daughter. Somehow, through the help of family and friends, she managed to move to Dubai and opened her trinket store for passing tourists. Unfortunately, the business was bad over the past few years, and she blew through her savings until she was forced to go out of business.

I had an idea and took her to the side, pulling Lana and Luna with me. It was a simple proposal. I offered to back her business if she converted it into an ice cream store serving the Croatian recipe. The woman liked it immediately and accepted my offer. It was a fair deal. After she paid all the bills and the salaries, whatever she made, we would split fifty-fifty as equal partners. This was about something other than profit for me, but my girls and I liked to come to Madinat Jumeirah often, and I wished I could have some great ice cream and coffee while the girls did their shopping.

My secret plan was, if that worked, to open an ice cream store in every mall where the girls and I shopped, offering coffee and tea, maybe even some cake, good coffee, and free high-speed internet. I could sit in such a place forever, tap on my phone or work on my computer while my girls explored.

Everyone had a great time. The boys pulled my hand to the data store, where the kind saleswoman let them try some for free. Of course, it was good business because I spent at least a hundred bucks on dates every time she did that. With many girls tracing my footsteps, I was bound to buy half of the store.

Little did the people know that one of the first purchases I made after selling my business was to buy that little date store and ensure it stayed in business. It was one of my little vanity projects. I loved those dates; they were delicious. I even got the old Count Conti hooked on them. He ordered tens of thousands of dollars worth of the dates for himself and as gifts for his friends. The shop could prosper just on that one customer, and his special orders were as extravagant as the man himself. The world changes once you become a billionaire; little things seem more important, and you learn to appreciate them.

We ended up at our usual restaurant, Neneh’s favourite, where they welcomed us with open arms and gave us the best private room with connected tables. The waiters didn’t even take orders, knowing it would take forever to choose any variations the girls liked. They made a deal with me a long time ago that whenever we visited, they would just feed us. It seemed more natural and spontaneous, passing the burden of choice onto our gracious hosts. They preferred it this way as well.

The girls took the newcomers on a boat ride around the canals, ending at Jumeirah beach, where we walked and sat in the shade while the boys played in the water. We were quite the spectacle, with tourists passing by and a group of women, half of whom were dressed in stunning abayas and hijabs.

When we moved to Dubai, at first, the people we met didn’t know what to think about us. Still, the people gave us a pass thanks to Neneh’s insistence that the boys go to the mosque and her dedication. Of course, we would be breaking a few laws and living together in my big house, but Dubai was accommodating, so they let us live in our little enclave. After receiving my final payment, I donated a million to Neneh’s mosque of choice, which sealed the deal in terms of speculation and intrigue. Even the most judgmental people looked the other way and let us be.

We arrived home in the late afternoon, following a leisurely stroll through the air-conditioned halls of the Mall of Emirates. The girls were eager to peruse some new clothing items. Due to their changing bodies, there was never enough even when the girls shared. It felt good to be back home after a day out, and we all collapsed onto the sofas and brand-new designer bean bags.

While I was away, the girls decided that bean bags were the most comfortable when they were pregnant, so they bought a whole lot of them and dragged them into the living room, where they could sprawl like cats and gestate.

I had just made a fresh batch of coffee and a pitcher of hot chocolate with marshmallows for the ladies when I heard a scream, followed by another one. Everyone started talking at once. I quickly rushed into the living room, only to see Amy standing in a semi-squatted position, looking at me like a deer caught in headlights.

“My water broke,” she said, and everyone panicked. We had discussed this and practised it numerous times, but when it actually occurred, no one knew what to do and was running around like a headless chicken.

“Stop, calm down, everyone,” I shouted, barking orders, holding the phone against my ear. “Come, come, let’s go,” I urged Amy to walk, but she only stared at me with her big blue eyes, looking petrified. I smiled at my little exhibitionist angel, took her in my arms and carried her to my Hummer. Iqbal was there, and I asked him to drive as none of the girls were calm or collected. I didn’t want to end up in an accident.

Cassie and Shay joined us for moral support, while Neneh and Tara started calming everyone down, getting them ready to visit the hospital as soon as Iqbal’s son arrived to drive his people carrier.

We were at the hospital within minutes. The nurses waited for Amy and rolled her into maternity, instructing the rest of us to stay. Amy was fine; she would be safe. It was the best possible ending for a beautiful day. I knew from my previous experience that this could take a while, so I found my way to the canteen and got us some drinks.

An hour later, all the girls arrived, joining us in the waiting room. When the doctor came out, she instantly spotted a bunch of pregnant women and rolled her eyes. The way everyone looked at me left little doubt about who the father was. She saw my boys sitting on chairs, swinging their legs in boredom and smiled. At least I made good-quality children, reducing the chance of a nasty surprise.

Around three thirty at night, the doors to maternity opened, and the nurse entered the waiting room, smiling and waving me over. All the girls were asleep in their chairs except Neneh, who nodded, letting me follow the nurse and see my woman and child. The nurses had already redressed Amy and rolled her into recovery. She was half-sat in the bed, propped with multiple white pillows behind her back. Her eyes were bluer than ever before, and her tears rolled down without stopping.

Amy held a wrapped bundle of joy in her hands. She had given me another son and decided to name him Nathan. As she looked at me, she began to cry uncontrollably. I went up to her and gently kissed her forehead.

“I love him so much,” she said, unable to control herself.

I love you both.“ Amy squeezed my hand and sobbed while I dried tears from the corner of my eyes. It was over. This was the moment where my life turned. Whatever happened before was gone. It was day one, the beginning of the rest of my life. Everything in my life so far led to this moment, the final crossroads, and I said within myself the final farewell to the man I could barely remember. I let go of my past, every shred of it, celebrating the new life, mourning my death, or at least the death of who I used to be. The old me had to die for the new me to be born. I had to cut the umbilical cord that connected me to my past, let go of everything, and detach from it all.

”First comes detachment. It is a precursor to faith. The only way, Jim, to win in this game is to refuse to play.“ My friend Jack’s words echoed in the distance. I recalled asking him, ”How did you get so wise?“ He chuckled, patting my back.

”You will know in time, Jim. I am sure of that,“ Sometimes Jack would quote someone, some sage, most likely an imaginary figure that used to speak in riddles like ”a rich man walks barefoot in the sand.“ It made no sense there, but I started to understand. ”Knowing that you don’t know anything is the beginning of wisdom. There is a difference between being smart and wise.“ Jack was full of such sayings and proverbs that made me think what it all meant.

Dan taught me how to think and act, and he became my first male role model. However, Jack was more subtle, and he made me understand. He gave me tasks because it amused him, opened a door, often with a riddle, then watched to see if I would walk through it if I would pay attention and try to find answers to questions he never asked. Jack taught me how to seek. He told me the secret and gave me the key to shed my ego and discover my id, the inner self, who I was beneath all the garbage, the final layer of lies, the final mask behind which was me alone.

I bent down slowly and gave my new son the gentlest of kisses, letting him rest against his mother’s bosom. ”My god!“ I whispered into the nothingness; Amy and I had performed a miracle. We had made another human being out of love. We had created life.

People sometimes ask silly questions like ”Is there a god?“ or ”What happens after death?“ Instead of looking up at the sky for answers, they should look closer to where they live—into their own children’s faces. Is there any greater proof of divinity than creating life itself? Only God has that power, and he has also given it to us. We see it as simply nature—living, eating and procreating, but there is so much more to it than just biology.

Buddhists traditionally respect all living beings. Perhaps we should honour and respect the ultimate power, the gift we were given, and life itself. To become a Buddha means to be enlightened. It is achieved by seeking the truths inside, not out there, and learning four noble truths about suffering, following the eightfold path. I needed a guide, but I found my truths inside, and now that I saw my child, I could feel my love. It burned through me and spread like a fiery avalanche, consuming me through and through. It was a reward like no other. All that this child could be, all the possible futures, Amy held in her soft hands, letting him sleep on his first day of this life.

Inside my heart and mind, I swore to the gods that I would fight tooth and nail and die before I would let anything bad happen to this thing. I would burn the world and piss on its ashes; I would unleash the apocalypse if someone even looked at him the wrong way. This little kid gave me a purpose. He quickened my faith, and my mind was clear now. All the veils had been lifted, and above everything and all, I knew who and what I was. It might not sound glamorous or extraordinary, but it meant everything to me. I was a father; that was my identity.

***

Massive celebration awaited Amy when she got home. I thought Nathan would cry, but he just looked up at all those aunties and his two older brothers, all wanting to see the beautiful boy. Amy was worried about how his teeth would turn out, and it was only the threat of spanking that made her calm down. The young mother bombarded the internet with pictures of her baby boy and received many good wishes. Poor kid didn’t even have a chance to live for more than a day, but he already had thousands of followers on the Instagram Amy set up for him.

Nathan Allen had a ring to it. I obtained his birth certificate and paternity test, which confirmed that he was indeed my son. I then mailed both documents to the appropriate authorities to establish his nationality and obtain his travel documents. My embassy was pleased to assist me with this process.

With Natan put to sleep as the first baby room customer, we all gathered downstairs and celebrated, hugging and kissing the young mother, who could finally sit down, eat regular food and have a cocktail. Amy suffered little from being pregnant, partially because she was so young and partially because of all the creams and lotions the girls rubbed their skin with five times a day. Still, she fretted, stood in front of a mirror and pointed at every microscopic part of her body that wasn’t the way she remembered.

”Come with me,“ I pulled on Amy’s hand the following morning, right after breakfast. Tara and the American girls joined us in my Hummer. Ten minutes later, we parked in front of a three-story glass building. When we walked in, the girls gasped. It was the most modern and luxurious gym they had ever seen in their lives.

”I got all of you a membership here,“ I said, failing to mention on purpose that I owned the place. I worked with the best sports consultants and architects, leasing closely with Kris, my personal trainer from London, to create this magnificent work of art. It was inspired by the level of service I had in London, only modern and stylish with more amenities.

The girl at the entrance greeted everyone, and I guided them upstairs, showing them around each room until we took the elevator to the basement, where there was a large pool, hot spa, massage rooms, sauna, and wellness facilities. It was like being in an exclusive fitness centre.

The place was still open, and it was understaffed. I applied the same formula for finding my gym employees as I did for my plane and for my ship, but I insisted on at least a bachelor’s degree in sports, nutrition or medicine. All those gorgeous doctors who washed out to become fashion models were welcome to work in my gym.

I quickly realised that with the number of pregnant women I had, recovery, nutrition, and post-natal care, I would be looking at millions in medical and cosmetic expenses, and I didn’t trust half of them. There was an opportunity in this, so I set up my own gym. I knew firsthand what a great gym should look like and how it should operate, so I modelled it based on my experience, augmented by expert advice.

When I calculated all the costs I would pay over time for the same quality and service I had in the UK, I could run the gym out of my pocket and still end up better off than if I sent my girls elsewhere. With that in mind, I created a piece of art with a view to going live after Amy gave birth, but I was behind my schedule.

I invented my own operating model. The gym would be staffed by the girls I directly employed and trained. All the beautiful girls could apply for the free membership and come for an interview, and if they had the looks, we would let them exercise for free, under the condition that they come at least once per week.

All other female members would have to pay one thousand dollars per month or ten thousand dollars a year, and all the men would have to pay ten thousand dollars per month or a hundred thousand dollars a year with a discount. I didn’t tell my plan to anyone because I didn’t want to hear that it can’t be done. Who in their right mind would pay ten thousand dollars for a month?

It turns out that my assumption was accurate, as the gym had already accumulated over a hundred free members, and six guys had paid for a year’s membership, resulting in a profit of six hundred thousand dollars in just the first month. I had to give Ahmad ten per cent as he agreed to be my local sponsor for the gym. Initially, he requested five per cent, but I offered him an additional five per cent if he introduced me to his wealthy friends, which he did, and all six members came from him. In fact, he has already paid off what he cost me and made a profit on top of that.

The principle was straightforward: offer free membership to attractive young women, and men would flock to the club in the hopes of winning their affections. It was common knowledge that many of these Instagram models had a side hustle. My contribution was to provide them with a platform to showcase their talents and a juice bar where they could work on their laptops.

On Fridays, the pool area was closed to men so that women wearing modest clothing could undress and swim without being watched by men. This principle was also applied in Dubai to certain parts of the beach. I didn’t want to go against the norm or reinvent the wheel, as what’s good for the geese is good for the gander.

The girls were ecstatic about what I had built and excitedly punched my shoulder. It took them a minute to realise that I was the mastermind behind everything. To my surprise, I wasn’t as mysterious as I thought I was. Amy embraced me tightly and gave me a kiss in front of everyone.

”Thank you, Jim,“ she said, knowing she was on my mind. They were all my girls and partners. Together, we worked hard in our own capacity to create something greater than the sum of its parts. I thought this was what a relationship should be, whether you do it with one person or twenty.

The girls loved the place so much that they wanted to exercise and blamed me for everything, punching my shoulder with fists in mock anger because I didn’t tell them how to dress. I led them to the juice bar, and on the other side was a shop that still remained clothes until I could adequately staff it.

I opened it and found a wide range of Juicy Couture and Creative Recreation shoes, sports equipment, trinkets, and a selection of swimwear. It had everything you could possibly need at a gym, even if you forgot to pack your bag. I thought having a vanity sports store would be appealing to customers, so I made a deal with local retailers to run an outlet. They paid me a flat rate for shelf space, and I got ten per cent of every sale they would make, which would cover the salary of an employee working there.

The girls were thrilled to loot the store, take what they needed, and christen the equipment. One of the on-duty personal trainers approached them and instructed them on how to operate the machines. I was pleased to see that and felt motivated. Within a week, all the new staff with medical degrees would arrive to concentrate on nutrition, skin, general health, rehabilitation specialists, and sports masseuses. It would also allow me to focus on my own health and return to my regular exercise routine of two hours five times a week.

Over the next week, all of my girls went to the gym, and I slowly built up my old routine. Of course, the pregnant girls couldn’t do strenuous exercises, but one of the certified yoga instructors arrived. When I saw them breathe together, I called my headhunters to find me a trained midwife and a couple of accredited nurses.

About four weeks after I arrived, the family fell into a regular routine, going in and out and taking care of the children. I resumed my work by getting into the Dubai office and working in person with my team onshore. The business I set up there was growing slowly and steadily. Life reached a new equilibrium of sorts. I was happy, and the girls were ecstatic. For now, they were satisfied with their lives, and even when everything changed, I planned to involve them in a range of business activities and give them greater purposes than just being mothers.

Chapter 51 - Tasty Treats

I stood at the docks with Tara, watching the ship arrive. All the onlookers watched as the vessel moored. It gathered quite the crowd; some even clapped. It was the largest and most luxurious ship there.

The sailor girls spotted me as I strolled down the dock and greeted me with a wave. The captain and the first officer stood at attention high above and saluted like soldiers. I turned to see the crowd staring at me, likely wondering, “Who is that guy?”

All sailors cheered as I climbed up. Their number had doubled, but they were still not at full strength. Everyone looked at me as if I were a god. I was willing to bet that the girls from the first batch told all kinds of stories, some of them grossly exaggerated. I greeted them all and made a little speech, welcoming the new sailors into my employment, pretty much the same speech I gave the first time.

Gaspard greeted me with a big hug, introducing me to Alma and Petra, the assistant chefs. Both girls came through Lana and Luna, who connected Gaspard with the best cooking school in Croatia. Initially, I thought of getting only one additional chef, but Gaspard understood perfectly what I wanted to achieve, so he got a chef who specialised in baked goods, pizza, dough, and bread and another one who specialised in ice creams and cakes. He flew to Croatia from Italy while the ship was refitted and personally selected the top ten chefs matching my general criteria—young, tall, slim, and gorgeous. Apparently, they were easy to find in Croatia.

From the ten applicants, Gaspard selected the two by hiring a professional kitchen for a day inside a large restaurant that had yet to open. He watched the girls work, assessing their every move, precision, and cleanliness before tasting what they prepared. I patted his back for a job well done, convinced that if Gaspard approved of them, I would love what they made. He also pointed out the restaurant staff and the waitresses. We went from two to five, with another five on standby in case we had many guests.

After greeting everyone, the first officer took me around to see what had changed. I was awed and impressed by the complete remodel of some rooms inside. Now, I had the same gym setup inside a ship as I did outside. It was my plan from the beginning to allow gym staff to work onshore or on the ship, allowing for the continuity of training. The worst thing about travelling was the interruption in my exercise routine, so I bit the bullet and applied the same solution Alexander The Great used to a Gordian knot problem.

I heard a commotion outside, so I went out on the main deck to notice a man in kandurah trying to board. He was part of a group of nine men, most of whom surrounded a tall guy with a kaffiyeh, a chequered scarf hiding his face. What made it special was the presence of a woman wearing a black abaya with a niqab covering her face. Even from this distance, I could recognise those green eyes. It was the woman I met in Madinat Jumeirah that day.

Without a second thought, I welcomed the man. It was the first guest I received on the ship, and he seemed to be of some importance, judging by the company he kept. After all the little clues I had analysed over time from whatever I heard or what nobody would tell me about that woman, I gathered that she was important. I even learned her nickname, Shams, but nobody would say to me who she was or where she came from, partially out of respect and partially out of fear I could see in their eyes. They wouldn’t even repeat her full name, just shaking their head whenever I asked. Clearly, Shams was not someone to be messed with.

“Ah, you are the one who owns that executive plane parked at the airport,” the man said as we introduced ourselves. It seems someone was paying attention during the inspection, and word got around. While I was busy with the gym and spending time with my children, the plane had been fully serviced and refitted. I haven’t seen it yet, but I offered to take the man on a tour, and he graciously accepted with a handshake.

By the time I finished showing the ship to the man, a small coffee table was set with freshly made Arabic coffee inside an ornate silver pot and expensive-looking cups. There was some fresh cake of a kind I had never seen before and a box of dates filled with honey dipped in white chocolate with Arabic writing in gold on it. Tara saw that I wanted to leave a good impression and immediately called the date shop to bring up a box with a motorcycle. The delivery boy broke all the speed rules to ride like a maniac and bring me that box before I sat down to honour the man.

Khalid, the man who came to visit, thanked me for my hospitality before taking a seat and complimenting the chef on the cake. I tried it, and it was lovely. Khalid and I talked about this and that, mostly about my gym, ship, or plane. He never asked me how I got my money or what was my business. He either knew already, or it was impolite. I was far from being an expert on Middle Eastern cultures. The one thing I learned about the Arabs was that they respect honour and are gracious hosts, so I tried to be one, opening my ship for a visit.

“I would love to see how it handles the open water,” Khalid said, admiring the vessel.

“Why don’t you invite your friends and family, and we’ll make a day trip out of it, maybe visit Doha, Manama or Kuwait, let the women go sightseeing or shopping while we enjoy a nice meal prepared by my chefs.” Khalid’s eyes glistened, and he accepted, choosing Manama, the capital of Bahrain. The women in his household often visited, so they knew where to go and had many friends there. At that moment, one of the waitresses arrived, bringing us two magnificently designed cups of ice cream.

“This is the best ice cream I’ve ever tasted,” the man exclaimed with a wide grin on his face.

“I stumbled upon it myself and decided to hire a chef,” I told Khaled about my agreement with the woman to be my business partner and my plan that if everything went smoothly, I would rent a space in the malls my girls frequently visited. The man laughed, slowly beginning to comprehend how my thought process worked. I didn’t undertake any of these activities for financial gain but to enhance my life and please my women.

“Are you sure you’re not an Arab?” the man joked, loving the taste of ice cream and asking the waitress to bring more. “You must open an ice cream shop in this place.” He showed me a map of the mall near where he lived, telling me that I would ruin his life if his wife tried the ice cream, but the only shop was far away.

It was funny, and we laughed while the girls brought another serving with different flavours mixed with freshly cut fruits. Khaled was having a great time, and I enjoyed talking with him about his likes. In his spare time, he taught a small junior basketball team. He even flew in a specialist from America to spraypaint his Rolls Royce with basketball-themed graffiti.

When it was time for him to leave, the girls packed Khaled an icebox full of various flavours. We set the date two weeks from then to bring everyone out into the sea and sail the ship to Bahrain. It would be the perfect timing, as I expected to be full-strength on staff by then. We shook hands and said our goodbyes, and then I texted Neneh to organise special abayas for all the sailor girls for the event. I didn’t want to make my guests feel uncomfortable.

Neneh texted me back, telling me she would get right onto it tomorrow or the next day. She was in the hospital with Cassie, who went into labour an hour ago. I said goodbye to everyone, taking Tara with me and making my way to the hospital. Four hours later, I was a dad again, kissing Cassie and Alfie, my new son. Cassie was in tears from happiness, loving her little boy more than anyone. When she saw him smile at her, that was it for Cassie.

“I want another and another,” she said, hugging me tight. Cassie had always wanted to be a mom; now that she was one, nobody in the world could be happier.

“Are you ready?” I asked.

“For what?” Cassie looked at me, so I gave her a sly smile, got up, and opened the doors, and the invasion of squealing women started. Poor Alfie looked at all this circus before him, probably thinking, “Get me back inside.” It was warm and cosy, and no crazy ladies cooing at him, acting infantile.

“How do you like this duet?” Tara asked me later, watching the two babies crying their hearts out, competing over which one had better lungs. I laughed, rustling her hair. Tara was still trying to get pregnant, bursting into tears every time she got her period.

“I’m waiting for the orchestra to arrive.” All the girls looked so pregnant, ready to pop in the next few months. Tara giggled, hugging me tight. Her love for me was immeasurable, as was mine for her and all my ladies, but it paled compared to how I loved my children.

It was a busy time as new staff arrived. Initially, I had a hiring ban on anyone outside of the UK and the US purely for cultural reasons. I wanted to avoid any favouritism or issues that might arise from different cultures. The recruiters were pulling their hair out, screaming at me, telling me that my conditions made it impossible for them to find the right people. Still, I was a stubborn old goat who stuck to my guns.

When I saw how well Lana and Luna integrated, and after just a month spent living and working with English speakers, their command of the language increased by leaps and bounds. So, I changed my mind. There are many ways a cat can be skinned, but I refused to apply creative thinking to recruitment. I was paying them plenty of cash to solve my staffing problems.

As soon as I relaxed the ban, I had many choices—Eastern Europeans, Russians, Argentinians, Brazilians. There were too many applicants with all sorts of degrees, so I tightened the looks rule, threw out the sevens and only wanted eights and above, the truly incredible genetic specimens, the girls that would leave any man breathless. That thinned the herd, and I picked out my personal favourites. There were over fifty girls on the way to Dubai or getting their documents sorted.

I was haemorrhaging cash on recruitment companies, so I decided to cut the fat and bought the best one, firing the unnecessary staff and converting it into my human resources department. I faced a growing headache with all the small shops and businesses, so I solved the problem by passing it on to someone else and saving money in the process. I kept all those finders’ fees and nonsense in my pockets, paying good salaries, much better than my employees had made under previous management. That was my entire business plan—cut out the middleman and pocket the difference. Dan would say I was building my pipeline.

If there was any doubt about the success of my Dubai enterprise, it was all gone. Since I met with Khalid, ice cream sales have increased by a thousand per cent. There were queues in front of the shop with people waiting for their cones. I had to hire four more people and buy a shop next door to handle the demand.

As a form of gratitude, the next ice cream shop I opened was in the mall Khalid wanted. When I talked about renting the place with the mall manager and explained what I wanted and why, he gave me the best spot at half the price and offered help with his team to set it all up. The shop was up and running within a week.

This wasn’t the only business that underwent a renaissance. Suddenly, out of nowhere, over a hundred men joined the gym, adding a million dollars to my accounts every month. This was enough to double the gym staff and turn it into the best gym in the world, at least inside my eyes. As soon as the new members started parking their Lambos, Ferraris, Bugattis, and other cars in front, there was an invasion of gorgeous women applying for free membership. The staff chose the most beautiful ones; the rest were sent to pay a thousand dollars a month, and some did. We had over fifty paying female members.

It just goes to show the importance of making friends and how you treat them. I treated Khalid with honour and respect, offering him friendship and hospitality, and he put in a good word with the people who respected him. One hand washes another, and the face washes both. Ultimately, any relationship with people is about the face, the honour and respect we show each other. It’s not the contract but the handshake that matters. When you build such a reputation that you won’t need contracts anymore, you’ll know that you are a man—not just in your own eyes or the eyes of women, but in the eyes of people who have earned your respect.

On the day of the cruise, the girls had outdone themselves. I had poached one girl named Indigo from a sizeable five-star hotel chain. They had given her a scholarship and tied her into a contract that paid a pittance, preventing her from working in the hotel industry for ten years if she quit her employment. The worst part was that she wasn’t just good at it but absolutely gifted. I showed her the ship and said, “Impress me,” and Indigo outdid herself.

There were girls in the abayas acting as ushers. Indigo had them learn a few Arabic words that say welcome. The ship was exquisitely decorated with tables and seats everywhere. I told Indigo to expect around a hundred guests, but one hundred and twenty came. The captain allowed Khalid’s oldest son to sound the horn, and the ship sailed out, followed by the curious looks of hundreds of people on the dock.

“It handles so nice,” Khalid said, enjoying the dates with his nonalcoholic cocktail. The kids quickly discovered the large pool inside, so the girls blocked off the access to men, allowing mothers to come in and swim with them. Indigo proved to be an outstanding manager. While everyone worked, she sat in her office and coordinated, getting the info on her phone in real time and barking orders. Employing her was the best decision I made, and the hotel chain didn’t even realise their loss until it was too late, or perhaps they didn’t care. Those large monolithic management structures didn’t respond well to someone as dynamic and agile. I gave Indigo a simple order to impress me with her skills and what she made.

Everything worked out perfectly with fifty-seven permanent staff and eleven borrowed from the gym, just in case. When our female guests discovered salons and spas, all of them wanted to try a massage. Most of them didn’t have the foresight to bring their swimwear, but luckily, Indigo was ready for that. She mirrored what we made in the gym and used a spare room to set up a small shop for anything that could be needed by the guests. She gave it all free to the women who visited. With four massage therapy specialists, two skin specialists, and a bunch of nail, makeup, and waxing experts, the wives had themselves a perfect spa day.

They left the children in the care of skilled sailors with expert swimming abilities to look after them. Everything turned out brilliantly, even better than I had anticipated, and the men were admiring Belle. She was a beautiful ship, perfectly maintained and presented. When the food finally arrived, it was some of the best they had ever tasted. The children went wild for ice cream and pizzas while the wives savoured the cakes and asked for recipes. Meanwhile, the men indulged in stuffed halal pentade with honey-roasted vegetables, tomato soup, and fine nonalcoholic wine. They even squeezed fresh, natural grape juice before it had a chance to ferment.

One by one, they came up to thank me for the invitation, making me promise to visit their homes. They all complimented me on creating this party for them and paying so much attention to detail as to address the cultural aspect. All my staff were modestly dressed in abayas and acted respectfully as if they were meeting a prince. By treating them as friends, I made friends with my guests. They made Dubai feel like home.

When we arrived in Manama, we were expected. The women disembarked, and some men boarded. The waitresses served a nice spread of snacks, drinks, and sandwiches. Everyone received their own tour of the ship and expressed their amazement. It dawned on me that those two countries share deep cultural connections and similarities, just as one would expect from next-door neighbours.

Everyone had a great time talking and drinking tea and coffee, and everyone loved the ice cream so much that I had to promise to open a shop in Bahrain. As soon as I did, two other guys insisted it wouldn’t be fair unless I opened one in Qatar and another in Kuwait. They were lovely people with clear eyes and friendly smiles, so I shook their hands and made commitments.

“If you find me a good location, I promise to open a shop there.” This sealed the deal, and I believed them. All of them insisted that I come to visit them. It was true what I heard about Arabs; they are wonderful people with open hearts and welcoming smiles, diametrically opposite from how they are portrayed by the lying fake news companies in the West. This only confirmed what I had assumed, and I was committed to banning all Western media companies throughout my enterprises. I was done with them.

As the evening rolled in, the girls served a magnificent dinner. We put all the kids to sleep, then ate and made speeches till late. It was an incredible evening, and I made so many friends. I was lucky to remember everyone’s face and name well.

In the end, we said our goodbyes and the ship made its way back after everyone was counted. It was a lovely night, full of stars, and we sat in a circle, drinking tea, and chatted. It was a special bonding moment between men, discussing seemingly mundane events and sharing love and friendship. To me, it looked like getting on the ship was a great excuse to organise a gathering of people who were too busy to meet otherwise, and they made me their friend.

“So, what do you think?” I said to Amir, sipping a drink and looking at the waves. I met him one day inside my gym, and we talked about this and that as we slowly moved towards business. I invited him to this trip as a guest so he could have a look and better understand what I proposed.

“It would work, but I think it’s too much.” I shrugged, measuring the Egyptian man up and down. The word on the street was he was a good trader, always looking out for himself.

“Perhaps I should be talking to someone else.” I turned back and started walking away.

“Wait, wait!” I said to Amir and smiled. He knew I got him and laughed, then he shook my hand, and we were in business. Things were coming out nicely, just the way I planned. The men joining my gym all paid massive amounts to have a first-class experience with what I felt was the best gym out there. I didn’t even bother checking the competition. It wouldn’t change my mind; it was irrelevant.

There were three reasons why they chose to join me. The first and most important one was the experience. It was a great place with incredible service provided by the best professionals money could buy. The second reason, at least for the guys, was all the pretty girls there. Even if the men didn’t want anything from them, looking at pretty ladies exercise, breathing their pheromones, buying them a drink and enjoying their company a little was nice.

The third reason, just as valid as the previous two, was that this guys’ club cost ten thousand dollars a month to join. I even gave everyone different-coloured bands with a chip inside to provide access to digital lockers. The grey bands meant you were a monthly member, and the gold ones meant you paid for a year. This instantly segregated the cautious guys from the big spenders.

Men could make friends at the gym and socialise, buy a few drinks for lovely ladies, and later, whatever happens, happens. As long as everyone plays by the rules, I wouldn’t ask what they did in their private lives, and it worked. The membership surged first when pretty girls joined, and several gold members joined later. The gym gave members a way to meet each other, network, and do some business if they wanted. It was similar to The Society, except we had a permanent location to come and exercise and enjoy a massage.

The idea I had was built on top of that. I would organise exclusive gatherings on the ship once a month and fill it with the fifty most gorgeous women seeking a rich husband. I would sell fifty exclusive tickets to an invitation-only group of people for one hundred thousand dollars apiece to spend the whole day on the vessel.

We would sail out at dawn and return at sunset, with the ticket including all food and entertainment. The men could meet, get to know each other, and talk business; meet the ladies and get to know them. However, sex was strictly forbidden on the ship.

They could swim in the nude and sunbathe naked. They could kiss, hold hands, but nothing more than that, and any inappropriate contact with staff would result in a lifetime ban. If you managed to meet some important people and arrange some business with them, it could all be worth it. That’s how I met Count Conti and he introduced me to others. If you have bad luck, come back another time.

If you’re lucky enough to find a good wife or girlfriend there, congratulations! You’ve won the lottery. But if you don’t, there’s always another chance. The key to this system is that I sold tickets through an auction. There were only fifty tickets available each month. Amir would sell them one by one at any price, starting at a hundred grand and ending wherever. Amir could keep all the profits, but he had to buy all the tickets, so I would receive five million for each trip. How much Amir made was his own business.

Amir attempted to negotiate a better deal by making me view him as the indispensable gatekeeper. That’s why I invited him on this trip so he could see my new friends and comprehend that I could make my own contacts without his services. It worked, and we made a deal.

If I ran this, the ship would make me sixty million dollars a year, which means it would pay itself off in six years on this kind of meeting alone, but I was sure we could increase the frequency as the word spread. For someone like Count Conti, one hundred grand would be loose change, and he wouldn’t want to meet with anyone who paid less. The money, in this case, served as a filter for undesirables. The more it costs to join the club, the better the members’ profile. I understood that well.

We docked in Dubai at the same spot we left. My new friends thanked me for a lovely evening, and I thanked them. It was a pleasure meeting the locals and offering them hospitality. My women thanked their children and promised them they could get ice cream in any of our shops for free whenever their parents allowed it.

It was a good day, and we disembarked. My hummer and Iqbal, with a people carrier, waited to take us home. I helped Shay walk. She was tired and heavy carrying twins. I couldn’t wait to meet my two new daughters and welcome them to this beautiful life I created for them. It was the start of new beginnings; we all felt that.

Chapter 52 - Happy endings

I was planning a trip, but Neneh, Rylee, and Callie went into labour within three weeks, giving me one more son and three daughters—Logan, August, Hayden, and Zoe. It felt incredible to be the father of all those children. I loved all of them more than I thought possible. Sometimes, I’d sneak into the baby room and lay on the floor, just listening to them coo. Zoe was born right on my birthday, and we celebrated it a week later on the ship, just me and all my employees.

I invested some of my money into a diversified portfolio of companies. One of them was the highest-rated cosmetic surgery hospital in Bangkok. It was a growth industry, and Thailand was one of the top locations for health tourism with a high-quality expert staff and top-of-the-range hospitals. I offered all the women in my employment free cosmetic surgery of any kind, valid for the next thirty days, as a gift for my forty-third birthday. Most of the girls accepted. Some wanted to do their noses, others their lips or something else.

“Can I get bigger breasts?” One of the sailors asked, and I laughed. Everyone knew my preference for large mammaries.

“As big as you want.” It was an expensive surgery that would typically cost at least five thousand dollars, even ten with all the trimmings. The plane had to make two trips to Bangkok to get everyone there. The hospital I bought had plenty of beds, but it would take them a week for the surgery and recovery, so the girls grouped together and left.

I busied myself with the final part of my project, exercising and spending a lot of time in the office, locked in my room, making phone calls, and sending emails everywhere. My girls were packing their suitcases and doing some shopping at home. I asked them to prepare for a long trip.

A couple of weeks after my birthday, all the girls returned from Thailand. Some went just to fix their noses or get their pubic hair permanently removed. When they saw the girls who wanted bigger breasts, they asked if they could have them done as well. Peer pressure, I guessed. In the end, almost all the girls who left returned with double dees standing perky and proud before them. The doctor recommended the transaxillary incision method, which left no scars on their chests but under the armpit instead. He was such an expert that even this was barely noticeable. All the girls were ecstatic with their new bodies.

Some girls had their teeth capped, and some got braces. All of them got their vaginal hair almost completely removed, leaving just the upper part in the shape of a landing strip. Never again would they have to worry about getting nicked. All of them had their armpit hair removed, as well as any unwanted hair anywhere. It amazed me how much could be done in a week with the right experts doing their best. Some girls even got their pussies rejuvenated and their assholes bleached, whatever was feasible in a short time.

It took a month for me to finish my plans and for the girls to fully heal from their treatments. In the meantime, Dixie and Paige gave birth to Willow and Winter, my two youngest daughters. I became a father again, which confirmed what I already knew—I loved being surrounded by my kids, and my plan had worked. I had assumed that everything would be fine with multiple women taking care of many children, and I was right. It didn’t matter to the girls who gave birth to whom, as they saw all their kids as their own. It wasn’t about biology; it was about love.

The day had finally arrived, and we had to put the Hummer into the garage. Iqbal and his sons assisted us in moving numerous suitcases onto the ship while the girls spread out across the decks, squealing with pure joy. The captain played the horn as the ship detached from the dock, and we gradually made our way out of the shipyard, picking up speed as we entered the gulf. We were now on our way.

As soon as the girls managed to settle, they came downstairs wearing the skimpiest and most obscene bikinis ever made, and I should know. I browsed the internet for the kind of swimwear and lingerie I liked, then found out who made them. The trail invariably led me to India or China. So, I hired an experienced textile engineer and bought a factory on the verge of bankruptcy for one dollar in Sri Lanka under the condition of paying its debts and keeping some employees. I fired half and gave them a good severance. Those were the ballast people in middle management who got their jobs through briberies and nepotism. I only kept the ones with valuable textile experience.

I bought one of each garment that I liked and sent it to the factory. The textile engineer opened them all up and, within a month, produced better-quality copies. It cost anywhere between one and three dollars to make the original bikini, and I paid twenty for the one we made using the best technology and materials available.

It cost me a bomb to bring advanced digital textile printers from China. I had to buy a small factory there, as they wouldn’t sell me the technology otherwise. It surprised me that the Western world had no technological capabilities to manufacture complex garments. The Chinese invested a lot of research and money into advanced textile technologies. They kept them and the entire supply chain China-centric.

Often, western politicians boast about bringing manufacturing back to the West despite a lack of understanding of the problem. The West lacks the technology and supply chain to support certain types of manufacturing. These politicians speak grandly about creating jobs and demonising China while we waste resources on wars and destruction. Other countries invest in themselves, watching as we slide back into the stone age.

This all came into play when I wanted to set up my garments factory in Sri Lanka. The textile technologist almost laughed at me when I told him we could get all we needed from the US or Europe. It turns out the only thing we could get from there is why I shouldn’t be doing it in the first place.

In the end, we got it going and produced better copies of the same garments under a different brand, with sufficient changes made to avoid getting sued. Meanwhile, our recruiters found several talented designers, and we signed part-time cooperation agreements with them. I provided them with pictures of the garments that I liked. If they came up with something unique, the textile technologist would assess whether it was feasible to produce it and provide a cost estimate. If it was financially viable, I would purchase the design, and we would move on to the production stage.

All of it was generating losses, but I intended to come up with a range of sexy clothes, market them at a high price based on the quality of material and manufacture, and build the brand on that. I could rent several stores in the Emirates, stock up the shop in the gym, and see if I could break even. On the plus side, I got the best-looking clothes made with the best materials and the best manufacturing processes at factory prices. The more my girls bought, the more profit they sent to the factory. Of course, it was all my money, but how you did the accounting mattered.

Our first stop was in Sri Lanka. I wanted to visit my factory in person, and we planned to stay a few days. While girls explored the place, doing the tourist things and taking thousands of pictures, I went inland with a driver to visit the factory I purchased. It was a relatively small and dirty place in desperate need of repair. I sat down with the manager and fired him on the spot, then called for everyone to stop and listen.

“I want to know what we need to turn this place into something we could be proud of, and I want all of you to tell me what is missing, what we could do better, and what needs to be fixed.” Everyone was silent, looking at me scared, so I smiled at them and called what looked like the oldest woman there to come up.

“How many years have you worked here?” She had been a seamstress for twenty years. I doubled her salary to stop what she was doing, train, teach and advise younger women, and report up the chain on what she needed. I made the technologist the interim manager until we could make a plan to renovate the place, create the proper structure, and turn it into a clean factory instead of a sweatshop it was, improve quality control, and stop theft.

All of this was part of a plan to give my girls something to do when they were ready to take on a different challenge. Some people are happy to be just parents, while others require the mental stimulation of a challenge to pit themselves against something difficult and win against the odds. This is why we climb mountains or compete in certain sports. Many of us need the fulfilment of achieving our own self-actualisation and greatness, and I wanted to establish a structure that supported that.

The Sri Lanka factory was an absolute disaster and a headache that would take at least a year to correct. Tara has been slipping into a bit of a depression for months because she couldn’t get pregnant, and I thought this would be the right time to try again and focus her mind on something different. I was sure Amy would want to help, and so would other girls, just like they did with the gym.

At first, the gym was my brainchild, and I kept running it, but as soon as the girls figured out it was fun, they volunteered to do this or that, and before you knew it, the gym was off my hands, and the girls ran it with great pleasure. They would come home and tell me stories about what they did and how they managed to solve complex problems. I could see the spark in their eyes. They were so excited and felt validated, so I kept throwing them little breadcrumbs, and they kept following the path.

My women ran the ice cream shops. The date shop expanded and turned into a little chain, and my girls ran it. I would start something and present them with a harder challenge, and the girls would take it up and have fun doing it. This was the secret to successful, cohesive relationships. Everyone felt valued and that they were contributing, adding to the family something more than their love and good genetics.

My girls were smart, and they knew why I did all that, and they loved me even more for it. Sometimes, showing that you’re paying attention can be as simple as buying a flower or doing something nice. However, this is not scalable, and such gestures become meaningless after they have been repeated numerous times. What I did had greater potential, and the girls were fully invested in it with passion.

We explored Sri Lanka for another day and had fun, eating local fruits and trying local cocktails before boarding the ship and continuing on our way. It was the long-deserved vacation I had planned for months to celebrate the success of my plan and the birth of my children. My entire family, all of my women, were there, sunbathing nude, joined by the off-duty sailor girls with massive fake tits, glistening in the sun, slick with lotion, looking incredible with their bronzed skin.

The captain took his time, and the ocean was warm and quiet. It was a great moment to let go and enjoy myself. I was forty-three, and if some are to be believed, I was halfway there. I wanted to live the rest of my life with my girls and children and teach them about love, honesty, and respect. I wanted to give them everything they deserved, a good start in life and, most importantly, a big family to love and support them in whatever they decided to do with their lives.

“Land ho!” Tara shouted, pointing with her finger. Far in the distance, she saw the Maldives. The captain stopped the ship at a safe distance, and the locals sent boats to greet us and take us to the hotel. It wasn’t so far, and I felt that any good swimmer could easily make the distance. I booked at one of those famous places with bungalows on stilts inside the ocean. The azure sea was calm and beautiful, with white coral sands.

I have always wanted to visit the Maldives, an archipelago of small islands with some of the world’s most beautiful beaches. The place was too small to do anything with it in terms of living or starting a business, but as a tourist destination, it was incredible. Indigo bought a range of snorkelling equipment, expecting it would be needed sooner or later, so I took one with me and swam around the island, looking at the fish and enjoying myself.

There was little to do in the Maldives other than eat, swim, enjoy the sunshine, and take long walks on the beach at sunset, but it was a beautiful and romantic place. The girls loved it and kissed me after the hotel staff served us dinner. I had to admit to myself that I preferred the ship, but it was a unique experience and a fulfilment of an old dream.

The following morning, after breakfast, I thanked our hosts, and we were back on our way. The captain helped me plot a fun route that would take longer than a straight line, but it would be enjoyable. Since we were so close, I thought why not visit all those places I had imagined all my life? After all, this was a well-deserved holiday.

We took it slow, in no hurry to get anywhere, well within the reach of our helicopter in case something happened. We had the first aiders on board and nurses trained as midwives, so I was confident that we had most angles covered. I spent the day mostly sunbathing and enjoying the hot spa, drinking cocktails and eating the best food prepared by my chefs. It made me happy that the gym they installed had the same core features as the mine in Dubai, and I made sure to use it for two hours each day upon waking.

I had a stringent exercise regime that helped me keep fit and flexible while reducing stress. Although it was sometimes difficult to sleep due to the remaining stress from the intense pressure of taking the New York company public, the memories of it slowly faded away. Spending time with my children and watching them grow and coo brought me joy and reminded me of the life I created.

Right after lunch, I was enjoying my hot spa and the sunshine with a nice glass of a refreshing coconut cocktail, another one of Gaspard’s inventions. I swore he could have made millions just by inventing drinks and licensing them to bars. I was lucky to have found the man.

Over time, I got to know everyone on the ship and liked my choices. The girls looked gorgeous after upgrades and weren’t shying away from showing it. The front deck pretty much turned into a nudist beach. All the bikinis the girls bought served little practical purpose, especially in the hot tub or on the sun beds. Who wanted tan lines anyway.

The girls joined my bubble bath, carrying their drinks and chatting with each other. I was surrounded by gorgeous naked flesh of babes so hot that my cock would explode if it wasn’t for all the sex. The good thing about being on the ship with a bunch of horny mothers was that no matter how often we had sex during pregnancy, they were cock starved, so I ended up fucking them at least six times a day, especially with Tara, who was desperate to get pregnant.

I heard the giggles and saw Tess on the other side of the hot spa conspiring something with a small group of off-duty sailor girls. Tess was a character who loved rough and nasty sex. She would grab me at every moment she could and make me fuck her in the most degrading and humiliating way, and she would spit profanities. Something was missing in Tess’s head, but it amused me. She was a great stewardess and a trustworthy employee, a great lay and someone I could count on, but she was weird. She made me laugh, and I enjoyed that.

One of the sailor girls detached herself from the group and slowly swam over to me, whispering into my ear.

“I am so horny. Would you please fuck me, Jim?” Now, who could refuse such a polite request? I looked at Tess on the other side and the grin on her face. The girls were snickering, sending Loraine over on a dare.

“Come on, let’s go,” I said, pulling her hand out of the hot tub. Lori looked back at her friends, and they shrugged. I could play those games as well.

I showered and put on a fresh change of clothes just moments before we arrived in Seychelles. I had arranged an incredible rate with a hotel to get all my staff in for a three-day shore leave. Seychelles was the most fantastic place, full of islands and corals and rich in old culture. It was a dream come true for me to explore it and see giant turtles in their natural habitat. It would be an excellent educational opportunity for everyone to marvel at something uniquely beautiful. It was our natural inheritance, and all humans should come and understand what we are fighting for and trying to preserve.

We moored the ship against a dock and started to come out. No inspection was necessary as the documents we sent in advance were sufficient. Nobody wanted to run away from their country and migrate to Seychelles forever, as the place was too small unless you wanted to play Robinson Crusoe.

The girls spread out, enjoying the local sights and snacks, slowly gravitating towards the beach. I hired a guide to take us to see the turtles, and we went on a small boat island hopping and met the ancestors of the great old land tortoises. They looked incredible. I was instantly in love with them—such incredible creatures—and the guides promised to take us snorkelling the next day.

Life is what you make of it, and I turned mine into enjoyment. Everything in my new life was custom-engineered to bring me joy and happiness. I never wanted any of this, just to live a normal, boring, average life, but all of it changed when I was betrayed and forced to start thinking for myself instead of letting others do all the thinking for me and tell me who I was and what to do with my life.

Of course, this was a much greater responsibility, but I took control of everything and planned, ending up with the life I created. In the evening, Gaspard and the chefs joined us for dinner. The guide took us to the best restaurant. I looked at the menu and said, “Yes,” ordering everything they had. We would never waste food. There were just too many of us for that, but I wanted to taste everything on offer.

The food was excellent, and I ended up arranging for Gaspard to spend the next day assisting the main chef, learning the best recipes and sourcing the right ingredients. I never knew there was a difference between Indian curries. It turns out I was wrong. Different areas used different ingredients. The chef even gave me two powders to try. One was Telugu, the other was Madras. The curries bore a strong resemblance in taste, but the difference was instantly evident, and Gaspard was fascinated.

By the time we bid farewell to the Seychelles, everyone on board, including the crew, felt rejuvenated. We all had such a fantastic time taking over a large hotel, swimming, snorkelling, sightseeing, and taking pictures. Little did I know that the girls had set up an Instagram account for the ship, where they posted the best photos of the gorgeous sailors posing in various locations we visited.

Belle attracted fans from all over the world. She was one of the most luxurious vessels out there, certainly staffed by the sexiest sailors in the history of sea travel. Since the account started, over a million people followed, helped by the shoutouts from all the Instagram princesses we had there.

The girls were raking in cash from product placements. Some months ago, I suggested to the Florida girls that they try their hands at marketing. I bought a small marketing firm in New York and another one in London, merged them into one, hired, fired, and reshuffled people, then set Rylee and Callie as the directors, and they convinced Morgan and Paige to join them.

The Dubai team revamped their website and created a new corporate identity. The girls partnered with companies to showcase their products on Instagram and TikTok. With a combined following of ten million, they successfully marketed Sri Lankan garments, mainly swimwear and lingerie, at a significant markup. They emphasised quality by sending garments to YouTubers who tested them and gave them a perfect score of ten out of ten.

We took a slow, steady course until reaching the coast of Madagascar. The sailor girls went nuts, held hands, and sang the song from the Cartoon. Watching that was equally funny, endearing, and freaky, making us look like some weird cult. I couldn’t help but laugh when my girls joined them.

“When in Rome,” I mumbled and held someone’s hand. Life was beautiful, and people on shore waved back to us when the ship docked. Since childhood, I had always wanted to see a baobab tree in real life. It looked so strange and unique that it sparked all sorts of fantasies.

The hotel staff greeted us with open arms and escorted us to our rooms to unpack. After changing our clothes, our tourist guides drove us to their jeeps and immediately ventured into the wilderness.

There it was, like an alley of trees, right by the road. The cars stopped, and I got out and hugged one of them. The girls laughed. It was one of my early childhood fantasies that I finally made happen. The older I got, the more I craved all the simple things I dreamed of as a kid. This would look silly to casual onlookers, but to me, it was the fulfilment of a lifelong dream.

Nobody dreams of being wealthy like Scrooge McDuck, jumping into a pile of gold coins, or worshipping a golden ring like Gollum. We dream of simple things as children, such as having loving parents, feeling warmth, and eating ice cream. We dream of playing with our father and skipping stones on a lake or just hearing our parents tell us that they are proud of us and love us.

Dreams often become complicated with endless disappointment, and we are given the “correct” dreams to have as grown adults. Good grades, a good salary, a good house, a good wife, good children, a good retirement, and a good death—these are the dreams we are told to have, but never to strive for greatness or excellence. These dreams are deemed unattainable, and any attempt to reach them is met with disapproval. This is how we are programmed and controlled by the constant fear and threats that surround us. “Cross the road on red, and we’ll spank you,” they say.

I intended to teach my kids something different: never settle for good enough and always shoot for great and excellent. I wanted my kids to be satisfied with small things like hugging the baobab tree but always shoot for the stars and give due respect and love to others. I wanted my children to use their own brains and think before doing anything people tell them, to intelligently evaluate all their choices, always win for themselves, and then share the winnings with those they love.

The girls enjoyed exploring the town, window shopping, and strolling through the market. Madagascar was such a beautiful place. It would have been easy to settle there, build a lovely home, and relish in the scenery and the beaches, but I had other plans. After a delightful dinner and spending the night on the ship, we sailed to Reunion Island, which was part of France.

We docked, and the girls spread out everywhere. Being in a small tropical place yet technically in the European Union felt so strange. It was a critical point as I could get all the legal protection here, all the EU rights and all the medical help if needed. The mothers could give birth to their children in France. It was a very subtle but important point.

Gaspard adored the location. It was a part of his country, and we remained on shore while Belle restocked with truckloads of produce. I established an agreement with a shipyard that had a dry dock to maintain my vessel twice annually and supply me with everything I required through a chain of French companies as frequently as necessary. Reunion would become my primary service and supply point for the Indian Ocean.

Everything was done by the end of the day, and we made our way slowly to the neighbouring island. We could have reached it quickly, but the captain ordered the first officer to arrive at dawn. There was no great magic in piloting Belle. It probably had more electronics than the space station. The captain showed me it once. I could press a point on the map, and the ship would sail itself there. It was loaded with technology from sonar to fish finder, satellite internet, and internal WiFi. I even got Starlink installed for high-speed internet when the ship travels in areas with coverage. Reunion was one of them.

***

The sun’s light burst through my window, stirring me awake. Yesterday was a long night spent with Lana and Luna. Since our first sexual encounter, the two had been eager for more. I must admit that I was developing a preference for Croatian women. Their sweet, devout demeanour and eagerness for penance and blessing with my special holy water made everything more thrilling. The girls were becoming like Tess, insatiable. Was this due to the high altitude, which only affected stewardesses? I chuckled, and the two women stirred awake.

“Mmm, what is it?” one of them asked. I long since gave up figuring out who was who. One of the twins had a barely visible mole on her inner thigh. If that was the deciding factor, then god bless them. None of it mattered in the end because those two were inseparable. They did everything together, ate the same food, dressed the same way, and naturally, they fell pregnant together – the very first time we made love. Was it a proverbial hole-in-one, or was it two holes? I found it confusing with the two of them.

Suddenly, the doors burst open, and Tara ran in, squealing like a monster. Lana and Luna screamed in surprise and ran away to hide and take a shower. I had to ask Tara three times to calm down and tell me what happened. She jumped on the bed, squealing and dancing, until I grabbed her foot and pinned her to the mattress.

“I’m pregnant! I’m pregnant!” Tara kept repeating. She pushed the clear blue stick into my hand to let me see while she squealed with excitement, jumping up and down and punching the air with her fists and legs.

“Yes, you are, my darling.” I kissed her, and she hugged me tight like a vice.

“Thank you, oh thank you, Jim, for everything, for saving my life.” Lately, Tara stopped calling me “master.” It kind of got old, and she matured. Tara wanted to be just one of my women, loved and cared for, safe and protected.

She started telling me her story one day, but I stopped her. It was ancient history. I had stopped telling my own story a long time ago. It was irrelevant. What mattered was here and now and what we did with it. We only had one life to live. Sometimes, people can’t move forward because they are stuck in their past. Other times, people keep rushing endlessly into the future, chasing a future that never comes. All of them forget about today. The now is a magical gift from the universe that allows us to enjoy our lives. That’s why it is called the present.

Carpe diem, seize the day, live in the moment—that is the lesson hardest to accept. It comes with detachment, something I learned from my friend Jack. He spoke in riddles, impossible to solve, but once you got there, the riddles made sense. They were designed in such a way as to make you look for the answer and go on the journey of enlightenment.

“You can’t see the valley from the foot of the mountain. Only at the summit is everything clear. This is when you understand that the mountain and the valley are irrelevant. The journey itself holds all the answers.” Jack used to drive me insane with the way he spoke. He learned it from someone, “a man on the beach fishing for a whale made out of wishes.” I couldn’t figure it out; no matter how hard I tried, none of it made sense. The obvious part was easy, but there was something else, and it infuriated me to feel so close yet always too far from the answers.

“Sometimes, Jim, you must stop and wait to reach your destination.” I sucked at metaphysical metaphors. Give me a logical or mathematical problem, and I would figure out how to solve it in time. Still, any form of ambiguity was doing my head in, just like the little happy minx trying to suffocate me.

I love you,“ I said, and Tara kissed me hard. Her tears rolled down her eyes. This was the happiest I had ever seen her. Her biggest dream had come true. She would be a mother and create a new life. This urge is something deep inside all of us, except that men experience it as a sexual drive until the moment they see the smile of their children, and then everything changes in an instant. Being a father is the most intense feeling in a man’s life. All your love, your dreams and your goals funnel into one. A man never knows true love until he becomes a dad.

Loud squeals from the deck prompted us to go to the window and look outside where we were. In front of us was a magnificent island with endless white beaches, palm trees, and vast views of a tropical paradise.

”It is Mauritius!“ Tara shouted in surprise. Belle was anchored just outside Belle Mare, my favourite area. It featured a single five-star luxury hotel at its centre, a three-story main building at the back and two-story ones at the sides, not counting the numerous exclusive bungalows behind them, creating a horseshoe look from the sea. In front of it were several dozen brown wooden sun loungers with dry straw umbrellas creating shade.

This is the place we visited on our last trip. All the girls had incredible memories; half declared they had seen paradise, and now they were ready to die. It was the most beautiful place on the planet. As much as I loved Dubai, Monaco, and even London, where I was born, nothing could come close to Mauritius. We all fell in love with it, the true garden of Eden.

I stood at the back of the ship as the captain dropped the anchor and lowered the side. Inside the ship was a secret compartment containing a small ten-person speedboat and four jet skis, two on each side, secured to the walls. As the water poured in, the automatic ramp lowered the speedboat into the water, and one of the sailor girls sailed it out. I wondered where our safe boats were, and they were all neatly packed inside, automatically inflatable in contact with water, including the packs of modern emergency inflatable jackets with GPS and transmitters. I had paid a top-tier subscription for emergency services in case something happened; I’d have helicopters flying to find us wherever we were.

The boat cautiously manoeuvred around coral reefs, ensuring that it did not harm them. We had a specific agreement with the government outlining where we could anchor the ships to avoid any damage to the reefs, including contact damage, so for a portion of the journey, we had to glide on the water with propellers lifted.

We slowly sailed through the shallows and beached the boat on the white sands. All the immigration processes were satisfied in advance, and the immigration didn’t require an inspection, so we were free to come and go as we pleased.

A team of hotel staff rushed towards us to stabilise the speedboat until we got off and then shoved it into the water to bring in the additional passengers. I granted all the sailors time off, retaining only a rotating crew of five.

”There are no guests,“ Amy noticed, and the girls quickly agreed. The hotel was empty, and we were the only ones there, so the girls looked at me suspiciously as if I had done something without telling them. Luckily, I was quickly rescued from the inquisition that brewed.

Lamin walked across the courtyard and shook my hand in welcome. I looked back to see the girls staring at the man.

”Welcome, boss. I’ve missed everyone.“

”I trust everything is in order,“ he nodded and greeted the girls. They ran up to Lamin and bombarded him with questions. I strategically moved away and jumped into the pool, then floated to the bare in the middle, making cocktails.

I’ll have one virgin Gaspard Fresh,” the bartender smiled and served me one five minutes later. I took a sip and exhaled; it was too early for alcohol, so I settled for a fancy fruit juice until everyone came over and we could have breakfast together.

I watched from a distance as Laming and the girls discussed something intense. Some saw me smiling from the pool and shook fists at me for surprising them this way. I contacted the hotel owners and bought the hotel outright without telling anyone. It cost me a bomb, but now the hotel, and a half mile in each direction, was mine.

That’s why the government didn’t fuss about the ship because I was one of the major investors in tourism, presenting them with a ten-year plan of turning a square mile behind the hotel into a luxury estate villa paradise with prices starting at a million dollars apiece just for an apartment. With that, I would heavily invest in infrastructure, providing all of the essential services, with all the taxes going to the government to finance a range of other much-needed projects.

If one looked far into the distance, they would see construction crews with bulldozers preparing the land to lift ten-foot walls around the estate. I was building an exclusive gated community with the hotel as its centrepiece. It would have its own security and a central recreation building with a helipad on top so that the rich people could fly in and out from their yachts. The entire project would cost billions of dollars, and I hired Lamin as its manager. It took some convincing, but we got there in the end.

I didn’t want to fire anyone from the hotel, but my plan was to slowly move them to work from the central management estate, taking care of villas, apartments, and gardens. The hotel had over two hundred employees. I estimated that I would need to quadruple the headcount to cover the new estate. It was another benefit for the local government. I would become one of the largest employers, creating jobs and lifting people from poverty into modest middle-class living by providing enough financial stability to educate their children.

The hotel staff led the girls to their rooms, and they unpacked, put on their sexy bikinis, and came to the courtyard to get their drinks and join me floating in the water. The concierge then called us for a late breakfast. We took a shower and put on white robes before joining Lamin in wishing us a warm welcome.

Lamin did an amazing job, refurbishing half of the rooms, rolling out a covered parking lot in the back, and resurfacing the main road with brand-new tarmac. Some building crews were still working at the back, placing the bricks to make footpaths on the roadside, cleaning the place, and collecting leaves. The entire front of the hotel was still being repainted before the workers hit a pause and moved to remodel the bungalows.

“The crews will start coming in a month,” Lamin said. We would begin with the central building, approximately a quarter mile away. This is where all the workers would be transferred from the hotel and replaced by the girls we had hired. The process would be similar to what we had done for the ship. I was responsible for closing the hotel to the public and removing all listings from the internet. The only way one could book a stay was if they were invited.

“What’s the point of all this?” Tara asked, probably trying to figure out if I had gone mad, and I laughed.

“Do you know how big a square mile is?” Tara shook her head. “It is two and a half million square meters, almost twenty-eight million square feet.” It took Tara a minute to visualise what I suggested, and then she gasped. I wasn’t just building a gated community but an entire town with exclusive villas and apartments.

There would be a church, a mall, a cinema, a hospital, a school, and even a kindergarten, as well as a learning centre for university-level students. They would all be built on strict principles, without radical nonsense or destructive political agendas. All future owners would have to sign an agreement to this effect, and if they breach it, there would be a legally binding arbitration process to remove the problem makers from the premises, with the cost of buying out their houses at the market value.

Tara sat down, trying to process the immensity of what she had learned, and Lamin took me outside to show me the parking lot, which had ten brand-new electric Hummers happily sitting in their charging bays. Over fifty charging points were in the parking lot, but only some were connected.

“What are we looking at?” I asked. Lamin knew his numbers by heart. Judging from the current estimate for each dollar we put into the development, we would get a thousand dollars back. Rich people were spooked by wars and uncertain times. We already had a few dozen customers ready to put money in and buy off the plan as soon as it got finalised and certified. Some were already speculating that the houses would double in price, and everyone wanted a cut, ready to splash millions.

I slowly spread the word down the grapevine, and all the investors were salivating. Once you make three billion dollars in a day, people start to listen to you and want to invest. Count Conti was one of the first people to reach out, counting he would double his investment in a year. It was a massive undertaking that would need a lot of people, and my girls would be happy to live here in a community they engineered.

When we returned, Gaspard was beside himself, frantically running around the kitchen and barking orders. He was displeased with how things were done, and I couldn’t help but chuckle. I knew there would be trouble when Lamin sent me the pictures.

“Would you mind helping redesign the kitchen to your standards?” Gaspard jumped like a rabbit, breaking out in French. Reunion Island was just a short boat ride away, and he could get whatever he needed in France. He was ecstatic at the opportunity to build his own kitchen and restaurant from scratch with the help of Alma and Petra, the Croatian chefs. The man started hyperventilating. I sent Indigo after him to manage his rants and turn them into something productive. She was losing her mind as well.

Since I was taking the hotel out of the listing, nobody could accuse her of working for the competition, and she poured over everything, inspired by what Lamin wanted to do and eager to help.

That evening, the Mauritian chefs taught Gaspard how they grilled fish and lobsters. I seated almost seventy people at the tables. Then I stood on the podium with a microphone, welcoming everyone and explaining what I had done. I asked everyone if they wanted to participate in something great.

Everyone cheered and lifted their glasses. This meant they all had a home different from where they came from, living within the world they helped build. As a perk of their employment, I promised free apartments to everyone, highlighting that we would need to hire and train at least two hundred more people.

I presented Tara with a challenging task, a model agency I bought in New York and another in Milan. She had oodles of experience, and I asked her to become a manager. She burst into tears and accepted. Finally, I found something she wanted to take on as a job. Then, I turned to Rylee and Callie.

“I have something for you as well,” I said, and presented them with a talent agency and a studio in Los Angeles, which I bought and offered them to manage. I was collapsing all my seemingly random investments like a house of cards into one large enterprise managed by my woman. All the other girls squealed, offering to help.

I had made billions of dollars from that one trade and everyone assumed I was set for life, but I had a plan. With each step, I moved forward, adapting it to fit my final big picture. Most people thought I was done after that and that I would just live happily ever after, spending my gains and living off dividends, but that was never the life I imagined.

Making money was always only half the equation; anyone could tell it should be balanced. “If you’re not moving forward, you’re slipping backwards,” Jack’s words still echoed in my head. Giving up on the world and enjoying life may seem fun for a while, but then problems would come and accumulate. After a decade, a disaster would strike. Someone would get bored or learn to resent me for all those perceived missed opportunities. This way, I made my form of perpetuum mobile, pushing people forward into new challenges, shifting from one side to another, and building the change, chaos and growth into the equation.

I always told everyone I wanted to invest my money into something stable like real estate, so they naturally thought I would buy houses and apartments, then speculate or rent them out as a passive income. Nobody expected me to do something unthinkable like banking on the dreams, fears, and greed of others to build a safe haven inspired by Monaco on the most beautiful tropical island ever, a proverbial stone’s throw away from France.

Lamin was right, although his estimate was overly optimistic. On paper, I could make a thousandfold return on investment. He was wrong by an order of magnitude, and if everything went according to plan, I would get to turn one dollar into a hundred, and I would have many dollars to spend. I had already burned over a billion for the hotel and the square mile of useless land with mud, grass, and bushes. It wasn’t good enough for growing sugar cane, initially zoned as farmland. Nobody wanted it except me. It was an insane plan, the kind I liked.

It was like a video game or a monopoly. I had already made myself rich, and the trick I pulled would change everything by multiplying my wealth and making me fuck you rich. I looked at Liam and Callum, my lovely two sons and laughed. I was going to build an entire world for them.

Chapter 53 - Crocodile tears

Time flies when you’re having fun, and the months pass like a breeze. Anya gave birth, and so did Morgan and Bailey in Clinique Darné, the best hospital on the island until I built mine. I already got the architects making blueprints for a private clinic on the Belle Mare estate and its twin in Reunion, France, connected with the one in Bangkok for staff and the experts. Four months in, the walls were finished, the central administrative building was already completed, the main streets were laid, and the hotel was completely refurbished.

The money was pouring in left, right, and centre from all investors and friends, and the ship started its monthly cruises. We picked up the fifty hottest girls on the planet from talent and model agencies. Then the men came, each forking out a hundred thousand dollars for a ticket. The business model worked.

At the end of the cruise, the girls who didn’t find a partner would be offered a complimentary one-week holiday at the hotel. Some decided to stay and work for any of the dozens of businesses the girls managed. It was a busy time for everyone, and the girls were happier than ever.

Tara was glowing with love for her unborn baby. Amy, Cassie, and Shay were pregnant again. The first thing we did was to completely remodel the gym in the hotel, turning it into a world-class place.

“Please prepare yourself for landing,” the voice said, and two new stewardesses approached me to ensure that I was secured and comfortable. I winked at them, and they giggled. They had just joined my enterprise a month ago and, until now, transported the girls around the globe chasing investors and various businesses. They had been angling to meet me for quite some time. We got to know each other well several times over the eleven-hour flight from Port Louis to London.

No story ends without the final act, and I knew mine was coming in due time. Tina ignored me for over a year, and then one day, out of the blue, she wrote to me, wanting to see her children. I ignored her email, and time passed. With it, she grew even more desperate. She begged and pleaded, telling me how wrong she was and how much she loved our children, crying out crocodile tears. It made me laugh.

Lately, her mood changed again, and she threatened to cause me all sorts of problems. It was time to stop that shit, once and for all, deal with it. Hell hath no fury like a woman scorned, and I didn’t want to test the proverb.

We landed at Heathrow, greeted by the rain. I stood in a fine drizzle for a good five minutes, watching the endless grey cloud of depression covering the skies. It was still morning, but it felt like dusk. A wave of nostalgia washed over me, so I turned back to take the tube. It had been a long time since I travelled underground and saw all those worn-out faces of people wearing drab clothes. Their eyes looked glazed, their posture bent like they carried the weight of the world on their shoulders, going through their lives anaesthetised.

The giant poster on the opposite side advertised cheap hamburgers accompanied by a serving of cancer. Two for one; get fat while you can. It made me wince and feel like vomiting at the same time. Fortunately or unfortunately, the train arrived, and I entered with the throngs of people dragging dead bodies inside my luggage. At least, it seemed that way with the suitcases the size of caskets, and they squeezed together tightly, inhaling each other’s scent.

The odour of unwashed bodies after intercontinental flights in cattle class, chewing salted peanuts permeated the air. Yes, I was in London, the national park, where wildlife is always well-behaved, except for the road men in their puffy black jackets dealing weed and shanking everyone in the heartland of Thailand.

I never saw London this way, a decaying empire hanging on threads. Once this great nation, the beacon of power and culture, turned into a meat grinder where new people immigrated, hoping for the better, while those who had that better escaped.

Deep inside my heart, I missed the British flags. I was raised to love and respect my heritage, but what the egomaniacs in power did with it gave me a gag reflex. It was hard to swallow the bullshit anymore. I always saw myself as a patriot, and I was ready to die for the cause, but not anymore, as nobody could articulate what exactly we stood for and what we created.

All great civilisations, including the Greeks, the Romans, and the Brits, have had their rise and demise. They used to say, “The sun never sets on the British empire.” It was setting now, at least after returning from the world I created for myself. It was all written on the faces of the people on the train, the resignation and ambivalence. Fallen, fallen is Babylon the Great.

Perhaps I was just projecting or attributing blame for the system that failed me and forced me to become someone else. All I wanted was to have a family, love my wife and raise my kids, teach them what I believed in, and then one day retire, perhaps on a small tropical island like Mauritius.

Maybe I was just jaded to be there under the same problematic circumstances, but something deep inside my heart told me this was the last time I visited. It was hard for me to reconcile where I was with how I felt and everything that happened, so perhaps I judged what used to be my home with undeserved harshness. Whatever it was, there was an apparent dissonance between the place and how I felt.

Luckily, the train ride ended, and I walked out to Paddington. Everything changed when I saw Marks & Spencer, and I smiled. My mood improved. This is what it took to turn everything around and fall in love with the country again.

Every place has its own unique quirks, advantages, and disadvantages. I went inside, bought a scotch egg, paid at the counter, and took a bite.

“Mmm,” it was the taste I remembered. That’s what was missing in my life. Scotch eggs and those terrible sausages that make you burp and give you indigestion. They are so awful that you can’t find them anywhere, no matter how much money you’re prepared to pay. I was certain Gaspard would hand in his notice if I asked him to fry them.

I decided not to experiment, so I climbed two flights of stairs, got a takeaway Starbucks in the passage, and I was inside the Hilton hotel. It felt weird to be there when I still paid the rent for my apartment. I just didn’t want to go back there. Too many memories, both good and bad.

Hot showers always make everything feel better. I booked myself into the best room they had available. It was nothing special and a far cry from what I had built in Belle Mare, even before the renovation.

Sitting on the bed in my bathrobe, I wondered, “What do I do now?” Half a day had passed, but I didn’t feel like walking outside in the rain. It was cold, filthy, and depressing. Then, a thought popped into my head, and I almost giggled like a teenager.

“Hey babe, it’s me. I am in town. Wanna fuck?” I called a friend I hadn’t seen for a long time. “Yes, Hilton, Paddington. Indeed. One more thing; dress like a slut.” Emma hung up, and I took off my clothes and lay naked on the bed, instructing the receptionist to give her a spare key.

Some forty minutes later, Emma came inside after tapping on a door a few times. She saw me naked and spread-eagled on the bed, playing with my erect cock. She smiled.

“You are bad,” she said. I reached into my wallet, pulled out a twenty-pound note, placed it on the pillow, and winked.

“I want to fuck you like a cheap whore.” Emma’s face turned almost purple, staring at me, shaking her head. “Undress slowly, give me a dance, then crawl over and eat my asshole.”

Emma’s hands trembled, and she bit her lip. We often played it this way, exchanging filthy texts and video files. After the first time we had sex, she told me her secrets. One of her biggest turn-ons and fantasies was to dress up like a streetwalker and get used by men.

Of course, she would never act on that. Emma was always prim and proper and enunciated her consonants, but I made her feel like a slut. When I made her laugh at that time in the hospital, something broke the fourth wall, and she opened up. We became great friends over time, and I wasn’t going back without making her an offer. Emma was too nice of a person to relegate to memory. I was sure there was a place for her in the world I created.

Emma undressed slowly, dropping clothing items to the floor piece by piece. I almost gasped, feeling my cock twitch, seeing her two generous mammaries again. Like the marathon runners, Emma was built to go the distance. She knelt on the floor and crawled over, licking her lips with a catlike smile, a predator sneaking up on its dangling prey.

Emma licked my foot and bit my calf, growling and purring, using her nails, edging so slowly towards my cock and balls. It was excruciating, tantalising, deliciously decadent. She gave my cockhead a gentle kiss before massaging my balls with her tongue.

“That’s it, slut. Take it in deeper; swallow it whole. Yes, good girl. Who’s daddy’s little whore?” Emma’s face turned almost purple, and her tits broke out in goosebumps while her nipples stood upright like two soldiers saluting the fags. They waved in sync as she gulped down my cock, making her massive tits look like udders waiting to be milked.

“Say, moo,” I said, and her face turned a shade darker.

“Mmmm,” Emma moaned, trying to swallow my rigid member. I could feel her throat muscles close around it, adding to the sensation.

“Stop. Come here,” I pulled her upwards. Emma was doing such a good job, but I had other plans. I turned her sideways, lying with her chest across my knees, then massaged her firm bubble butt with my hands, watching with admiration as her soaking-wet pink pussy lips parted and closed like a fish trying to breathe outside water.

“Mmm, no. Please, Jim, not this,” she moaned. I could feel her leg muscles trying to close.

“Stop this, slut,” I slapped her ass so hard it instantly turned red, and she yelped. “Open wide. Don’t you dare close your legs again?” Emma squealed into the pillow but let me proceed unabated, rubbing my index finger against her puckered asshole.

I reached into the nightstand drawer to pull out a plastic bag I bought at Ann Summers shop. Emma yelped again. Her butt and legs broke out in goosebumps when she felt cold gel applied to her anus.

“Please, Jim,” she pleaded, not daring to close her legs. Emma’s face was burning in humiliation while her pussy was drooling from excitement.

“Oooh, no, please, it’s too big. Please, Jim, I’ll do anything, just not this.” I ignored Emma’s distress, pushing a little harder on the other end, rolling my hand in circles, watching her sphincter stretch until it looked perfectly round, like outstretched lips biting an apple. She screamed, and her pussy started to pump as soon as her asshole closed around a brand-new butt plug. It was the biggest one I could find, about the same circumference as a can of Coke.

“Take it out! Take it out, please,” Emma begged, pulling on the bedsheets with her clutching hands.

“Shut up and take it, whore,” I said, rolling her on her back and climbing on top of her. Emma was impossibly tight. I struggled to push my cock into her sopping insides. The butt plug took up almost all the space.

“Aaah,” Emma screamed in orgasm as soon as she felt my cock plunge all the way. I waited a minute, letting her ride the feeling before I started to pump. It was hard. I could feel the butt plug pressing on my cock, a tight fit, adding to the experience.

Emma only got louder, cumming over and over about every minute, feeling used and violated as I mercilessly jackhammered into her, uninterested in her pleasure, slapping her massive tits and pulling on her nipples. I was enacting a play she shared with me once. Emma only believed it would ever happen in real life. I was determined to give it my best.

“Aaargh,” I screamed, blasting my cum deep into her orifice, filling her womb, and hosing down her ovaries. “Take it, you slut. I hope you get pregnant from that.” Emma only gurgled and panted, too far gone in her own pleasure. She bit her lip, and her pupils dilated. Her body bounced while her hips gyrated. It was a big one, and I smiled.

It took us twenty minutes of cuddling embraced before our breathing slowed down, and Emma cooed into my ear, telling me how much she missed me. We lay like that for some time, whispering sweet nothings to each other.

“Get dressed,” I ordered, handing over her dress. I took her intricate lace panties and put them into my pocket. Emma’s eyes spoke volumes, the words her lips kept hidden. She gave me her hand, and I pulled her downstairs, nodding to the doorman who waved a black cab.

We could have walked it, but who has the time, down to the Marble Arch, then to Oxford Street, all the way to Shaftesbury Avenue, and through a park to a place I knew from some other life.

It was still there, at the edges of SOHO. Emma looked at me like a lost soul. Her palms were wet, and her chin trembled. I snorted like a Cambridge-educated twat, and rolled my eyes like a millennial teenager. Emma didn’t dare ask any questions. All of it was self-explanatory in the end.

“I’ll take these,” I said to the shopkeeper, pointing at a pair of silver studs.

“Please, sit here, miss,” he said, pointing at the private cabinet at the back. Emma’s eyes watered, but she managed to keep her tears in check while I rolled down her dress, releasing her magnificent breasts to the view of a stranger.

Like in a haze, Emma watched the man rub her nipple erect with the alcohol. He took a small tool with a practised hand and pushed a needle inside. Emma screamed, squeezing my hand with all her might, then again when the man pierced her other nipple. The entire process took about twenty minutes. We were in and out. I paid, and we were gone.

“Why are you looking at me this way,” Emma asked, and I just smiled, enjoying the impression her two pierced nipples left on the dress. Anyone who had a look at her from up close could tell Emma’s nipples were pierced.

She was in shock, enough for the taxi ride to seem like mere minutes. We were expected, and the usher of a posh restaurant welcomed us in and showed us the table. It was a nice, cosy place for affluent clientele to enjoy the best fine dining London had to offer. Cassie and Shay found the place. It belonged to another Chamber member. I moved in different circles now. The world looked different when my metamorphosis was complete.

“Why this? What does this mean?” Emma asked, discretely pointing at her erect nipples. In the privacy of our booth and cosy atmosphere, her dress seemed to come alive, following the sinew of her curves.

“It means that you belong to me now. You are my property.” I chuckled, noticing something akin to panic rising on her face. Emma and I have been talking for a long time, and she told me all her fantasies. The biggest one was of her being a prostitute, but as time went on, she told me the rest. Emma had plenty of time to expand on the initial statement, adding taste and colour only imagination can paint about belonging to a pimp, having no free will, being whored out, and used for sex.

Who am I to judge other people’s fantasies? Who could say what is good or bad, right or wrong in this age? We live at a precipice, the end of Western civilisation, where up is down and being a whore is celebrated online while chastity is a mental illness. In words eternalised by the cinema, “life is like a box of chocolate,” until you put it in your mouth and realise it’s just brown. I used to identify with Forrest Gump at times until I realised it wasn’t me but everyone else who’s retarded.

It was getting dark. The sun was setting on Britain. It used to be great once, but the war criminals and pig fuckers have made it less. The time was nigh to cash all the chips and call it a day. It was the curtain call for the West.

The food was excellent, and so was the wine. I dropped twenty grand on a bottle. It was my way of saying farewell to the land I once loved. This was the hardest part of all. I have lived, loved, and I had lost. The time has come for some other people, some other faiths, to test their fate. This country of mine used to be home, but my story was ending. It was time to turn another page and embrace a different destiny. A man is what he believes. At least, Fyodor Dostoyevsky seemed to think that.

Emma held onto my arm like a limpet, clicking her heels like Dorothy, looking into my eyes like someone in love with great expectations and great hopes. It was a mild evening, and people buzzed, going about their lives like busy bees, oblivious to my internal turmoil. It hurt to breathe. Until this moment, the finality of what I’ve done hasn’t fully registered. Somewhere at the back of my mind, I always said, “I could come back anytime,” but it was just a coping mechanism. In my heart of hearts, I knew what it was. This was the last time I saw London.

Later that evening, I languished in a warm bathtub, inhaling the fragrant salts as my hands explored Emma’s luxurious curves, poked, prodded, kneaded and rubbed while she moaned. Emma’s eyes were closed, and her eyelids fluttered. My gaze was focused on the mirror on the other side, showing me her perfectly smooth pussy as her hips gyrated, bringing her lower part in and out of foamy water. This was the life.

It was the fitting end for the adventure, years in the making, now at its sunset. Whatever happens now is unpredictable. I was torn between two feelings, one of profound tiredness and another of nervous eagerness, so I lingered. I balanced on the knife’s edge, holding on by the single strands of hair, taunting myself with all that held me back versus the life that unfolded ahead. Nobody can fight time or their destiny; they only linger and look into the abyss.

Emma moaned as I flipped her over so her tits pressed into my chest, and we kissed while I gently pulled and pushed her butt plug out. Her asshole stretched and closed like a pupil of an eye.

“I’m going to fuck that ass of yours tonight and fill it with my cum,” I said, and Emma shuddered.

“Whatever you want,” she said. Life has its little idiosyncrasies. It made me smile. The road behind me all but vanished into the haze of memories, like a bad dream after getting drunk. I was waking up from a headache. There was only one thing left: to make the moment memorable.

I pulled Emma out of the bath and threw her on the bed, spread her legs wide, and dove for her pussy with my tongue, still playing with her butt plug as I went. Perhaps I would make her keep it inside. She loved how it made her feel, especially in public, where I made her sit on it during our posh dinner.

Emma screamed in the first orgasm of the night. It was an overture to the concert, and I smiled. Life made a full circle, and I was where I started; only the world changed, but I remained the same, or perhaps I became who I never knew myself to be. On some more profound level, I must have known it. We all have the potential for good, bad and evil. There is greatness in all of us, but we lack faith. Faith and fate are inexorably connected. Only faith can change our fate, and I was a believer. I let go of the threads that bound me to my past, let myself go and fell with my tongue into Emma’s insides. She screamed again. What is life other than what we make of it? Impressive are horses or elephants which have been well-trained, but more impressive are individuals who have tamed themselves.

***

I was sitting at the head of the desk inside the conference room I rented from the hotel, typing something on my laptop, when a knock on the glass door came. One of the receptionists opened the door, and three men in business suits walked in with Tina behind them. Our eyes met for a second, and hers were full of hate. She scowled at me, and I smiled. Gone were the days when I was scared of witches. Now, the only fairy tales in my life were the ones I read to my children before sleep.

“May we?” one of the men asked, pointing at the chairs on the other side of the desk. I shrugged in response. He sat at the head with his two colleagues to his left and Tina to his right, flashing them a winning smile. One of them slid their business card across to me, and I caught it before tossing it into the garbage. The men looked uncomfortable, scowling in response to my unexpected action. It was amusing to watch their discomfort.

“Why are we here?” I asked, wishing to get it over with as soon as possible. One of the men handed me a yellow manila folder and slid it across the table. It contained a lawsuit for the custody of my children.

“You can’t do that. We had an agreement. I gave your client a million pounds, and she signed away her parental rights.” Tina suppressed her laughter.

“We’ll address the one million pounds later. We contend that Tina signed it under financial duress, which you are solely responsible for by not paying court-ordered alimony.”

“All right, what’s next?” The guy slid another manila folder with another lawsuit alleging that I lied during the divorce proceedings and that I hid a million pounds in marital assets. It was another good one, and I congratulated the lawyers. They did their research.

“This is all conjecture. Where is the evidence?” The lawyers were a bit light on that, but they played a good game, dragging my kids into the process, threatening to submit them to child psychologists, and alleging I was preventing their gender expression. I got bored after some time and started playing Minesweeper on my computer while they went through the litany of all sorts of things they would do to my kids, the mud they would drag them through, and all the emotional damage it would cause.

“Cut the shit. You wasted too much of my time. What is it that you want?”

“Hundred million pounds.” The main guy blurted out. I had to give it to them. They came prepared.

“What makes you think I have such money?” They slid another folder at me with pictures of me on my ship or next to my plane. There were plenty of them with a cutout from several tabloid newspapers wondering who the secretive billionaire going around the world is, paying no taxes. I had to give it to Tina. She did a great job finding the best sleaze ball lawyers, working on commission to rip off the rich men. It was a highway robbery, and the worst part of it was that they had the case, a weak one, but still potentially damaging for my children. It was time to bring this nonsense home.

“This is all wonderful, but if you had done your job properly, you would have discovered none of this is in my name.”

“That’s because you used a complex network of shell corporations and intermediaries. The court will issue subpoenas for these records, and we will discover the truth in due course.”

“This could take years, possibly a decade, and by that time, both boys would be of adult age, so none of this would matter.”

“It could still cause the kids immeasurable harm to be dragged like this from court to court, prodded and examined. You don’t want that.” This is where I laughed.

“Finally, we can agree on something. I absolutely wouldn’t want this, which is why it will never happen.” They looked at me with big eyes as I sat up straight in my chair and looked at them, changing my tone of voice. No more Mr Nice Jim. He was dead, gone, and buried. “Here’s what’s going to happen. You will go to court and try to sue me, then they will throw it out.” They shook their heads, trying to process all that.

“Why would they do that?”

“Simple,” I laughed, remembering the old Count Conti and the favour he did for me and that white envelope he gave me containing the documents. That was the price I paid with my company, not the apartment I got in the deal. “My kids don’t exist in the British legal system. I renounced their British citizenship. And before you start building your house of cards, I also renounced my citizenship. All three of us are citizens of Monaco now, and your client, Tina, is completely irrelevant. Nothing is tying her to my children where we live, and this will never happen because she is not a Monaco citizen. My kids won’t step foot on British soil until they are eighteen. They are beyond your reach.”

The lawyers were stunned, muttering something to each other as Tina tried to interject. They shushed her, and she grew increasingly loud until she lost her composure and screamed at me, hurling a string of insults my way. I could see the ships sinking in her eyes. I knew what I did with Tina wouldn’t hold water for more than a year until she figured out how to screw me over again and suck out whatever she could, so I made my plan.

It is strange how some people are unable to solve complex problems. There are too many variables at the same time to figure out the right approach. All of this was only about my children in the first place. I had a desired outcome in mind and worked backwards to the start. I didn’t start the company to be rich and then figure out what to do with my children. Instead, I figured out how to take my kids away and found someone to help me with that. Count Conti wouldn’t do it for free, so I needed the right leverage. I couldn’t have come to him if I wasn’t a part of The Society, which I wouldn’t get invited to if I wasn’t a member of The Chamber. It is easy to see all the dominos after they fell.

This brought us back to Dan. He was a wildcard, and I used his knowledge of attracting women to seduce everyone and create exactly the life I wanted. My women played a critical role in my plan, not just random bystanders caught in a wake. They were all black and white stones on a “go” board, not pawns but warriors. It reminded me of my favourite Sun Tzu quote from his famous book, The Art of War. “All men can see these tactics whereby I conquer, but what none can see is the strategy out of which victory is evolved.” I played my game one battle at a time until my strategy revealed itself.

“My turn now,” I said, and everyone quieted down as I reached into my bag and pulled out the manilla envelope. It was full of Tina’s text messages, audio and video transcripts, and emails where she threatened to abuse my children to get her revenge. It was recorded and notarised with affidavits from the lawyers who witnessed some of that.

“My lawyer used this to start criminal charges against your client. You are right, I am rich, much richer than you imagine, and there’s one thing you should know about rich people. We have friends in high places. I will take this hundred million you wanted and pay it, not to you but to someone else who will spend every penny to ruin you personally and your business. Your entire family will be under a microscope. Your kids won’t get into universities. You will never get another loan again, nor will your family, neighbours or friends. Anyone whom you’ve ever cared for will have their lives ruined. And if a hundred million is not enough, I will pay a hundred more, and I will never stop. It will never stop, and you can do nothing about it. You have permanently ruined your lives and careers by threatening my children. I will slowly erase your seed into poverty until your entire bloodline disappears from the gene pool. I will erase you from human history.”

Like on cue, my phone bleeped, and I gave them an evil grin. “I expect your phones will ring in a minute,” I said with a sneer. “You have just been fired, and an investigation was launched into legal malpractice.” I switched on the TV behind me, and the lawyers on the other side of the Zoom call gave them evil smiles.

All three of them turned pale in their faces. They were about to stand up when their phones rang, but they were too scared to pick them up, so I grinned and reached into the bag, pulling out a small sack and sliding it to Tina.

“Your client was right. Upon auditing my assets after the divorce settlement, I found this. It was an honest mistake, and I offer my apologies. I correct it now by giving you the entirety of those assets. She looked around and found thirty coins.

”What is that?“ she asked, looking at me with daggers in her eyes.

”Thirty pieces of silver.“ I pointed at the door. ”Now, please leave.“ I could see the lawyers’ hands trembling and their pale foreheads covered with a thin sheen of perspiration as they put their stuff into their suitcases.

”Tina, just a moment,“ I said as Tina was about to follow them out. She looked at me with ultimate hatred.

”What is it?“

”If I hear from you or see you again, I will kill you,“ her eyes got big, and her tears bubbled out. She could see it in every pore, every nuance of my speech, every tone of my voice—I wasn’t bluffing. ”Goodbye, Tina,“ she shuddered, feeling the finality in my voice. There would be no negotiating or discussions anymore. I came to London to say that sentence and go home.

Tina left, and that was the end. They made an empty threat; I made an empty threat. I didn’t want to take her to court for the same reason why I didn’t want to see her in court. It was always for the sake of my boys. We had a good life now, and I was their father. Nobody would ever come in between us, and I would protect them with every breath I had, but it wasn’t just me anymore. All my women saw Liam and Callum as their own, and there would be hell to pay if anyone even looked at them the wrong way. All of my women were fiercely protective of our children.

I walked out of the meeting room long after the lawyers were gone. They would return tonight to their homes just to learn that the bank pulled their mortgages. This wasn’t an act of revenge but a clear message to anyone who might even think of trying again, ”don’t fuck with my children.“

The lawyers knew the game was over the moment I told them that the kids were now Monaco citizens. Everything I did served a purpose, plans within plans, games within games, all deeply calculated. To have a claim, the lawyers would have to bring it under the Monaco jurisdiction, which was probably the most expensive place in the world. Tina would have to finance flights and their stay there, and she wanted the money because she was penniless in the first place. The lawyers knew they couldn’t fund that, especially on a wobbly case that could take years to complete with delays, schedule changes, and a million other ways. The kids were mine to stay, and nobody could change that.

It was still early outside, and I had plenty of errands to run, visit several banks and businesses, close some accounts and open others. With all the money pouring into my Mauritius development, I bought a small private bank in Monaco and created a branch in London. It made it easier for the clients to transfer the cash. I had one more trip to New York to do the same. I felt strangely unburdened after meeting those lawyers, and I expected to never see or hear from Tina again. It was finally done, and she was gone from my life. If she ever resurfaced, I’d pay someone to take care of that. Accidents happen every day.

The evening slowly arrived, although it was hard to tell time by looking at the grey skies above, the source of seasonal affective disorders. I found myself inside a pub where my old colleagues often frequented to join one of them for a pint of Guinness.

”So, how are things back in the office?“ I asked, taking a sip.

”You got out in time,“ Wilfred said. He was a second-generation Nigerian immigrant, a fun guy with a sunny disposition, and a competent engineer from another group with whom my team worked. ”After you left, things started to turn bad. Diarmaid was fired, but the management kept the reason secret. Nobody knows where he is now.“

I did. Diarmaid was dead. He ended up in prison, where he was killed in an altercation with inmates. Diarmaid always had that legendary short fuse. One just had to know how to push his buttons the right way, and it turned out someone figured out how to do it in the prison, and that was the end for Diarmaid.

When I found out, I was curious to know what had happened to his family, and I was surprised to learn that his wife had disappeared. It was like she had dropped off the planet. His daughter passed away in a hospital, and his son was arrested and sentenced to an institution for criminally insane, charged with multiple murders. The entire family disintegrated within a year of Diarmaid going to prison. It got me thinking about what role Lexi played in any of this. Perhaps it was something I would never know, belonging to another tale. My story was ending anyway. A few more days here, and I will be on my plane, going home.

Chapter 54 - Final farewell

It took me a couple of days to sort everything out, dealing with the greatest British invention: red tape. In the end, all was done, and I found myself inside The Chamber in the evening. People I hadn’t seen in a long time came over to shake my hand and congratulate me on becoming a dad again. Several of them were in touch with Cassie, who was helping them purchase a property in Belle Mare.

My new business was a great success. Five members of The Chamber already owned villas there, at least on paper. Teams from a dozen construction companies worked around the clock to build the properties, but the area was so vast that it seemed like it was moving at a snail’s pace. We had our own water reclamation system, straight from the sea, then into a reverse osmosis system, then into the subterranean tanks and pumping stations to provide enough for pools being built.

Each building would have a secondary reverse osmosis system that produced clean drinking water and stored it in tanks. All the roofs would be covered in solar cells that heated up throughout the day. We used clean water to cool the cells or, instead, to heat the water up and push it into an evaporation chamber that collected the condensate and trickled it into a mineral filter before going into tanks. It was a slow but constant process that could produce up to a hundred litres per day of the purest, mineral-enriched distilled drinking water, much more than anyone could spend for drinking or cooking alone.

Everything we built was state-of-the-art. All the buildings had fiberoptic cables to connect to the internet. There were WiFi corners in every nook and cranny, all going through the firewall that my guys in Dubai supported, which would filter out all the shit and nonsense on the internet and present a clean and safe environment for the children. We built our own AI system to access new web pages and read them, understanding what they were about and banning them in almost real-time if they weren’t safe for the children.

This alone was a great selling point for the estate. The villas cost tens of millions to buy but only about a hundred thousand dollars to make and furnish. I bought a massive furniture company in Italy to make the most exclusive designs for the estate, using the finest materials like ostrich leather and such. It cost me peanuts to make, and I sold it at astronomical prices. Nobody even blinked.

Ahmad, from whom I bought the Dubai house, was one of our most valuable clients. He had the foresight to invest in an entire block of apartments off-plan, spending billions of dollars hoping to double his investment by selling them to wealthy Emiratis once construction was complete. It wasn’t just the exclusivity of the development that attracted him, but the security it provided for his children. In this community, parents could allow their kids to play freely without worrying about them being harmed. There were no predators or radical ideologies present to hurt the young residents. It was a safe haven from the political influences of other countries with questionable moral codes. It’s no wonder that those with money were interested in this opportunity.

“The prodigal son returns,” I heard the voice with a strong French accent, turned around, and there he was.

“Pierre, in the flesh!” I embraced the man, remembering the first time we met. Pierre and I became good friends. Of course, he was one of the first to buy a villa in Belle Mare with a special discount. I liked to live next to my friends, and he thanked me with a special discount on his chocolate. Gaspard almost melted from happiness when I gave him a sample and explained the deal I made. It was the best and most expensive chocolate in the world to be served next to our exclusive dates. I even expanded the date business to include dry figs with the same principle. They were selling like hotcakes.

The Frenchman sat beside me and ordered a cocktail, saying, “Thanks for this, Jim. It’s wonderful. I can’t stop drinking it.” We clinked our glasses, enjoying our Gaspard Fresh.

I wanted to propose something, so I started laying out my idea. The hotel was finished and fully staffed. We moved all the local workers to the central building and had them take care of the places being built. Everyone would need their house cleaned, grass cut, pool maintained, or something serviced, and the team would take care of that. Laundry and washing, drying and ironing. In my vision, the estate provided a complete service.

I wanted to extend The Chamber by offering VIP members a meeting place for one million per year. This would operate on the same principles as The Chamber, and they could bring up to two guests and stay up to a week each month. Alternatively, they could pay a hundred grand for a week, bringing up to two guests, but could only stay in the main building, not the bungalows, which were available only to VIP members who paid for a year.

The members could purchase a villa, including a one-year complimentary club membership. This was the same offer I had extended to the Society members, and several dozen had already taken advantage of it. A million-dollar membership was a significant discount on the cost of the house. It would become active once the total amount was cleared. Pierre patted my knee and chuckled. It was an excellent sales pitch, and he had fallen for it the first time around. Now, I was expanding it to a broader audience. Wealthy individuals from New York and London to Saudi Arabia and Qatar bought lavish properties worth hundreds of millions of dollars.

A villa that cost me about a hundred thousand to build would go for ten million off plan, and it was the smallest one we offered before getting into apartments. They were selling out faster than I could market them. Many mid-level multimillionaires looking to become billionaires bought them up, hoping to rub shoulders with the right kind of people at the club and make lasting connections.

I already had over a thousand private accounts in my Monaco private bank with satellite offices in London and soon New York, which I took upon myself to facilitate while the girls opened the offices in Dubai, New Delhi, Moscow, Hong Kong, Singapore, Johannesburg and Tokyo. My plan was almost complete. Only a few small things were left to complete before I went back home and lived happily ever after, taking up my full-time role of a father and handing over the keys to the enterprise to my women and kids when they grew up. The purpose of life is to live it, and I intend to do just that.

Pierre shook my hand, obviously interested. He planned to spend at least half a year in Mauritius after his villa was finished, and he wanted as many of his old friends as possible to join him in the adventure. Duty called. Some new prospects arrived, and Pierre asked to be excused.

I waved to the waiter, who brought me two more cocktails. By the time they arrived, Lexi had sat down on the other side of me. We clinked our glasses together, and she pushed her briefcase over to me. I opened it up, mostly out of nostalgia rather than to check its contents. A million dollars in gold coins was neatly stacked inside acrylic holders. It was the same gold I had given Tina, who then passed it on to her ex-boyfriend.

“It is all there,” Lexi said with a smile, preempting any questions about how it ended up in her hands. I took my phone and tapped on it for a few seconds, and Lexi’s phone bleeped.

“It is all there,” I said, smiling back after transferring fifty thousand in crypto I owed her for the job well done.

“This is a fantastic cocktail,” Lexi said, changing the subject. Our business was over, and we were just friends again.

“Remember that place in Mauritius that you liked? I found the owner, and he will sell it to you for a reasonable amount.” Lexi loved Mauritius and went there for a holiday, falling in love with an old French colonial chateau on the hill. I visited it once, and it looked so serene, a perfect getaway from all the buzz of the world. Lexi had dreamed of owning it for a long time. She recently came into some financial fortune, making all of it possible.

“Thank you,” she said with a smile, checking the info on her phone.

“Just remember, Belle Mare is out of limits for you. I don’t want to ever see you there.” Lexi’s eyes flashed like daggers, and her face instantly changed to a scowl. She knew that I knew what she had done, but I was too rich and powerful to mess with, and I had my women who would pick her apart if anything happened to me or our children.

Lexi nodded, finished her cocktail, fixed her dress, and excused herself. She had other businesses to attend to and other webs to weave. Lexi always made me smile whenever I remembered our first night together. She kept my mind straight, focused, and always supported me for a price.

I lay back on a plush leather sofa, sipping my drink and watching the people talk, drink and laugh. They sometimes reminded me of Mary Howitt’s poem. “Will you walk into my parlour? Said the Spider to the Fly. ’Tis the prettiest little parlour that ever you did spy.” It made me smile. Games within games, like the onion peels. Everyone presented a mask to hide what they wanted no one to see. In the end, life could be like a computer game, cause and effect, and sometimes you must choose the most unintuitive path to throw the opponents of their game. I have been misjudged and misinterpreted all my life, but not anymore. In the moment when all the masks fall, there is no Jim anymore, just me, whoever I wanted to be, raw and unbridled, made of power, and the world was my game to keep me entertained. I have always loved good challenges and problems to be solved.

Perhaps I took it too far and lost myself along the way. Was it a good thing or bad? Only the future will tell. My life might inspire someone one day or serve as a cautionary tale. Nothing is ever the way it appears. We hide behind layers of masks, weaving our webs constantly, presenting a different face to our friends and children. That’s why when we look into a mirror, we can hardly recognise ourselves because all it reflects is what we project, not the truth behind the veils.

I was merely an IT guy who noticed an opportunity to make myself indispensable, so I invested time and effort into a company that profited from it. The concept of supply and demand is straightforward. I did my job and received a salary of a thousand pounds per day after taxes, which was all I required to live a decent life and care for my children. I could have easily led the rest of my life without any of this nonsense happening.

When my wife cheated on me, everything changed, and I was forced to use my brain for something different. It was a challenge, and I was disadvantaged, a shy boy raised by his mother with mild Asperger, a high-functioning one, as they liked to call it. I didn’t get a great deal when socialising with people. That’s why I became introverted after I was bullied in school and focused on books and knowledge, getting good grades and even a scholarship to Cambridge.

I watched big guys, small guys, weak guys, and strong guys interact with women and each other, drawing up commonalities, extracting behavioural patterns, analysing them statistically, and learning from observing. And what did I find out? Nobody is born with social skills. It is something that is learned. I was good at learning, as most intelligent people are, especially the technical ones like myself. We have an analytical mind that can categorise and compartmentalise. Analysts love causalities and sequences that lead to events. The key was adapting my thinking and finding the best teacher. It was Dan.

When I began implementing my plan, it was straightforward—just getting my boys and neutralising my ex-wife. However, as my power grew, so did my appetite. Simply getting the boys was no longer enough for me. I wanted to create a world for them, so I carefully wove my web like a spider, making my play. The key to the game of chances is knowing when to quit and cash out your chips, and I have reached this point. There was nothing more I desired than to raise my children and have more of them. Dan would be astonished if he knew what I did with all his knowledge. I took it to another level and created a monster. Perhaps I was a monster myself.

When I visited Dubai, I often looked at my friends and my IT colleagues working every day, shaking their heads when learning about my life. It wasn’t this hard to succeed, but they lacked faith. They didn’t believe they could do the same thing as me. They rejected the thought that social skills could be learned and that they could make themselves attractive to others. It made me laugh sometimes. They knew how to talk about programming languages, and they learned how to ask for food by talking to their parents.

None of this was inherent; all of it was learned. The endless excuses they used to self-limit and procrastinate only reinforced the belief that they couldn’t do anything about their lives. Like me, at some time, they believed that the cruel destiny dealt them a set of cards, and they couldn’t find their way out of it because of all the fear in their lives. It was the system, the constant programming of schools and media, telling men, “You are nothing. You are toxic. You are rapists,” and telling women that they need to find jobs, be strong and independent, and never serve a filthy man. It was all a pile of shit, but they believed it was like a gospel. It became the religion of the new modern age.

How is a slut shaking her tits on TikTok more valuable than a virgin who would refuse to sleep with any other man but her husband, raise her family and educate her children? We lived in messed up times when the up is down, and being an internet prostitute on a fan site, shoving massive dildos up her asshole until it bled, is somehow considered a career. The girls would cringe in disgust when a twenty-year-old girl admitted she was a virgin, as if it were shameful to not be gang-banged by half the high school football team or suck strangers’ cocks at parties.

I had plenty of daughters now and loved them with all my heart. I knew exactly how to raise them and what values I should impart. They will know what it means to have a loving, supportive family and be raised with a peer group of kids with the same mindset. By the time they passed puberty and became adults, there would be no need to police their minds. All my children would learn to live, be strong and independent with good values. We’ll sit in our tropical estate and watch the Western world eat itself inside out. The only way to win that game was not to play.

I barely recognised Jack as he approached my table and shook my hand. He was the first true friend I made, putting me on a path to fixing my life. It was his advice that guided me to the right place. Jack sent me to Dan. He told me what to read and taught me how to understand the message written between the lines. While Dan focused on my exterior and identity, Jack glued it all together, leading me to discover myself. He made me find the detachment; within it, I found my faith. I finally figured out Jack’s riddles, and they made me laugh.

Jack was right. Only from the summit do you realise that it’s not the mountain that counts, but the climb. All the goals and wishes are just street signs often placed to confuse strangers and try a different road. It made me laugh to remember Jack’s stories, and I finally understood the one about the fish.

“If fishes were wishes,” I said with a smile.

“I would be the fisher of dreams.” He laughed in response. We finally understood each other, and I invited him to share a drink with me.

“I am sorry, my friend. My time is up. I have to leave. My job is done here.” I knew better than to ask the questions; it was another riddle. Jack looked older, and he shaved his head, grew his beard long, and looked thinner and stronger. “We are all on a journey somewhere.” He smiled and nodded.

“When will I see you again?” I asked.

“Oh, don’t worry, Jim. I’ll be around when you need me, but this is a road you have to travel alone.” It was another riddle. I couldn’t keep it in me anymore, so I stood up and hugged the man.

“One last thing, Jim. Do you know the story of Rumpelstiltskin?” Jack asked, grinning from ear to ear. I read it as a child. It was an old German folk tale about a strange little man and a princess who lied so she could marry the king. She bargained with the little man to guess his name or give him her firstborn child in exchange for spinning yarn into gold.

“My name is not Jack. You’ll know how to find me when you figure out my real name.”

Jack’s laughter died out in the distance, leaving me standing, looking confused. That man loved his mystery. It was Jack’s way of playing with me. Jack, or whatever was his name, would remain my friend forever. I knew many people and made many friendships, but the one I had with Jack was special, and I didn’t want to lose it. Dan and Jack are two sides of the same coin. One healed me from the outside, while the other helped me find faith.

I looked around, and the place suddenly seemed so old. I caught myself unconsciously looking for Cassie. This place lost something special when she left. I said my goodbyes to the people I knew and walked out on the street. The rain stopped, and the night was mild, so I made my way into town, one foot in front of the other. No matter how much grudge I held, I knew deep in my heart I would miss this place with so much potential and hope if only the powerful cared.

The next day, I had many business meetings to attend, which involved signing an extensive amount of documents. The London branch of my Monaco bank was officially open. As a result, I only had one item left on my agenda for the day, so I indulged in a hearty meal and hailed a cab.

“Where to go, sir?”

“North London, Pentonville.” The man looked me up and down, turned on his meter and drove us away. Some forty minutes later, we stopped in front of the entrance. A large navy and white plate read, “Welcome to HMP Pentonville. Visitors, please follow the pedestrian route. No unauthorised vehicle allowed beyond this point,” with a royal seal on top.

I’ve never been to a prison before, so I walked on and presented my documents, passed through the scanners and ended up in a visitors section of the detention centre. Pentonville has made many headlines for violence, drug use, and overcrowding. It was the third worst prison in London and not a nice place.

Ten minutes later, a tall, muscular man with tattoos on his knuckles sat down and looked into my eyes with menace. I knew that if we met on the street, he wouldn’t hesitate to throw me a beating.

“What the fuck do you want?”

“Tut-tut, language, please.” He snorted, watching me pull out some pictures I printed of gold coins neatly stacked on yesterday’s newspapers. “Do you know what this is?” The man’s eyes popped. He stared at what I showed him, trying to comprehend what it meant.

“This is impossible. I gave it to…” then it clicked.

“Yes, you made Tina use my children to extort this money and give it to you.”

“But, but, that means that you…”

“Yes,” I laughed, placing all the photographs back in my envelope. The man began hissing at me, vowing to kill me once he was released, calling his friends and having them murder me. I simply shrugged.

“What did you think was going to happen? You are going to fuck my wife, then take my money, and I would just take it? Your biggest mistake was using my kids to threaten me. I could get over anything, but you dared to mess with my kids. Here’s what’s going to happen. In a week, the order will come that they found the gold with ten kilograms of heroin. Your prints will be all over it, and your sentence will triple. You will be classified as a dangerous criminal, and they will transport you to Belmarsh. I’m sure you’ll enjoy that. I paid scholarships for the children of a whole bunch of inmates. You know, the real violent types who like to beat and rape pretty boys like you, and they promised me you’ll have a huge welcome party, and they swore that you won’t spend a single day of your sentence feeling lonely. And before you think about guards, remember that they, too, have kids who all have received a scholarship letter. This is the last time you see me. I just wanted you to know a year from now when you can’t take it anymore and decide to kill yourself. It was all me.”

I stood and walked away, watching the tears roll down the man’s face. He just sat there without words, staring into nothingness. He had no doubt that everything I said was true. A man willing to sacrifice a million pounds to frame another would have no compunction about walking the distance.

The guards arrived to escort him to his cell. I observed his defeated demeanour through the window until he disappeared. Another task accomplished; just tying up the loose ends. The former Jim would have been appalled by this, but I was less concerned about the potential consequences and moral implications. As they say, “actions have consequences.” The man had fucked around a bit too much, and now he was going to find out. The school was back in session, and he just met the principal.

***

“That’s it?” I asked, and my psychiatrist smiled at me.

“Yes, Jim. We are done. You don’t need my help anymore.” It took a long time for me to dig myself out of that hole. It all started about a year before I caught my wife having sex with her ex-boyfriend. I noticed a weird discrepancy in my monthly cash retrieval bills. Tina’s patterns changed, and I was out of pocket about a grand a month through small retrievals at the cash machine.

Typically, such things would never be noticed, but when I was a kid, my mother sent me to all sorts of specialists who diagnosed me with Asperger’s, but not only that. I also had a strange phenomenon, which they probed and dissected for two years before giving up. For some reason, I have always loved numbers. That’s how I learned to program the mainframe at work in hex code. It was just eight-bit binary code represented in a hexadecimal way where the base was sixteen instead of ten, and numbers went from zero to “F.” It was my favourite way of representing numbers.

The strange phenomenon that the doctors noticed was called synesthesia. I didn’t just like the numbers; I loved them. I could physically smell and taste them. Prime numbers tasted like mulberry, and the Fibonacci sequence smelled like forsythia. I was used to the smell and taste of Tina’s spending patterns, making it immediately noticeable as the taste changed.

I hired an investigator, and it took him a week to obtain the pictures for me. The day I received them, I immediately texted everyone that I had an emergency meeting to attend before checking into a hotel room, where I cried the entire weekend. Once I regained my composure, my first thought was of my children, and it took me six months to find the right psychiatrist who could help me cope with what was to come.

He helped me prepare myself and devise a plan to reunite with my children. My psychiatrist assisted me in readying myself and formulating a detailed strategy. One day, I arranged for the kids to be away on a school trip while I texted my wife that I would be working late. I was parked outside, observing through the window as Tina’s former boyfriend entered, followed by my arrival twenty minutes later with flowers in hand. It was then that things began to unfold, marking the commencement of my arduous journey to regain custody of my children.

I knew that the courts would rule in her favour because they were biased, so I did everything I could to tip the scales the other way. It wasn’t enough to get the children; I had to destroy my ex-wife forever, ruin her credibility for future court cases, and make her even doubt her sanity. It was painful but necessary, and my psychiatrist helped me through it, the heartbreak, the revenge. He advised and supported me all the way, and I came to thank the man for his help. The psychiatrist was the only one who knew my plan. He was the only one who saw me for what I was beneath the masks.

“You are a special case, Jim,” the psychiatrist said when we met, studying my case file containing all the tests. I joined MENSA as a teenager and played Bobby Fischer to test myself some years before he died. I won three to nil, but I never had much interest in chess. It was too limiting. I loved to play “Go” with the experts. One day, a friend at a major tech company gave me secret access to their AI “Go” system that got the world champion obliterated, and I won three-nil.

I wasn’t a better player in either case. I just didn’t play the board the same way. This was always the problem with all those games and artificial systems. They were made to adapt to a particular gameplay, looking two or three steps ahead. Those were all just numbers, like a two-dimensional eight-by-eight matrix for chess. And I played all the moves at once. If I flattened the chess board in my head into a sequence of numbers, it was as easy for me to figure out what someone played as tasting vanilla or chocolate. I could literally taste and smell the strategies my opponents played by faking their moves, getting into their minds even before they played them.

“I’m going to teach you how to use this incredible brain of yours to apply it to everything and come up with a plan to win. I will help you win your family back and build an incredible life. I will show you how to use your unique intelligence to create a sequence of events that will lead you to success.” My psychiatrist was right. He taught me how to apply maths to real life and how to recognise patterns and quantify them. He made me see the world in a completely different way.

Some people said I was a genius, but I was far from being one. I merely possessed an extremely narrow focus on an exceedingly small set of problems. Everything revolved around numbers for me. As a result, developing social skills proved to be a daunting undertaking. It required a highly skilled and knowledgeable teacher, coupled with a substantial effort on my part to decipher it in a manner that my brain could comprehend. My psychiatrist helped me with that.

My colleagues never understood why it was difficult for me to socialise, and I never understood their lack of self-confidence to try to improve. I started with a mental handicap as far as socialising was concerned and had to work ten times as hard to learn the basics as most people. It always baffled me when I looked at others living sullen, unexciting lives and constantly complaining about it. The men I knew lived in loveless marriages with a wife and children, turning into sole providers, finally getting divorced and doing nothing to change their future.

My psychiatrist was right; it hurt like hell when I got divorced. I cried and felt like killing myself, sinking deeper into depression, and experiencing the most terrible pain I ever felt in my life. He kept me stable, sane, and focused, spending hours on the phone with me, focused on my plan. As I sank deeper into depression, I lost my faith, most notably the belief in myself, and the days got darker as the world got smaller. Then, one day, everything changed, and I bought that lottery ticket. It was the catalyst, and I needed to put my life in order.

I made a plan, then another. It was like a game of “Go,” only much more sophisticated, so I played all the moves at once in my head, tweaking the numbers and shaping reality by tilting the table instead of applying gambits and strategies. Most men don’t fight when they lose, happily forking out cash just for the opportunity to see their children once a week, always on a short leash, but that was not what I wanted. I loved my boys and wanted to teach them how to become men, so I had to learn it myself.

“To see you happy and well-balanced is all the thanks that I need,” the psychiatrist said. I offered him money, but he just laughed and waved his hand.

“Thank you, doctor, for everything.”

“Our time is up, Jim. I am not your psychiatrist any more, only your friend. You don’t have to call me doctor now.” I nodded and smiled.

“Thank you, Cyrus.” We shook hands, and I was off.

Epilogue

“That’s quite some place you’ve got here, Jim,” Owen said, stretching out on his comfortable sun bed, sipping a Gaspard Fresh cocktail and nibbling on chocolate-covered figs and dates. He had recently retired after successfully taking his company to the next level and absorbing my former New York business just as planned. He signed a direct perpetual contract with my Dubai firm before we left, which made me an additional ten million dollars in yearly royalties. In return, I gave him a beautiful villa in Belle Mare. We both benefited from our arrangement.

“You did well for yourself, Jim,” he commented, admiring Anya’s luxurious body, heavily pregnant again. Someone, somewhere, knew how many kids I had. I refused to count them. I loved them as much as a father could love his sons and daughters, and I refused to quantify them.

Perhaps it was a silly way to think, but my life used to be controlled by numbers. I refused to count my women or children, as I loved them all more than I loved myself.

Owen decided to spend half a year in Belle Mare and the other half somewhere in Europe. I suspected it would be Frankfurt, spending his hard-earned gains helping young, beautiful women through schools and universities. The wolf changes its fur, not his character. It didn’t matter to me; I was retired.

I decided to spend a week every couple of months in Dubai and a month a year in Monaco, but most of my time would be spent with my women and kids in Belle Mare, enjoying the fruits of my labour. It would take another decade to build the estate. New villas were opening every day, with new families moving in, meeting the neighbours, and making new friends.

The club, a former hotel, was always occupied, serving great food and drinks by gorgeous ladies, all of whom worked for me directly or one of my women. Since we got rid of local staff, I relaxed the rules on wearing swimwear. It was common for the girls to swim or sunbathe in the nude with no risk of someone from the outside snapping some pictures, making The Club one of the worst-kept secrets in the community of multimillionaires. It made just over five hundred million in yearly membership alone. We were making so much money that we didn’t know what to do with it, but the girls somehow found new and very profitable opportunities.

“Opportunities multiply as they are seized,” the quote went. Sometimes, I wish Sun Tzu was still alive. He would make a great teacher for my children.

Sometimes, I would sit by the beach watching dawn and think about my life, remembering my friend Jack and all the books I’ve read, what I learned, and how it changed me. My girls would sit next to me, and I would tell them stories. It was the faith, belief, and connection with something greater that connects us to the universe, to each other, and to ourselves.

The girls adored the story of Origin, the religion from the books Jack recommended. It all began as a prank, but as time passed, more and more girls joined in. Over the months that followed, it became a custom for my girls to walk out onto the beach at dawn to welcome the sun, humming the frequency of the world waking up and feeling grateful for the gift of light, the gift of life, the gift of love, the gift of children, and all the other blessings that most of us take for granted. One by one, they all found faith.

“Why did you choose me?” I asked Cassie one day. We walked on the beach at sunset, holding hands while the kids ran behind us, playing in the sand and finding little shells to collect. I knew it wasn’t for my looks, status or money. That was common in The Chamber. She looked into my eyes, giggled like a child, licked my cheek and ran off while I chased her like we were playing tag.

“I saw who you are inside,” Cassie said, still breathing heavily from the chase. “It was the strength of your character, capability to love, intelligence, and honesty. I saw all that you could be.” Cassie could take any guy and make him successful and wealthy. She knew the right people and had all the contacts.

“You are a strange character, Jim. You never cared about money or wealth—about your kids, loving and being loved. Money to you was always like a high score in a game. You got it because you could, and it meant nothing to you. It could buy you nothing you valued.” Cassie waved, pointing with her hand at everything I created.

“This is all just a game for you, an entertainment. I took you for who you are inside. I saw the man you wanted to become and fell in love.” I pulled her into my arms and kissed her, loving her more than ever. Cassie was always the astute one who never spoke in long sentences. All of the women I loved gave me something special. They invested themselves in my dream and made it real.

Life can be a cruel game, and relationships can sometimes be the same. At the end of the day, when you remove society, all those masks, and strip all the paints we are coloured with, what is left is who we are underneath, the nature without nurture, inside our DNA.

I tried to analyse it this way or another, but whichever formula I used was unbalanced. In the end, the only thing a woman has to offer to a man is not companionship or physical intimacy, like what some were trying to brainwash us to believe. It is a child, a family. Kids are the only true thing we have to offer to each other.

Suppose I were a rich man who could afford big houses, yachts, and abundant gorgeous women. What is the one thing that differentiates one from another? Sooner or later, it all becomes a blur and loses its meaning. It is possible to get bored with French cuisine and desire something simple like ice cream.

It is the children. It was always them. They are the ones that make the equation balanced. I didn’t know if a god existed, but I found my faith. I may live through the lives of my future grandchildren. Imagine the beauty, the art and science, the culture they would develop someday. None of this would be possible without having children. It was the only worthwhile investment in life, even if they end up hating you in the end because it isn’t even about us, but about them.

***

Life continues predictably, with each day bringing us its rewards and challenges. We loved each other more with every passing moment. We brought children into this world, fed them and clothed them, raised them, and taught them, gave them faith. Most of my girls fell pregnant again, even Lana and Luna, who each gave me triplets, three sons and three daughters. Tara gave me two healthy boys. She was pregnant again and wanted more.

While girls would stand on the beach at dawn, I would go for a walk to watch the sunrise and listen to the hum of the sea and the world awakening to the new day. Sometimes, I think and remember the road I took to get here, walking barefoot on the beach, feeling white coral sand slip between my toes, tasting an exotic tropical cocktail in the morning air, like a rum punch with coconut milk and the slightest tinge of salt on a sea breeze. It made me lick my lips, instantly drunk on life.

My mind would go back to the lottery ticket. I had it framed and hanging on the wall of my home. It always made me smile how, like a butterfly effect, a single flap of the wings could change the universe. That losing ticket won me something incredible. I remember looking at it and imagining what would have happened if I had won millions with it.

The ticket made me realize that there were other ways. It dared me to imagine a world where everything could be different. If all of this was an illusion and the world was like a computer game, there was a way to bend the rules and shoot for a high score. My imagination changed everything for me, and I had an epiphany. Anything is possible if you can imagine it.

I saw Nathan running towards me with wide-open eyes and a big smile. He was the most curious of all my kids and had just turned five.

“What are you doing daddy?” I rustled his hair, picked up a driftwood stick, and stood by the water.

“I am fishing for the moon made of cheese,” I said, and Nathan looked into the ocean for a minute.

“I can see it, Daddy. It’s there.“ He pointed his little finger. I pointed mine and traced an imaginary line.

“Can you see the boy riding a golden whale over there?“ Nathan squealed, clapping his hands. I hugged him closer, and we sat on the sand, watching the angels in diamond dresses dance ballet on the waves.

“I love you, Daddy,” Nathan said, and I kissed his little blonde head.

“I love you too, my son.” This was all I ever wanted from life.

“Power tends to corrupt, and absolute power corrupts absolutely. Great men are almost always bad men, even when they exercise influence and not authority.” Lord Acton’s wise words echoed through my conscience, and I chuckled, rustling Nathan’s hair, and looked far into the distance. There is no light without darkness or joy without pain. You can’t have a rainbow without a little rain.